<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926148987486X</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(89)87486-X</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-000926148987486X</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(89)87486-X</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(89)87486-X</pii><dc:title>Author index to volume 155 </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>155</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>6</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>625</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>634</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>625-634</prism:pageRange><prism:number>6</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1989-03-17</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>17 March 1989</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1989  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:description/><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926148987486X" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/000926148987486X" rel="scidir"/></coredata><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20011115">2001-11-15</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20011115">2001-11-15</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2015-09-25T15:41:42</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926148987486X</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(89)87486-X</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926148987486X</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(89)87486-X</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.2</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-ONLY</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X11980</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20150927">2015-09-27T16:41:14.793852-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19890317</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1989</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1005782400">2001-11-15T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav articletitle</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>155</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>155</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>6</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>6</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 155, Issue 6</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>23</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>625</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>634</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>625</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>634</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19890317</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>17 March 1989</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1989-03-17</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1989</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>mis</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1989  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>AUTHORINDEXVOLUME155</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:refkeys/>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(89)87486-X</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926148987486X</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926148987486X</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(89)87486-X</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2015-09-27T16:41:14.793852-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1989-03-17</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926148987486X-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926148987486X/MAIN/application/pdf/4e049931121cbb5295a577dd551a14ff/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926148987486X/MAIN/application/pdf/4e049931121cbb5295a577dd551a14ff/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>710388</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>10</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926148987486X-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926148987486X/PREVIEW/image/png/09fded54dec77dc6d93b05778d55e521/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926148987486X/PREVIEW/image/png/09fded54dec77dc6d93b05778d55e521/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>63979</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>Volume 155, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  17 March 1989  AUTHOR INDEX TO VOLUME 155    Acker, W.P., D.H. Leach and R.K. Chang, Stokes and anti-Stokes hyper-Raman scattering  from benzene, deuterated benzene, and carbon tetrachioride  Adrian, F.J., K. Akiyama, K.U. Ingold and J.K.S. Wan, The effects of hyperfine interaction  and radical concentration on the relative contributions of ST0 and ST_ mixing in CIDEP  Ahlrichs, R., see D.J. Swanton  Akiyama, K., see F.J. Adrian  Akiyama, V., K. Tanaka and T. Tanaka, Infrared diode laser spectroscopy of the SiF~ ion  Allaf, A.W., G.Y. Matti, R.J. Suffolk and J.D. Watts, The production and photoelectron  spectrum of thiazyl iodide. NSI  Amezian, K. and M.C. Bacchus-Montabonel, Ab initio potential energy curves for several  molecular states of the multiply charged ion (OHe )64  Arikawa, T., see V. Matsumi  Atakan, B., A. Jacobs, M. Wahl, R. Weller and J. Wolfrum, Kinetic measurements and  product branching ratio for the reaction NH2 + NO at 294 1027 K  Avdievich, N.L, E.G. Bagryanskaya, Yu.A. Grishin and R.Z. Sagdeev, Time-resolved stim-  ulated nuclear polarization  155 (1989) 491  155  155  155  155  (1989) 333  (1989) 329  (1989) 333  (1989) 15  155 (1989) 32    155 (1989) 199  155 (1989) 486    155 (1989) 609    155 (1989) 141  Bacchus-Montabonel, M.C., see K. Amezian  Bagchi, B. and A. Chandra, Solvation of an ion and of a dipole in a dipolar liquid: how  different are the dynamics?  Bagryanskaya, E.G., see N.I. Avdievich  Bahnrnaier, A.I-l., R.-D. Urban and H. Jones, The infrared spectrum of two isotopic species  of indium hydride ( 5InH and  3InH)  Balakrishnan, A., W.J. Jones, C.CI. Mahajan and B.P. Stoicheff, Vibronic spectrum of XeKr  and determination of ground and excited state dissociation energies  Barrientos, C., see A. Largo-Cabrerizo  Barron, L.D., see P.K. Bose  Bartlett, R.J., S.A. Kucharski and J. Noga, Alternative coupled-cluster ansAtze II. The un-  itary coupled-cluster method  Baskin, J.S., see D.S. Tinti  Bassi, D., see M. Scotoni  Bauerle, P., see K. Ulrich  Begemann, M.I-I., R.W. Dreyfus and J.M. Jasinski, Absolute rate constants for the reaction  of SiH with hydrogen, deuterium and silane  Begemann, M.H., see J.O. Chu  Benito, R.M. and J. Santamaria, Contributions of parent molecule fixed and excess ener-  gies to product energy partitioning in four-center elimination reactions  Bergstrom, H., H. Hallstadius, H. Lundberg and A. Persson, Detection of carbon using am-  plified laser-induced fluorescence  Berkowitz, M., see M. Rami Reddy  Bianconi, A., see M.V. Russo  155 (1989) 199    155 (1989) 533  155 (1989) 141    155 (1989) 269    155 (1989) 43  155 (1989) 550  155 (1989) 423    155 (1989) 133  155 (1989) 243  155 (1989) 233  155 (1989) 437    155 (1989) 351  155 (1989) 576    155 (1989) 391    155 (1989) 27  155 (1989) 173  155 (1989) 599  625  volume 155, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  17 March 1989  Bickelhaupt, F., see 0. Grabandt  Bielecki, A., A.C. Kolbert and M.H. Levitt, Frequency-switched pulse sequences: homo-  nuclear decoupling and dilute spin NMR in solids  Billing, G.D. and 0. Jolicard, On the application of the adiabatic invariance method for  the identification of  quantum chaos   Bitto, H., see H.-P. Lutz  Blasse, 0., J. Sytsma and L.H. Brixner, X-ray excited Gd3~ emission in the PbFC1 struc-  ture: higher-level emission and vibronics  Boens, N., see A. Malliaris  Boesl, U., see K. Walter  Bogey, M., C. Demuynck and J.L. Destombes, Millimeter wave spectrum of MgC1 X2E~  and isotopomers in different vibrational states. Determination of mass-invariant  parameters  Bondybey, V.E., see M.F. Cai  Boschetti, A., see M. Scotoni  Bose, P.K., Li?. Baron and P.L. Polavarapu, Ab initio and experimental vibrational Ra-  man optical activity in (+ )-(R)-methylthiirane  Bowman, R.M. and K.B. Eisenthal, The role of translational friction in isomerization  reactions  Brearley, AM. and D.B. McDonald, Picosecond fluorescence study of the energy depen-  dence of geminate recombination kinetics in nonpolar liquids  Brenton, A.G., see M. Hamdan  Brixner, L.H., sec 0. Blasse  Burton, N.A., I.H. Hillier, M.F. Guest and J. Kendrick, Pseudopotential calculations of the  geometry and ionization energies of palladium(II) acetylacetonate  Busmann, H.-G., see H. Staerk    Cacelli, 1., V. Carravetta, A. Rizzo and R. Moccia, Two-photon ionization calculations. Re-  sults for H20  Cai, M.F., T.P. Dzugan and V.E. Bondybey, fluorescence studies of laser vaporized alu-  minum: evidence for a 3fl,, ground state of aluminum dimer  Callear, A.B. and l.A. Cooper, Combination of CH3 with CHO  Campbell, S.A., R. Lowry, R.D. Newmark and L.M. Peter, 207Th NMR and Raman spec-  troscopy of lead ethanoate and lead perchiorate in aqueous solution  Carravetta, V., see I. Cacelli  Chandra, A., see B. Bagchi  Chang, R.K., see W.P. Acker  Cheskis, SO., A.A. kgansen, P.V. Kulakov, 1.Yu. Razuvaev, 0.M. Sarkisov and A.A. Titov,  OH vibrational distribution in the reaction 0(1 D) + CH4  Chesnoy, J., see A. Mokhtari  Chu, J.0., M.H. Begemann, J.S. MclCillop and J.M. Jasinski, Quantum yield studies of dis-  ilane photodissociation at 193 nm by infrared diode laser spectroscopy  Cogdell, R,J., see J. Ullrich  Cooper, D.L. and K. Kirby, Theoretical study of the (3sa) fl Rydberg state of CO, Chem.  Phys. Letters 152 (1988) 393. Erratum  Cooper, l.A., see A.B. Callear  155 (1989) 221    155 (1989) 341    155 (1989) 521  155 (1989) 251    155 (1989) 64  155 (1989) 587  155 (1989) 8      155 (1989) 265  155 (1989) 430  155 (1989) 233    155 (1989) 423    155 (1989) 99    155 (1989) 83  155 (1989) 321  155 (1989) 64    155 (1989) 195  155 (1989) 603      155 (1989) 210    155 (1989) 430  155 (1989) 146    155 (1989) 89  155 (1989) 210  155 (1989) 533  155 (1989) 491    155 (1989) 37  155 (1989) 593    155 (1989) 576  155 (1989) 363    155 (1989) 624  155 (1989) 146  626  Volume 155, number 6  CHEMECAL PHYSICS LETTERS  17 March 1989  Cousins, L.M. and S.R. Leone, Time-of-flight measurements of hyperthermal Cl2 molecules  produced by UV laser vaporization of cryogenic chlorine films  Cox, R.A., see G.D. Hayman  Crouch, S.R., see Y.-Y.J. Wu  Cunha, M., see T. Fonseca    Danielewicz-Ferchmin, I., On the non-linear dielectric effect in some non-polar liquids and  nitrobenzene  Dargelos, A., see M. Papailhou  Das, S.K., see R. Debnath  Davoli, I., see M.V. Russo  Debnath, R. and S.K. Das, Site-dependent luminescence of Cu + ions in silica glass  De Lange, C.A., see 0. Grabandt  Demuynck, C., see M. Bogey  DePristo, A.E., K. Haug and H. Metiu, A new method for calculating time-dependent  quantum correlation functions for systems with many degrees of freedom  Dc Schryver, F.C., see A. Malliaris  Destombes, J.L., see M. Bogey  Diercksen, G,H.F. and A.J. Sadlej, A possible determination of the nuclear quadrupole mo-  ment of 9Be from molecular calculations of electric properties of BeH~  Dorn, H.C., R. Gitti, K.H. Tsai and T.E. Glass, The flow transfer of a bolus with  H dy-  namic nuclear polarization from low to high magnetic fields  Dreyfus, R.W., see M.H. Begemann  Dzugan, T.P., see M.F. Cai    Ebben, M., see M. Scotoni  Eisenthal, K.B., see R.M. Bowman  Ejiri, A., see K. Nakagawa  Engel, V. and H. Metiu, The study of Na! predissociation with pump probe femtosecond  laser pulses: the use of an ionizing probe pulse to obtain more detailed dynamic  information  Ernst, WE., JO. SchrOder and B. Schaal, Hyperfine structure of the X2E~ and B2E~ states  of SrI measured by polarization spectroscopy  Ernst, W.E., see J. Kdndler    Fain, B., see S.H. Lin  Fonseca, T. and M. Cunha, Time-dependent solvation effects on the rate of nonradiative  electronic relaxation in solution  Fujimura, V., see T. Noguchi  Furlani, A., see M.V. Russo    Geers, A., J. Kappert, F, Temps and J.W. Wiebrecht, State-selective vibrational excitation  of OH (X 2fl) radicals by stimulated emission pumping  Georgiou, A.S., D.J. Millen, Z. Kisiel and A.C. Legon, Analysis of a Coriolis interaction  between the in-plane and out-of-plane hydrogen bond bending modes in the dimer of  oxirane and hydrogen fluoride  Gerber, R.B., see L. Shen  Gitti, R., see H.C. Dorn  (1989) 162   (1989) 1   (1989) 69  (1989) 385      (1989) 539  (1989) 406  (1989) 52  (1989) 599  (1989) 52  (1989) 221  (1989) 265  155  155  155  155      155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155 (1989) 376  155 (1989) 587  155 (1989) 265    155 (1989) 127    155 (1989) 227  155 (1989) 351  155 (1989) 430    155 (1989) 233  155 (1989) 99  155 (1989) 278      155 (1989) 77    155 (1989) 47  155 (1989) 470    155 (1989) 216    155 (1989) 385  155 (1989) 177  155 (1989) 599      155 (1989) 614      155 (1989) 447  155 (1989) 119  155 (1989) 227  627  volume i 55, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  17 March 1989  Glass, T.E., see H.C. Dorn  Glinski, R.J. and C.D. Taylor, Effects of isotopic substitution on the chemiluminescence  spectra obtained during the reaction of F2 with CS2  Gordon, E.B., V.V. Khmelenko, A.A. Pelmenev, E.A. Popov and 0.F. Pugachev, Impurity-.  helium van der Waals crystals  Grabandt, 0., C.A. de Lange, R. Mooyman, T. van der Does and F. Bickelhaupt, He (I)  photoelectron spectroscopy of diisocyanogen (CNNC)  Greiner, S.P., J. Winzenburg, B. von Maltzan, C.J. Winscom and K. MObius, A resonance  Raman study of selected tetraphenylporphyrin dimers and their monomer constituents  Greis, J., see J. Ullrich  Grishin, Yu.A., see NI. Avdievich  Guest, M.F., see N.A. Burton    Hallstadins, H., see H. Bergstrom  Halpern, J.B., G.E. Miller and H. Okabe, The reaction of CN radicals with cyanoacetylene  Hamdan, M. and AG. Brenton, First experimental observation of vibrationally excited  N02~(X2E~, A211)  Harrison, J.A. and R.G.A.R. Maclagan, Ab initio potential energy surfaces for the reaction  of BH2 with NO  I-laser, M., see D.J. Swanton  Haug, K., see A.E. DePristo  Hayman, G.D. and R.A. Cox, UV absorption spectrum and thermochemistry of C1203  formed in the photolysis of OCIO-containing mixtures at low temperatures  Herbst, E. and G. Winnewisser, An experimentally derived torsional potential function for  HSSH  Hillier, I.H., see N.A. Burton  Hirst, P.R., see R.C.T. Slade  Hoeft, J. and K,P.R. Nair, The rotational spectra of indium monochloride: molecular con-  stants and breakdown of the Born Oppenheimer approximation  Hoffmann, 0., D. Oh, H. lams and C. Wittig, Reactions of hot H atoms with N2O under  single-collision, gas-phase conditions and in photoexcited N20 HBr complexes:  OH(X2fl)+N2 OH(A2E)+N2, and NH(X3~)+NO(X2fl) channels  Huber, J.R., see H.U. Suter  Huber, JR., see H.-P. Lutz  Hufnagel, F., see J.K. Vij  Hunt, P.M., see Y.-V.J. Wu    lams, H., see 0. Hoffmann  Ingold, K.U., see F.J. Adrian  Iogansen, A.A., see S.G. Cheskis  Irzhak, V.!., see A.B. Raukhvarger  Isenor, N.R. and J. Qi, Anomalous fragmentation in the electron-impact ionization of SF6  and SiP4 in Ar clusters    Jacobs, A., see B. Atakan  Jasinski, J.M., see M.H. Begemann  Jasinski, J.M., see J.O. Chu  155 (1989) 227    155 (1989) 511    155 (1989) 301    155 (1989) 221    155 (1989) 93  155 (1989) 363  155 (1989) 141  155 (1989) 195    155 (1989) 27  155 (1989) 347    155 (1989) 321    155 (1989) 419  155 (1989) 329  155 (1989) 376   155 (1989) 1    155 (1989) 572  155 (1989) 195  155 (1989) 305    155 (1989) 273      155 (1989) 356  155 (1989) 203  155 (1989) 251  155 (1989) 153  155 (1989) 69    155 (1989) 356  155 (1989) 333  155 (1989) 37  155 (1989) 455    155 (1989) 283    155 (1989) 609  155 (1989) 351  155 (1989) 576  628  Volume 155, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  17 March 1989  Johnson, P.M., see S. Sharpe  Johnson, S.G. and G.J. Small, Spectral hole burning of a strongly exciton-coupled bacter-  iochlorophyll a antenna complex  Jolicard, G., see G.D. Billing  Jones, H., see A.H. Bahnmaier  Jones, R.G., see N.K. Siagh  Jones, W.J., see A. Balakrishnan  Jovania, B., see V. Uroevia    Kalpouzos, C., D. McMorrow, W.T. Lotshaw and G.A. Kenney-Wallace, Femtosecond laser-  induced optical Kerr dynamics in CS2/alkane binary solutions  Kandler, J., T. Martell and W.E. Ernst, Electric dipole moments and hyperfine structure of  SrF At and B2I~  Kappert, J., see A. Geers  Kashiwagi, H., see M. Saito  Kawasaki, M., see Y. Matsumi  Kendrick, J., see N.A. Burton  Kenney-Wallace, GA., see C. Kalpouzos  Khmelenko, V.V., see E.B. Gordon  Kimura, K., see K. Nakagawa  Kinugawa, T., see V. Matsumi  Kirby, K., see D.L. Cooper  Kisiel, Z., see A.S. Georgiou  Knowles, P.J., Very large full configuration interaction calculations  Kobarai, K., see M. Tsuji  Kolbert, A.C., see A. Bielecki  Kownacki, K., see P. Myslinski  Kucharski, S.A., see R.J. Bartlett  Kuhnle, W., see H. Staerk  Kulakov, P.V., see S.G. Cheskis  Kunkel, W.B., see G.C. Stutzin    Largo-Cabrerizo, A, and C. Barrientos, Theoretical studies of potential astrophysical mol-  ecules. The CICC and SC2H radicals  Laubereau, A., see A. Molchtari  Leach, D.H., see W.P. Acker  Lee, C.J., Dynamics of interaction of a spin with a radiation field: a consistent full-quantum  mechanical treatment  Legon, A.C., see A.S. Georgiou  Leone, SR., see L.M. Cousins  Leroi, G.E., see Y.-V.J. Wu  Leung, K.N., see G.C. Stutzin  Levine, R.D., see I. Oppenheim  Levitt, M.H., see A. Bielecki  Lezius, M. and T.D. Mark, Direct experimental evidence for the Coulomb explosion of  doubly charged argon cluster ions. Ar~4  Lin, S.H. and B. Fain, Application of the theory of two-dimensional spectroscopy to the  real-time femtosecond transition state spectroscopy  155 (1989) 262    155 (1989) 371  155 (1989) 521  155 (1989) 269  155 (1989) 463  155 (1989) 43  155 (1989) 325      155 (1989) 240    155 (1989) 470  155 (1989) 614  155 (1989) 557  155 (1989) 486  155 (1989) 195  155 (1989) 240  155 (1989) 301  155 (1989) 278  155 (1989) 486  155 (1989) 624  155 (1989) 447  155 (1989) 513  155 (1989) 481  155 (1989) 341  155 (1989) 256  155 (1989) 133  155 (1989) 603  155 (1989) 37  155 (1989) 475      155 (1989) 550  155 (1989) 593  155 (1989) 491    155 (1989) 399  155 (1989) 447  155 (1989) 162  155 (1989) 69  155 (1989) 475  155 (1989) 168  155 (1989) 341    155 (1989) 496    155 (1989) 216  629  Volume 155, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  17 March 1989  Lotshaw, W.T., see C. Kalpouzos  Lowry, R., see S.A. Campbell  Lukovits, I., A simplified normal coordinate analysis of the vibrations of adsorbed molecules  Lundberg, H., see H. BergstrOm  Luo, H., see A. Malliaris  Lutz, H-P., H. Bitto and J.R. Huber, Single vibronic level decays of triplet states in a super-  sonic jet    Maclagan, R.G.A.R., see J.A. Harrison  Magerl, A., see R.C.T. Slade  Mahajan, C.G., see A. Balakrishnan  Mailiaris, A., N. Boens, H. Luo, M. Van der Auweraer, P.C. De Schryver and S. Reekmans,  The micelle water monomer exchange process in solutions of ionic surfactants mea-  sured by transient fluorescence quenching  Malmqvist, ~.-A. and B.O. Roos, The CASSCF state interaction method  Mark, T.D., see M. Lezius  Martell, T., see J. Kandler  Matsumi, V., M. Kawasaki, T. Sato, T. Kinugawa and T. Arikawa, Photodissociation of  chlorine molecule in the UV region  Matsunaga, N., see J.A. Montgomery Jr.  Matsuo, T., see H. Vonemura  Matsuoka, 0., Comments on the basis spinors in Dirac Fock Roothaan calculations  Matsuoka, 0. and S. Okada, Dirac Fock Roothaan calculations on the sixth-row elements  Ti-Rn  Matsushima, T., Anisotropic angular distribution of desorption of CO2 produced on  Pd(llO) surfaces  Matsuura, H., see K. Ohno  Matthews, G.P. and A. Townsend, An effective isotropic pair potential energy function for  carbon dioxide  Matti, G.V., see A.W. Allaf  McDonald, D.B., see A.M. Brearley  McKillop, J.S., see J.O. Chu  McMorrow, D., see C. Kalpouzos  Metiu, H., see V. Engel  Metiu, H., see A.E. DePristo  Millen, D.J., see A.S. Georgiou  Miller, G.E., see J.B. Halpern  Mobius, K., see S.P. Greiner  Moccia, it, see I. Cacelli  Mokhtari, A., J. Chesnoy and A. Laubereau, Femtosecond time- and frequency-resolved  fluorescence spectroscopy of a dye molecule  Montgomery Jr., J.A., G.A. Petersson and N. Matsunaga, On the helium pair potential  Mooyman, R., see 0. Grabandt  Myslinski, P., D. Wieczorek and K. Kownacki, Picosecond fluorescence anisotropy mea-  sured by frequency conversion    Nair, K.P.R., see J. Hoeft  155 (1989) 240  155 (1989) 89  155 (1989) 297  155 (1989) 27  155 (1989) 587    155 (1989) 251    155 (1989) 419  155 (1989) 305  155 (1989) 43      155 (1989) 587  155 (1989) 189  155 (1989) 496  155 (1989) 470    155 (1989) 486  155 (1989) 413  155 (1989) 157  155 (1989) 544    155 (1989) 547    155 (1989) 313  155 (1989) 443    155 (1989) 518   155 (1989) 32   155 (1989) 83  155 (1989) 576  155 (1989) 240  155 (1989) 77  155 (1989) 376  155 (1989) 447  155 (1989) 347  155 (1989) 93  155 (1989) 210    155 (1989) 593  155 (1989) 413  155 (1989) 221    155 (1989) 256    155 (1989) 273  630  volume 155, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  17 March 1989  Nakagawa, K., A. Ejiri, M. Nishikawa and K. Kimura, Density effect on structures in pho-  toconductivity excitation spectra of supercritical xenon doped with anthraccne molecules  Nakamura, H., see H. Vonemura  Nakano, H., see T. Nogami  Neely, W.C., El. Newhouse, S. Pathirana and S.D. Worley, An AMI SCF MO study of the  reaction of formaldehyde with atomic oxygen  Newhouse, E.I., see W.C. Neely  Newmark, R.D., see S.A. Campbell  Nishikawa, M., see K. Nakagawa  Nishimura, V., see M. Tsuji  Noga, J., see R.J. Bartlett  Nogami, T., H. Nakano, V. Shirota, S. Umegaki, V. Shimizu, T. Uemiya and N. Vasuda,  Optical second-harmonic generation from a series of [cyano (aikyloxycarbonyl )- meth-  ylene ] -2-ylidene- 1, 3-dithioles and their methyl and dimethyl derivatives  Nognchi, T., S. Sato and V. Fujimura, Coriolis coupling effects on the angular distribution  of photoelectrons from time-resolved two-photon ionization of polyatomic molecules  155 (1989) 278  155 (1989) 157  155 (1989) 338  155  155  155  155  155  155  (1989) 381  (1989) 381  (1989) 89  (1989) 278  (1989) 481  (1989) 133  Obase, H., see M. Tsuji  Oh, D., see 0. Hoffmann  Oh no, K. and H. Matsuura, The C P stretching vibration of phenylmethylidynephosphine  PhC~P studied by infrared spectroscopy  Okabe, H., see J.B. Halpern  Okada, S., see 0. Matsuoka  Oppenheim, I. and R.D. Levine, Proposed cooperative model of dissociative chemisorption    Paldus, J., see S. Zarrabian  Panit, B., see V. Uroevia  Papailhou, M., C. Pouchan and A. Dargelos, A theoretical study of the vibrational structure  of the 2A1 band in NF3: potential curves and Franck Condon analysis  Pathirana, S., see W.C. Neely  Pelmenev, A.A., see E.B. Gordon  Persson, A., see H. BergstrOm  Peter, L.M., see S.A. Campbell  Petersson, G.A., see J.A. Montgomery Jr.  Polavarapu, P.L., see P.K. Bose  Popov, E.A., see E.B. Gordon  Porsch, F. and H. Stegemeyer, Electrostriction of liquid crystalline blue phases  Port, H., see K. Ulrich  Pouchan, C., see M. Papailhou  Pugachev, O.F., see E.B. Gordon  155 (1989) 338    155 (1989) 177    155 (1989) 481  155 (1989) 356  (1989) 443  (1989) 347  (1989) 547  (1989) 168  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155  155 (1989) 183  155 (1989) 325  (1989) 406   (1989) 381   (1989) 301   (1989) 27   (1989) 89  (1989) 413   (1989) 423   (1989) 301  (1989) 620  (1989) 437  (1989) 406   (1989) 301  Qi, J., see N.R. Isenor    Raas, M.C., see A.H.M. Sondag  Rami Reddy, M. and M. Berkowitz, The dielectric constant of SPC/E water  Rasing, Th., see X.D. Zhu  Ratner, M.A., see L. Shen  155 (1989) 283    155 (1989) 503  155 (1989) 173  155 (1989) 459  155 (1989) 119  631  Volume 155, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEflERS  17 March 1989  Raukhvarger, A.B., M.Ve. Solovyov and V.1. Irzhak, Microphase segregation during de-  formation of elastomers  Razuvaev, I.Vu., see 8.0. Cheskis  Reekmans, S., see A. Malliaris  Reynhardt, E.C., Spin lattice relaxation and molecular motions in amorphous fructose 6-  phosphate  Rizzo, A., see I. Cacelli  Rode, B.M., see M.G. Schwendinger  Roos, B.O., see K-A. Malmqvist  Russo, M.V., A. Furlani, 1. Davoli and A. Bianconi, XANES studies of bis- 1 -oxopyridine-  2-thiolato Pt(It) complexes    Sadlej, A.J., see G.H.F. Diercksen  Sagdeev, R.Z., see N.I. Avdievich  Saito, M. and H. Kashiwagi, An ab initio MO study on the structure dependence of Moss-  bauer spectra in iron porphyrin complexes  Santamarla, J., see R.M. Benito  Sarkisov, 0.M., see S.G. Cheskis  Sarma, C.R., see S. Zarrabian  Sato, S., see T. Noguchi  Sato, T., see V. Matsumi  Savia, P., see V. Uroevit  Schaal, B., see W.E. Emst  Schaefer III, H.P., see B.F. Vntes  Schlachter, AS., see G.C. Stutzin  Schiag, E.W., see K. Walter  SchrOder, J.0., see W.E. Ernst  Schwendinger, M.G. and B.M. Rode, A Monte Carlo simulation of a supersaturated so-  dium chloride solution  Scotoni, M., M. Zen, D. Bassi, A. Boschetti and M. Ebben, An opto-thermal study of NH3  rotational relaxation in NH3 He supersonic expansions  Sharpe, S. and P.M. Johnson, A multiphoton spectrum of the Rydberg region of CC1  Shen, J. and RD. Snook, Thermal lens measurement of absolute quantum yields using  quenched fluorescent samples as references  Shen, L., R.B. Gerber and M.A. Ratner, Static mean-field theory for molecular vibrations:  self-consistent correlation corrections  Shen, Y.R., see X.D. Zhu  Shimizu, V., see T. Nogami  Shirota, V., see T. Nogami  Singh, N.K. and R.G. Jones, A surface phase transition driven by the density of states at  the Fermi level  Slade, R.C.T., P.R. Hirst, B.C. West, R.C. Ward and A. Magerl, Quasielastic neutron scat-  tering investigation of motional processes associated with two dynamic hydrogen pop-  ulations in the bronze ~ 63Mo03  Small, G.J., see S.G. Johnson  Snook, R.D., see J. Shen  Solovyov, M.Ve., see AM. Raukhvarger  155 (1989) 455  155 (1989) 37  155 (1989) 587    155 (1989) 317  155 (1989) 210  155 (1989) 527  155 (1989) 189    155 (1989) 599    155 (1989) 127  155 (1989) 141    155 (1989) 557  155 (1989) 391  155 (1989) 37  155 (1989) 183  155 (1989) 177  155 (1989) 486  155 (1989) 325  155 (1989) 47  155 (1989) 563  155 (1989) 475   155 (1989) 8   155 (1989) 47    155 (1989) 527    155 (1989) 233    155 (1989) 262    155 (1989) 583    155 (1989) 119  155 (1989) 459  155 (1989) 338  155 (1989) 338    155 (1989) 463      155 (1989) 305  155 (1989) 371  155 (1989) 583  155 (1989) 455  632  Volume 155, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEflEES  17 March 1989  Sondag, A.H.M., M.C. Raas and P.N.T. van Velzen, Contamination of aluminium oxide  surfaces in ambient air investigated by FTIR MSR and TOF SIMS. Chemisorption of  aliphatic carboxylic acids  Speer, R., see J. ljllrich  Staerk, H., H.-G. Busmann, W. Kuhnle and A. Weller, Solvent effects on the magnetic-field-  dependent reaction yields of photogenerated radical ion pairs  Stegemeyer, H., see F. Porsch  Stoicheff, B.P., see A. Balakrishnan  Stone, A.J., The induction energy of an assembly of polarizable molecules  Stone, A.J., Assessment of multipolar approximations to the induction energy  Stroh, F. and M. Winnewisser, Ilsocyanogen, CNCN: infrared and microwave spectra and  structure  Stutzin, G.C., A.T. Voung, A.S. Schlachter, K.N. Leung and W.B. Kunkel, In situ mea-  surement of rovibrational populations of H2 ground electronic state in a plasma by VUV  laser absorption  Suffolk, R.J., see A.W. Allaf  Suter, MU. and J.R. Huber, S~ potential energy surface of HONO: absorption spectrum  and photodissociation  Swanton, D.J., R. Ahlrichs and M. HAser, Ab initio SCP calculations of the boron cage mol-  ecules B9H9 and B9C19  Sytsma, J., see G. Blasse    Tanaka, K., see V. Akiyama  Tanaka, T., see V. Akiyama  Tanner, P.A., Vibronic analysis of the (~G5/2)I 9 ._. 6H5,2, 6H712, 6H912 luminescence tran-  sitions of Cs2NaVC16: SmCles3  o  Taylor, C.D., see R.J. Glinski  Temps, F., see A. Geers  Tinti, D.S., J.S. Baskin and A.H. Zewail, Picosecond studies of jet-cooled ehromyl chloride  Titov, A.A., see 5.0. Cheskis  Townsend, A., see G.P. Matthews  Tsai, K.H., see H.C. Don  Tsuji, M., K. Kobarai, S. Vamaguchi, H. Obase, K. Vamaguchi and V. Nishimura, Dis-  sociative excitation of SiH4 by collisions with metastable argon atoms    Uemiya, T., see T. Nogami  Ulirich, J., R. Speer, J. Oreis, J.IJ. von Schlitz, H.C. Wolf and R.J. Cogdell, Carotenoid  triplet states in pigment protein complexes from photosynthetic bacteria: absorption-  detected magnetic resonance from 4 to 225 K  tjlrich, K., H. Port and P. Bauerle, Photochromic thiophenefulgide absorption spectra and  kinetics of photochemical isomerizations  Umegaki, S., see T. Nogami  Urban, R.-D., see A.H. Bahnmaier  Uroevie, V., B. Panie, B. Yovani~, Lj. Zekovie and P. Savie, Effect of pressure on the ruby  fluorescence lifetime    Van der Auweraer, M., see A. Malliaris  Van der Does, T., see 0. Grabandt  155 (1989) 503  155 (1989) 363    155 (1989) 603  155 (1989) 620  155 (1989) 43  155 (1989) 102  155 (1989) 111    155 (1989) 21      155 (1989) 475  155 (1989) 32    155 (1989) 203    155 (1989) 329  155 (1989) 64    155 (1989) iS  155 (1989) 15    155 (1989) 59  155 (1989) 511  155 (1989) 614  155 (1989) 243  155 (1989) 37  155 (1989) 518  155 (1989) 227    155 (1989) 481    155 (1989)338      155 (1989) 363    155 (1989) 437  155 (1989) 338  155 (1989) 269    155 (1989) 325    155 (1989) 587  155 (1989) 221  633  Volume 155, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  17 March 1989  Van der Maarel, J.R.C., Relaxation of spin 3/2 in a nonzero average electric field gradient  Van Velzen, P.N.T., see A.H,M. Sondag  Vij, J.K. and F. Hufnagel, Millimeter and submillimeter laser spectroscopy of water  Von Maltzan, B., see S.P. Greiner  Von Schiitz, J.U., see J. Ullrich    Wahl, M., see B. Atakan  Walter, K., R. Weinkauf, U. Boesl and E.W. Schlag, Spectroscopy of the benzene cation:  resonance-enhanced multiphoton dissociation spectra of the ~ (E2g) ~ ( Ejg) transition  Wan, J.K.S., see F.J. Adrian  Ward, R.C., see R.C.T. Slade  Watts, J.D., see A.W. Aliaf  Weinkauf, R., see K. Walter  Weller, A., see H. Staerk  Weller, R., see B. Atakan  West, B.C., see R.C.T. Slade  Wiebrecht, J.W., see A. Geers  Wieczorek, D., see P. Myslinski  Winnewisser, 0,, see B. Herbst  Winnewisser, M., see F. Stroh  Winscom, C.J., see S.P. Greiner  Winzenburg, J., see S.P. Greiner  Wittig, C., see 0. Hoffmann  Wolf, H.C., see J. Ulirich  Wolfrum, J., see B. Atakan  Worley, S.D., see W.C. Neely  Wu, Y.-Y.J., P.M. Hunt, G.E. Leroi and S.R. Crouch, Dual laser ionization (DLI) mea-  surements of ion mobilities in a H2 02 Ar flame    Vamaguchi, K., see M. Tsuji  Yamaguchi, S., see M. Tsuji  Yasuda, N., see T. Nogami  Yates, B.F. and H.P. Schaefer III, Tetrasilacyclobutadiylidene: the lowest energy cyclic iso-  mer of singlet Si4H4?  Yonemura, H., H. Nakamura and 1. Matsuo, External magnetic field effects on photoin-  duced electron transfer reactions in phenothiazine viologen-linked systems complexed  with cyclodextrins  Young, A.T., see G.C. Stutzin    Zarrabian, S., C.R. Sarma and J. Paldus, Vectorizable approach to molecular CI problems  using determinantal basis  Zekovia, Lj., see V. Uroevia  Zen, M., see M. Scotoni  Zewail, A.H., see D.S. Tinti  Zhu, X.D,, Th. Raring and V.R. Shen, Laser-induced thermal desorption of CO oh Ni( 111):  determination of pre-exponential factor and heat of desorption  155 (1989) 288  155 (1989) 503  155 (1989) 153  155 (1989) 93  155 (1989) 363    155 (1989) 609    155 (1989) 8  155 (1989) 333  155 (1989) 305  155 (1989) 32  155 (1989) 8  155 (1989) 603  155 (1989) 609  155 (1989) 305  155 (1989) 614  155 (1989) 256  155 (1989) 572  155 (1989) 21  155 (1989) 93  155 (1989) 93  155 (1989) 356  155 (1989) 363  155 (1989) 609  155 (1989) 381    155 (1989) 69    155 (1989) 481  155 (1989) 481  155 (1989) 338    155 (1989) 563      155 (1989) 157  155 (1989) 475      155 (1989) 183  155 (1989) 325  155 (1989) 233  155 (1989) 243    155 (1989) 459  634   F., see A. Geers  Tinti, D.S., J.S. Baskin and A.H. Zewail, Picosecond studies of jet-cooled ehromyl chloride  Titov, A.A., see 5.0. Cheskis  Townsend, A., see G.P. Matthews  Tsai, K.H., see H.C. Don  Tsuji, M., K. Kobarai, S. Vamaguchi, H. Obase, K. Vamaguchi and V. Nishimura, Dis-  sociative excitation of SiH4 by collisions with metastable argon atoms    Uemiya, T., see T. Nogami  Ulirich, J., R. Speer, J. Oreis, J.IJ. von Schlitz, H.C. Wolf and R.J. Cogdell, Carotenoid  triplet states in pigment protein complexes from photosynthetic bacteria: absorption-  detected magnetic resonance from 4 to 225 K  tjlrich, K., H. Port and P. Baue</xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="mis" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>8987486X</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(89)87486-X</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(89)87486-X</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="other" year="1989"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Author index to volume 155</ce:title>
         </head>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>