<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926149180320W</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(91)80320-W</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-000926149180320W</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(91)80320-W</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(91)80320-W</pii><dc:title>Author Index to Volume 181 </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>181</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>6</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>591</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>600</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>591-600</prism:pageRange><prism:number>6</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1991-07-12</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>12 July 1991</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1991  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:description/><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926149180320W" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/000926149180320W" rel="scidir"/></coredata><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20011105">2001-11-05</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20011105">2001-11-05</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2015-09-25T08:06:19</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926149180320W</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(91)80320-W</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926149180320W</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(91)80320-W</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.2</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-ONLY</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X10329</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20150927">2015-09-27T08:35:23.217666-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19910712</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1991</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1004918400">2001-11-05T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav articletitle</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>181</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>181</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>6</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>6</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 181, Issue 6</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>21</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>591</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>600</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>591</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>600</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19910712</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>12 July 1991</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1991-07-12</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1991</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>mis</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1991  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>AUTHORINDEXVOLUME181</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:refkeys/>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(91)80320-W</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926149180320W</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926149180320W</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(91)80320-W</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2015-09-27T08:35:23.217666-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1991-07-12</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926149180320W-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926149180320W/MAIN/application/pdf/c62c300f598b346c39d62d21b03ea16b/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926149180320W/MAIN/application/pdf/c62c300f598b346c39d62d21b03ea16b/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>641096</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>10</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926149180320W-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926149180320W/PREVIEW/image/png/914d8be4aaa3f7c00acb98661f5dd35f/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926149180320W/PREVIEW/image/png/914d8be4aaa3f7c00acb98661f5dd35f/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>57142</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 July 1991  Author Index to Volume 181  Achiba, Y., see Y. Kajii  Adhikari, S.K., Anomalies of variational phase shifts  Adolph, H.G., see P. Politzer  Agranat, I., T.P. Radhakrishnan, W.C. Herndon and A. Skancke, Evaluation of Y- versus  linear-delocalization and the role of charge alternation in trimethylenemethane dianion  and butadiene dianions  Agrawal, R.K. and VS. Varma, Phase transition in an ensemble of anharmonic oscillators  Akamatsu, N., K. Domen, C. Hirose, T. Onishi, H. Shimizu and K. Masutani, SFG study  of rotational anisotropy of cadmium arachidate Langmuir Blodgett films  Alfimov, MV., see M.F. Budyka  Al Jghgami, I.F., see A.P. Losev  Almlof, J., Elimination of energy denominators in Moller Plesset perturbation theory by  a Laplace transform approach  Almlof, J., see M. Haser  Andreocci, M.V., M. Bossa, A. Furlani, G. Poizonetti and M.V. Russo, todine polyphen-  ylacetylene charge-transfer complex: an ab initio quantum-chemical assessment  Andrews, L., see Z. Mielke  Angerhofer, A,, see V. Aust  Asahi, T., see A. Osuka  Atkinson, J.B., see W. Kedzierski  Aust, V., A. Angerhofer, J. Ulirich, J.U. von SchUtz, H.C. Wolf and R.J. Cogdell, ADMR  of carotenoid triplet states in bacterial photosynthetic antenna and reaction center  complexes    Balasubramanian, K., see Z. Ma  Banerjee, A.K., see L. Kundu  Basche, Th. and C. Brauchle, Temperature dependent hole-burning study of dye molecules  adsorbed on metal oxide powders  Batchelor, S.N., K.A. McLauchlan and l.A. Shkrob, Time-resolved reaction yield detected  magnetic resonance (RYDMR)  Bauschlicher Jr., C.W. and H. Partridge, Mg~ 1igand binding energies  Bauschlicher Jr., C.W., see M. Sodupe  Beavis, R.C. and B.T. Chait, Velocity distributions of intact high mass polypeptide mol-  ecule ions produced by matrix assisted laser desorption  Benning, P.J., see G.H. Kroll  Berlyand, L.V., N.y. Chukanov and V.A. Dubovitsky, Exactly solvable random model and  IR spectroscopy of a strained defective lattice  Bhattacharyya, S.N., see R. Sen  Bhattacharyya, S.P., see R. Sen  Bhattacharyya, S.P., see P. Dutta  Biczok, L., see M. Hugerat   181 (1991) 100   181 (1991) 435   181 (1991) 78   181 (1991) 117   181 (1991) 441   181 (1991) 175   181 (1991) 59   181 (1991) 45   181 (1991) 319   181 (1991) 497   181 (1991) 582   181 (1991) 355   181 (1991) 213  181 (1991) 413, 419   181 (1991) 427      181 (1991) 213    181 (1991) 467  181 (1991) 569    181 (1991) 179    181 (1991) 327  181 (1991) 129  181 (1991) 321    181 (1991) 479  181 (1991) 112    181 (1991) 450  181 (1991) 288  181 (1991) 288  181 (1991) 293  181 (1991) 400  591  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 July 1991  Birk, H. and H. Jones, Diode-laser measurement of the infrared spectrum of tin monosulfide  Bjerre, N., I. Hazell and D.C. Lorents, Spin orbit coupling in Fl3  Bdrner, K., G. Diezemann, E. Rossler and H.M. Vieth, Low-temperature methyl group dy-  namics of hexamethylbenzene in crystalline and glassy matrices as studied by 2H NMR  Bossa, M., see MV. Andreocci  Brauchle, C., see Th. Basche  Budyka, M.F., AG. Rachinsky and M.V. Alfimov, Donor acceptor complexes: the model  of unlimited co-aggregation or polycomplexes formation  Byteva, I.M., see A.P. Losev    Campagnola, P.J., D.M. Cyr and M.A. Johnson, Size-dependent collisional incorporation  of 020 into (H20); around n= 15: implications on the origin of magic numbers in the  hydrated electron cluster distribution  Carrere, D., see L. Schriver  Castleman Jr., A.W., see B.C. Guo  Cederbaum, L.S. and H.-D. Meyer, On natural orbitals for properties  Chabal, Y.J., see P. Dumas  Chait, B.T., see R.C. Beavis  Chen, R., A.G. Marshall and M. Wang, Ion-locked cyclotron resonance: a means for in-  stantaneously changing ion cyclotron orbital radius  Chen, X., see K. Du  Chen, Y., see G.H. Kroll  Chernyak, V. and R. Reisfeld, Speciroscopic behaviour of malachite green in sol gel glasses  Chibante, L.P.F., see G.H. Kroll  Chowdhury, M., see L. Kundu  Chukanov, N.y., see L.V. Berlyand  Cioslowski, J., Electronic structures of the icosahedral C60H60 and C60F60 molecules  Cogdell, R.J., see V. Aust  Colson, S.D., see G. Reiser  Cornell, BA,, see F. Separovic  Cyr, D.M., see P.J. Campagnola  Cyvin, S.J., Note on the series of fully benzenoid hydrocarbons with a constant number  of isomers    Dantus, M., M.H.M. Janssen and A.H. Zewail, Femtosecond probing of molecular dy-  namics by mass-spectrometry in a molecular beam  Darsey, J.A., D.W. Noid and BR. Upadhyaya, Application of neural network computing  to the solution for the ground-state eigenenergy of two-dimensional harmonic oscilla-  tors, Chem. Phys. Letters 177 (1991) 189. Erratum  Datar, A.S. and S.D. Prasad, Adsorbate clustering and surface rates above T~: a modified  mean-field approach  De Santis, A., A. Gregori and D. Rocca, Microscopic configurations and shape of the atom   atom pair distribution function of liquid chlorine  Destro, R., Proton transfer in the solid state: thermodynamic parameters from an X-ray  study in the temperature range 20 293 K  Diezemann, G., see K. Borner  Distefano, G.., see A. Modelli  181 (1991) 245  181 (1991) 301    181 (1991) 563  181 (1991) 582  181 (1991) 179    181 (1991) 59  181 (1991) 45        181 (1991) 206  181 (1991) 505  181 (1991) 16  181 (1991) 163  181 (1991) 537  181 (1991) 479    181 (1991) 168  181 (1991) 344  181 (1991) 112  181 (1991) 39  181 (1991) 112  181 (1991) 569  181 (1991) 450  181 (1991) 68  181 (1991) 213  181 (1991) 1  181 (1991) 157  181 (1991) 206    181 (1991) 431      181 (1991) 281      181 (1991) 386    181 (1991) 445    181 (1991) 579    181 (1991) 232  181 (1991) 563  181 (1991) 361  592  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 July 1991  Domen, K., see N. Akamatsu  Dopfer, 0., see G. Reiser  Down, S.E., see D.E. Manolopoulos  Dressler, R.A., see J.A. Gardner  Drozdov, N.N., see A.P. Losev  Du, K., X. Chen and D.W. Setser, Identification of the SiCl2 (A3B , ~  A1) emission sys-  tern and a flow reactor source of SiCI2 (a3B1)  Dubois, L.H., see B.J. Hinch  Dubovitsky, V.A., see L.V. Berlyand  Dumas, P. and Y..J. Chabal, Electron-energy-loss characterization of the H.terminated  Si (111) and Si (100) surfaces obtained by etching in NH4F  Durup, J., see F.X. Gadea  Dutta, P., D. Majumdar and S.P. Bhattacharyya, Global optimization of molecular ge-  ometry: a new avenue involving the use of Metropolis simulated annealing  Dvorak, M.A., see S.W. Reeve  Dye, R.C., R.E. Muenchausen and N.S. Nogar, Laser ablation of Y203 in an oxygen  atmosphere    Ebbesen, T.W., K. Tanigaki and S. Kuroshima, Excited-state properties of C60    Fallon, P.J., see P.L. Hansen  Fastrup, B., see M. Muhler  Feliz, M. and G. Ferraudi, Mechanism of the photoreversible ClRe(CO)3(4-phenylpyri-  dine)2-induced reduction of a Cu(II) macrocyle  Ferraudi, G., see M. Feliz  Firth, D.W., see S.W. Reeve  Furlani, A., see M.V. Andreocci    Gadea, F.X. and J. Durup, Comment on  Photodissociation of Ar~ cluster ions   Gardner, J.A., R.A. Dressler, R.H. Salter and E. Murad, A laboratory study of charge  transfer and hydrogen atom pickup reactions in N~ H2O( D20) collisions at suprath-  ermal energies  Gerber, R.B. and A.T. Yinnon, Properties of atom scattering from percolation lattices: He  scattering from substitutionally disordered Xe + Kr monolayers  Gole, J.L., see C.B. Winstead  Gotts, N.G., R. Hallett, J.A. Smith and A.J. Stace, A new perspective to the photodisso-  ciation of cluster ions: the detection of neutral fragments following the photoexcitation  of Ar~  Grantier, D., see C.B. Winstead  Gregori, A., see A. De Santis  Grotheer, H.H., see H. Oser  Grotheer, 0., see H. Oser  Guo, B.C. and A.W. Castleman Jr., The bonding strength of Ag~ (C2H4) and Ag~ (C2H4 )2  complexes    Haarer, D., see S. Jahn  Hagiwara, S., see M. Sato  181 (1991) 175  181 (1991) 1  181 (1991) 105  181 (1991) 5  181 (1991) 45    181 (1991) 344  181 (1991) 10  181 (1991) 450    181 (1991) 537  181 (1991) 378    181 (1991) 293  181 (1991) 259    181 (1991) 531    181 (1991) 501    181 (1991) 367  181 (1991) 380    181 (1991) 201  181 (1991) 201  181 (1991)259  181 (1991) 582    181 (1991) 378      181 (1991) 5    181 (1991) 553  181 (1991) 222      181 (1991) 491  181 (1991) 222  181 (1991) 579  181 (1991) 521  181 (1991) 521      181 (1991) 16    181 (1991) 31  181 (1991) 526  593  Volume 181, nuniber 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  l2July 1991  Hallett, R., see N.G. Gotts  Hammond, T., see C.B. Winstead  Hamrick, Y.M., R.J. Van Zee and W. Weltner Jr., ESR of bimetallic transition-metal mol-  ecules: Mo and W with Cu, Ag and Au  Han, K., X. Zheng, B. Sun, U. He and R. Zhang, Chemical reaction dynamics of barium  atom with alkyl bromides  Hansen, P.L., P.J. Fallon and W. Kratschmer, An EELS study of fullerite    Haser, M., J. Almldf and G.E. Scuseria, The equilibrium geometry of C60 as predicted by  second-order (MP2) perturbation theory  Hashimoto, H., see E. Nishizawa  Hayamizu, K., see F. Separovic  Hayashi, H., see M. Igarashi  Hazell, I., see N. Bjerre  He, G., see K. Han  He, K.X., see C.B. Winstead  Henri, G., see G. Reiser  Herndon, W.C., see I. Agranat  Hewitt, T.D. and D. Roy, Optical second harmonic generation as a probe of hydrogen evo-  lution on copper  Hinch, B.J. and L.H. Dubois, Water adsorption on Cu (111): evidence for Volmer Weber  film growth  Hirose, C., see N. Akamatsu  Hollauer, E. and M.A.C. Nascimento, A CASSCF description of the n1t~ singlet and triplet  electronic excited states of the trans-glyoxal molecule  Hong, S.D., see B.J. Yoon  Howard, S.L., Low-energy threshold of the fine-structure transition in rare-gas charge  transfer  Howell, R., A.G. Taylor and D. Phillips, Laser-induced-fluorescence spectroscopy of the  jet-cooled dimer of N-ethylcarbazole  Hugerat, M., H. Levanon, F. Ojadi, L. Biczok and H. Linschitz, Multiple decay pathways  and electron transfer in excited ion-paired zinc copper porphyrins: laser photolysis and  time-resolved EPR spectroscopy  Hynes, A.J., Laser-induced fluorescence of silicon monoxide in a glow discharge and an  atmospheric pressure flame    Igarashi, M., Y. Sakaguchi, H. Hayashi and Y.J. I Haya, Formation of a-keto alkyl radical  in the photoreduction of chromone as studied by the laser photolysis ESR technique  I Haya, Y.J., see M. Igarashi    Jaeger, K., see L. Schriver  Jahn, S., D. Haarer and B.M. Kharlamov, Spectral diffusion in organic glasses measured  by transient hole recovery kinetics on a time scale 1 500 ms  Janssen, M.H.M., see M. Dantus  Jhon, M.S., see B.J. Yoon  Jiang, R.-C. and T.-M. Su, Potassium-containing hypermetalated compounds and their  water complexes: K3OH, K4(OH)2, K2 (OH) (H20) and K3 (OH) (H20)  Johnson, MA., see P.J. Campagnola  181 (1991) 491  181 (1991) 222  181 (1991) 193  181 (1991) 474  181 (1991) 367  181 (1991) 497  181 (1991) 387  181 (1991) 157  181 (1991) 187   181 (1991) 301   181 (1991) 474   181 (1991) 222   181 (1991) 1  181 (1991) 117  181 (1991) 407  181 (1991) 10  181 (1991) 175  181 (1991) 463  181 (1991) 73  181 (1991) 298  181 (1991) 21  181 (1991) 400  181 (1991) 237  181 (1991) 187  181 (1991) 187  181 (1991) 505  181 (1991) 31  181 (1991) 281  181 (1991) 73  181 (1991)373  181 (1991) 206  594  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  l2JuIy 1991  Jones, D., see A. Modelli  Jones, H., see H. Birk  Jones, H., see R.-D. Urban  Judson, R., see D. Neuhauser  181 (1991) 361  181 (1991)245  181 (1991)485  181 (1991) 151  Kajii, Y., T. Nakagawa, S. Suzuki, Y. Achiba, K. Obi and K. Shibuya, Transient absorp-  tion, lifetime and relaxation of C60 in the triplet state  Kalontarov, L.l. and R. Marupov, Nonstationary dynamics of laser-induced destruction of  polymeric solids  Kaneko, K., see M. Sato  Kaziska, A.J., M.L. Shchuka and M.R. Topp, Polarized fluorescence measurements of jet-  cooled 2,5-diphenylfuran and van der Waals complexes  Kedzierski, W., J.B. Atkinson and L. Krause, Laser-induced fluorescence from the  3l1j43D) state of Zn2  Kellman, M.E., Z. Li and L. Xiao, Bond-selected bimolecular reactivity and phase space  structure of intramolecular excited states  Kharlamov, B.M., see S. Jahn  Kimura, K., see M. Takahashi  Kimura, V., see Y. Yoshimura  Kirsten, F., G. Parschau and K.H. Rieder, He diffraction and resonant scattering studies  ofRh(llO)(1xl) 2H  Koyama, Y., see E. Nishizawa  Kratschmer, W., see P.L. Hansen  Krause, L., see W. Kedzierski  Kroll, G.H., P.J. Benning, Y. Chen, T.R. Ohno, J.H. Weaver, L.P.F. Chibante and  R.E. Smalley, Interaction of 02 with C60: photon-induced oxidation  Kundu, L., AK. Banerjee and M. Chowdhury, Two-photon absorption spectrum of gad-  olinium elpasolite  Kuroshima, S., see T.W. Ebbesen  Kuskov, V.L., see G.G. Lazarev    Lane, P., see P. Politzer  Launay, J.M. and S.B. Padkj~er, Quantum-dynamical study of the CI + H2 ~ClH + H reaction  Lazarev, G.G., V.L. Kuskov, Ya.S. Lebedev and A. Riekcr, The mechanism of formation  of stable radical pairs by photolysis of 2,6-di-tert-butyl benzoquinone diazide in crystals  of 2,6-di-tert-butyl-4-methylphenol  Lebedev, Ya.S,, see G.G. Lazarev  Lendvay, G., Fractional bond orders in E2H4 molecules (E = Si, Ge, and Sn)  Leone, S.R., see H.C. Miller  Leopold, K.R., see S.W. Reeve  Leszczynski, J., Theoretical evaluation of new nucleic acid bases. II. Ab initio study on  tautomerism of pyrazolo [4,3-d ]pyrimidine-5,7 (4H,6H )-dione  Levanon, H., see M. Hugerat  Levine, R.D., see F. Remade  Li, Z., see M.E. Kellman  Lindner, R., see G. Reiser  Linschitz, H., see M. Hugerat  181 (1991) 100    181 (1991) 27  181 (1991) 526    181 (1991) 134    181 (1991)427    181 (1991) 141  181 (1991) 31  181 (1991)255  181 (1991) 517    181 (1991) 544  181 (1991)387  181 (1991) 367  181 (1991)427    181 (1991) 112    181 (1991) 569  181 (1991) 501  181 (1991) 512    181 (1991) 78  181 (1991) 95      181 (1991) 512  181 (1991) 512  181 (1991) 88  181 (1991) 250  181 (1991) 259    181 (1991) 123  181 (1991) 400  181 (1991) 307  181 (1991) 141  181 (1991) 1  181 (1991) 400  595  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 July 1991  Lorents, D.C., see N. Bjerre  Losev, A.P., I.N. Nichiporovich, I.M. Byteva, N.N. Drozdov and IF. Al Jghgami, The per-  turbing effect of solvents on the luminescence rate constant of singlet molecular oxygen    Ma, Z. and K. Balasubramanian, Electronic states of WH  Majumdar, D., see R. Sen  Majumdar, D., see P. Dutta  Manolopoulos, D.E., J.C. May and S.E. Down, Theoretical studies of the fullerenes: C34  to C70  Manzanares I., C., Photoacoustic overtone spectroscopy of liquids with continuous wave  laser excitation  March, N.H., see A. Nagy  Marshall, A.G., see R. Chen  Marupov, R., see LI. Kalontarov  Maruyama, K., see A. Osuka  Masutani, K., see N. Akamatsu  Mataga, N., see A. Osuka  May, J.C., see D.E. Manolopoulos  May, V. and M. Schreiber, Electron-transfer dynamics in a donor acceptor complex  MeLauchian, K.A., see S.N. Batchelor  Meijers, H.C. and D.A. Wiersma, Spectral diffusion in glasses: a photon-echo study of  zincporphin in ethanol  MelichereIk, M. and L. Treindl, The ferroin-catalyzed Belousov Zhabotinskii system with  a  clock  behaviour  Meyer, H.-D., see L.S. Cederbaum  Mielke, Z. and L. Andrews, Infrared detection of the PCO radical and HPCO molecule  Miller, H.C., K. Yamasaki, J.E. Smedley and S.R. Leone, An optically pumped ultraviolet  laser on SO(B3~ X3~)  Modelli, A., D. Jones, G. Distefano and M. Tronc, Electron affinity and dissociative elec-  tron attachment in saturated dialkyl group-l 6 derivatives  Muenchausen, R.E., see R.C. Dye  Muhler, M., L.P. Nielsen and B. Fastrup, Comment on  On the role of promoters in pro-  moted iron catalysts used in the industrial synthesis of ammonia   Muller-Dethlefs, K., see G. Reiser  Murad, E., see J.A. Gardner  Murray, J.S., see P. Politzer    Nagy, A. and N.H. March, Kinetic energy in terms of electron density for atomic s and p  shells in a bare Coulomb field  Nakagawa, T., see Y. Kajii  Nakano, H., see T. Nogami  Nascimento, M.A.C., see E. Hollauer  Neuhauser, D., R. Judson and A. Perski, Inelastic probabilities above the three-body  breakup threshold via a projection operator formalism  Nguyen, M.T., K. Pierloot and L.G. Vanquickenborne, Fulminic acid (HCNO): bent ver-  sus linear equilibrium structure?  Nichiporovich, LN., see A.P. Losev  181 (1991) 301  181 (1991) 45  181 (1991) 467  181 (1991) 288  181 (1991) 293  181 (1991) 105  181 (1991) 51  181 (1991) 279  181 (1991) 168   181 (1991) 27  181 (1991) 413, 419   181 (1991) 175  181 (1991) 413, 419   181 (1991) 105  181 (1991) 267  181 (1991) 327  181 (1991) 312  181 (1991) 575  181 (1991) 163  181 (1991) 355  181 (1991) 250  181 (1991) 361  181 (1991) 531   181 (1991) 380   181 (1991) 1   181 (1991) 5   181 (1991) 78   181 (1991) 279  181 (1991) 100  181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 463   181 (1991) 151   181 (1991) 83   181 (1991) 45  596  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 July 1991  Nielsen, L.P., see M. Muhier  Nishimura, Y., see A. Osuka  Nishizawa, E., H. Hashimoto and Y. Koyama, Raman spectrum of bacteriochlorophyll a  in the S~ state  Nogami, T., H. Nakano, Y. Shirota, S. Umegaki, Y. Shimizu, T. Uemiya and N. Yasuda,  Optical second-harmonic generation from a series of [cyano-(alkyloxycar-  bonyl )methylene ] -2-ylidene- 1 ,3-dithiole and their methyl and dimethyl derivates, Chem.  Phys. Letters 155 (1989) 338. Erratum  Nogar, N.S., see R.C. Dye  Noid, D.W., see J.A. Darsey    Obi, K., see Y. Kajii  Ohno, T.R., see G.H. Kroll  Ojadi, E., see M. Hugerat  Onishi, T., see N. Akamatsu  Oser, H., D. Walter, N.D. Stothard, 0. Grotheer and H.H. Grotheer, Application of flow  reactors to very low pressures by using CH3+ 0 (3P) as a test reaction  Osuka, A., K. Maruyama, N. Mataga, T. Asahi, I. Yamazaki, N. Tamai and Y. Nishimura,  Photoinduced electron transfer reactions in quinone-linked zinc porphyrin arrays  Osuka, A., H. Yamada, K. Maruyama, N. Mataga, T. Asahi, I. Yamazaki and Y. Nishimura,  Picosecond dynamics of intramolecular singlet excitation energy transfer and photoin-  duced electron transfer in covalently-linked carotenoid porphyrin and carotenoid por-  phyrin pyromellitimide molecules  Ozeki, H., see M. Takahashi    Padkjnr, S.B., see J.M. Launay  Parschau, G., see E. Kirsten  Partridge, H., see C.W. Bauschlicher Jr.  Perski, A., see D. Neuhauser  Petersson, G.A., see WA. Shirley  Phillips, D., see R. Howell  Picorel, R., see N.R.S. Reddy  Pierloot, K., see M.T. Nguyen  Politzer, P., J.S. Murray, P. Lane, P. Sjoberg and H.G. Adolph, Shock-sensitivity relation-  ships for nitramines and nitroaliphatics  Polomsky, P., see R.-D. Urban  Poizonetti, G., see M.V. Andreocci  Prasad, S.D., see AS. Datar    Rachinsky, A.G., see M.F. Budyka  Radhakrishnan, T.P., see I. Agranat  Radhakrishnan, T.P., Ground-state spin of conjugated non-Kekule molecules  Reddy, N.R.S., G.J. Small, M. Seibert and R. Picorel, Energy transfer dynamics of the  B800 B 850 antenna complex of Rhodobacter sphaeroides: a hole burning study  Reeve, S.W., M.A. Dvorak, D.W. Firth and K.R. Leopold, Coriolis coupling in Ar HC1  Reiser, G., 0. Dopfer, R. Lindner, G. Henri, K. Miiller-Dethlefs, E.W. Schlag and  S.D. Colson, A new approach to vibrational spectroscopy of ion clusters: the  zero ki-  netic energy (ZEKE)  photoelectron spectrum of the phenol water complex  181 (1991) 380  181 (1991)413, 419    181 (1991) 387        181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 531  181 (1991) 386    181 (1991) 100  181 (1991) 112  181 (1991) 400  181 (1991) 175    181 (1991) 521    181 (1991) 413        181 (1991) 419  181 (1991) 255    181 (1991) 95  181 (1991) 544  181 (1991) 129  181 (1991) 151  181 (1991) 588  181 (1991) 21  181 (1991) 391  181 (1991) 83    181 (1991) 78  181 (1991) 485  181 (1991) 582  181 (1991) 445    181 (1991) 59  181 (1991) 117  181 (1991)455    181 (1991) 391  181 (1991) 259      181 (1991) 1  597  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 July 1991  Reisfeld, R., see V. Chernyak  Remade, F. and R.D. Levine, The maximum entropy of an optical spectrum and the re-  distribution in phase space  Rieder, K.H., see E. Kirsten  Rieker, A., see G.G. Lazarev  Rocca, D., see A. Dc Santis  Rossler, E., see K. Borner  Roy, D., see T.D. Hewitt  Russo, MV., see M.V. Andreocci    Sakaguchi, Y., see M. Igarashi  Salter, R.H., see J.A. Gardner  Sato, M., T. Sukegawa, T. Suzuki, S. Hagiwara and K. Kaneko, Surface fractal dimensional  change of microporous carbon fibers with partial graphitization  Scheraga, H.A., see B.J. Yoon  Schlag, E.W., see G. Reiser  Schreiber, M., see V. May  Schriver, A., see L. Schriver  Schriver, L., D. Carrere, A. Schriver and K. Jaeger, Matrix-isolation photolysis of SO2, 03  and H20: evidence for the H20: SO3 complex  Scuseria, G.E., see M. Haser  Sebastian, K.L., see K. Sumithra  Seibert, M., see N.R.S. Reddy  Sen, R., D. Majumdar, S.P. Bhattacharyya and S.N. Bhattacharyya, Hyperpolarizabilities  of twisted-intramolecular-charge-transfer (TICT) molecules: a case study on p-dime-  thylaminobenzonitrile (DMABN) and p-dimethylaminonitrosobenzene (DMANB)  Separovic, F., K. Hayamizu, R. Smith and B.A. Cornell, C-l 3 chemical shift tensor of L-  tryptophan and its application to polypeptide stmcture determination  Setser, D.W., see K. Du  Shchuka, M.I., see A.J. Kaziska  Shibuya, K., see Y. Kajii  Shimizu, H., see N. Akamatsu  Shimizu, Y., see T. Nogami  Shirley, W.A, and G.A. Petersson, The convergence of coupled-cluster methods for Be2  Shirota, Y., see T. Nogami  Shkrob, l.A., see S.N. Batchelor  Shushin, A.I., The effect of the spin exchange interaction on SNP and RYDMR spectra  of geminate radical pairs  Siguenza, C.L., Activation of the infrared multiphoton dissociation of CF2HC1  Sjoberg, P., see P. Politzer  Skancke, A., see I. Agranat  Small, G.J., see N.R.S. Reddy  Smalley, R.E., see G.H. Kroll  Smedley, i.E., see H.C. Miller  Smith, I.W.M. and X..F. Yang, Vibrational energy transfer in binary collisions between  isotopomers of HCN  Smith, J.A., see N.G. Gotts  181 (1991) 39  181 (1991) 307  181 (1991) 544  181 (1991) 512  181 (1991) 579  181 (1991) 563  181 (1991) 407  181 (1991) 582   181 (1991) 187  181 (1991) 5   181 (1991) 526   181 (1991) 73   181 (1991) 1  181 (1991)267  181 (1991) 505  181 (1991) 505  181 (1991) 497  181 (1991) 549  181 (1991) 391  181 (1991) 288  181 (1991) 157  181 (1991) 344  181 (1991) 134  181 (1991) 100  181 (1991) 175  181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 588  181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 327  181 (1991) 274  181 (1991) 351  181 (1991) 78  181 (1991) 117  181 (1991) 391  181 (1991) 112  181 (1991)250  181 (1991) 335  181 (1991) 491  598  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETFERS  l2July 1991  Smith, R., see F. Separovic  Sodupe, M. and C.W. Bauschlicher Jr., A1~ 1igand binding energies  Stade, A.J., see N.G. Gotts  Stothard, N.D., see H. User  Su, T.-M., see R.-C. Jiang  Sukegawa, T., see M. Sato  Sumithra, K. and K.L. Sebastian, Reaction dynamics on surfaces in the harmonic  approximation  Sun, B,, see K. Han  Suzuki, S., see Y. Kajii  Suzuki, T., see M. Sato    Takahashi, M., H. Ozeki and K. Kimura, A new high-resolution threshold photoelectron  analyzer: observation of rotational structure of NO~ cation  Tamai, N., see A. Osuka  Tanigaki, K., see T.W. Ebbesen  Taylor, A.G., see R. Howell  Topp, M.R., see A.J. Kaziska  Traytak, S.D., The rate constant of diffusion-limited reactions in a weak external electric  field  Treindi, ii., see M. Melichereik  Tronc, M., see A. Modelli    Uemiya, 1., see T. Nogami  Ullrich, J., see V. Aust  Umegaki, S., see T. Nogami  Upadhyaya, B.R., see J.A. Darsey  Urban, R.-D., P. Polomsky and H. Jones, A reassessment of the ground-state infrared spec-  trum of BiH and BiD    Vanquickenbome, L.G., see M.T. Nguyen  Van Zee, R.J., see Y.M. Hamrick  Varma, V.S., see R.K. Agrawal  Vieth, H.M., see K. Bonier  Von Schutz, J.U., see V. Aust    Walter, D., see H. Oser  Wang, M., see R. Chen  Waugh, K.C., Reply to the comment on  On the role of promoters in promoted iron cat-  alysts used in the industrial synthesis of ammonia   Weaver, J.H., see G.H. Kroll  Weltner Jr., W., see Y.M. Hamrick  Wiersma, D.A., see H.C. Meijers  Winstead, C.B., LX. He, D. Grantier, T. Hammond and J.L. Gole, Electric-field-en-  hanced laser-induced plasma spectroscopy of jet-cooled silicon trimer  Wolf, H.C., see V. Aust  181 (1991) 157  181 (1991) 321  181 (1991) 491  181 (1991) 521  181 (1991) 373  181 (1991) 526    181 (1991) 549  181 (1991) 474  181 (1991) 100  181 (1991) 526      181 (1991) 255  181 (1991) 413  181 (1991) 501  181 (1991) 21  181 (1991) 134    181 (1991) 558  181 (1991) 575  181 (1991) 361    181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 213  181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 386    181 (1991) 485    181 (1991) 83  181 (1991) 193  181 (1991) 441  181 (1991) 563  181 (1991) 213    181 (1991) 521  181 (1991) 168    181 (1991) 383  181 (1991) 112  181 (1991) 193  181 (1991) 312    181 (1991) 222  181 (1991) 213  599  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  l2July 1991  Xiao, L., see ME. Kellman    Yamada, H., see A. Osuka  Yamasaki, K., see H.C. Miller  Yamazaki, I., see A. Osuka  Yang, X.-F., see I.W.M. Smith  Yasuda, N., see T. Nogami  Yinnon, A.T., see R.B. Gerber  Yoon, B.J., S.D. Hong, MS. Jhon and H.A. Scheraga, Calculation of the entropy and the  chemical potential of fluids and solids from the radial free-space distribution function  Yoshimura, Y. and Y. Kimura, Solvent-density dependence of the unimolecular reaction  rate: dissociation reaction of 2-methyl-2-nitrosopropane dimer in carbon dioxide from  gas to liquid states    Zewail, A.H., see M. Dantus  Zhang, J.Z.H., Variational calculation of integral cross sections for the reaction  E+H2 ~HF+H  Zhang, R., see K. Han  Zheng, X., see K. Han  181 (1991) 141    181 (1991) 419  181 (1991) 250  181 (1991)413, 419  181 (1991) 335  181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 553    181 (1991) 73      181 (1991) 517    181 (1991) 281    181 (1991) 63  181 (1991) 474  181 (1991) 474  600   I.W.M. and X..F. Yang, Vibrational energy transfer in binary collisions between  isotopomers of HCN  Smith, J.A., see N.G. Gotts  181 (1991) 39  181 (1991) 307  181 (1991) 544  181 (1991) 512  181 (1991) 579  181 (1991) 563  181 (1991) 407  181 (1991) 582   181 (1991) 187  181 (1991) 5   181 (1991) 526   181 (1991) 73   181 (1991) 1  181 (1991)267  181 (1991) 505  181 (1991) 505  181 (1991) 497  181 (1991) 549  181 (1991) 391  181 (1991) 288  181 (1991) 157  181 (1991) 344  181 (1991) 134  181 (1991) 100  181 (1991) 175  181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 588  181 (1991) 385  181 (1991) 327  181 (1991) 274  181 (1991) 351  181 (1991) 78  181 (1991) 117  181 (1991) 391  181 (1991) 112  181 (1991)250  181 (1991) 335  181 (1991) 491  598  Volume 181, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETFERS  l2July 1991  Smith, R., see F. Separovic  Sodupe, M. and C.W. Bauschlicher Jr., A1~ 1igand binding energies  Stade, A.J., see N.G. Gotts  Stothard, N.D., see H. User  Su, T.-M., see R.-C. Jiang  Sukegawa, T., see M. Sato  Sumithra, K. and K.L. Sebastian, Reaction dynamics on surfaces in the harmonic  approximation  Sun, B,, see K. Han  Suzuki, S., see Y. Kajii  Suzuki, T., see M. Sato    Takahashi, M., H. Ozeki and K. Kimura, A new high-resolution threshold photoelectron  analyzer: observation of rotational structure of NO~ cation  Tamai, N., see A. Osuka  Tanigaki, K., see T.W. Ebbesen  Taylor, A.G., see R. Howell  Topp, M.R., see A.J. Kaziska  Traytak, S.D., The rate constant of diffusion-limited reactions in a weak external electric  field  Treindi, ii., see M. Melichereik  Tronc, M., see A. Modelli    Uemiya, 1., see T. Nogami  Ullrich, J., see V. Aust  Umegaki, S., see T. Nogami  Upadhyaya, B.R., see J.A. Darsey  Urban, R.-D., P. Polomsky and H. Jones, A reassessment of the ground-state infrared spec-  trum of BiH and BiD    Vanquickenbome, L.G., see M.T. Nguyen  Van Zee, R.J., see Y.M. Hamrick  Varma, V.S., see R.K. Agrawal  Vieth, H.M., see K. Bonier  Von Schutz, J.U., see V. Aust    Walter, D., see H. Oser  Wang, M., see R. Chen  Waugh, K.C., Reply to the comment on  On the role of promoters in promoted iron cat-  alysts used in the industrial synthesis of ammonia   Weaver, J.H., see G.H. Kroll  Weltner Jr., W., see Y.M. Hamrick  Wiersma, D.A., see H.C. Meijers  Winstead, C.B., LX. He, D. Grantier, T. Hammond and J.L. Gole, Electric-field-en-  hanced laser-induced plasma spectroscopy of jet-cooled silicon trimer  Wolf, H.C., see V. Aust  181 (1991) 157  181 (1991) 321  181 (1991) 491  181 (1991) 521  181 (1991) 373  181 (1991) 526    181 (1991) 549  181 (1991) </xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="mis" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>9180320W</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(91)80320-W</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(91)80320-W</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="other" year="1991"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Author Index to Volume 181</ce:title>
         </head>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>