<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926149180262V</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(91)80262-V</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-000926149180262V</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(91)80262-V</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(91)80262-V</pii><dc:title>Author index to volume 185 </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>185</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>5-6</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>576</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>584</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>576-584</prism:pageRange><prism:number>5-6</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1991-10-25</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>25 October 1991</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1991  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:description/><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926149180262V" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/000926149180262V" rel="scidir"/></coredata><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20011113">2001-11-13</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20011113">2001-11-13</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2015-10-02T11:45:04</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926149180262V</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(91)80262-V</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926149180262V</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(91)80262-V</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.3</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-ONLY</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X10962</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20151003">2015-10-03T17:59:33.579975-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19911025</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1991</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1005609600">2001-11-13T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav articletitle</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>185</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>185</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>5</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:iss-last>6</xocs:iss-last>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>5</xocs:issue>
         <xocs:issue>6</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 185, Issues 5–6</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>29</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>576</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>584</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>576</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>584</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19911025</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>25 October 1991</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1991-10-25</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1991</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>mis</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1991  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>AUTHORINDEXVOLUME185</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:refkeys/>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(91)80262-V</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926149180262V</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926149180262V</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(91)80262-V</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2015-10-03T17:59:33.579975-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1991-10-25</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926149180262V-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926149180262V/MAIN/application/pdf/6ae8d65f4db41cabef13807b7eeb5a46/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926149180262V/MAIN/application/pdf/6ae8d65f4db41cabef13807b7eeb5a46/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>583170</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>9</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926149180262V-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926149180262V/PREVIEW/image/png/ccb47450eccd4cdbfdbb9dcb9f33d5ff/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926149180262V/PREVIEW/image/png/ccb47450eccd4cdbfdbb9dcb9f33d5ff/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>54322</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  25 October 1991  Abbouti Temsamani, M., see M. Herman  Abbouti Temsamani, M., see M. Herman  Aberg, U. and V. Sundstrom, Photochemical isomerization in the absence of a potential  barrier: origin of wavelength-dependent ground-state recovery kinetics  Achiba, Y., see A. Hiraya  Adamowicz, L., Photoexcitations of the Si~ anion. Theoretical study  Agullo-Lopez, F., see E. Camarillo  Akiyama, K., S. Tero-Kubota and Y. Ikegami, Time-resolved EPR observation of the short-  lived excited triplet states of diamagnetic metallophthalocyanines in a rigid glassy matrix  Alfimov, M.V., S.P. Gromov and I.K. Lednev, Molecular design, photoisomerization and  complexation of crown ether styryl dyes  Amiot, C. and J. Verges, Laser-induced fluorescence of BaCI: the A  2~ state  Amos, R.D., J.S. Andrews, N.C. Handy and P.J. Knowles, Open shell Moller Plesset per-  turbation theory  Andersson, D., see U. van Slooten  Andrews, J.S., see R.D. Amos  Asahi, T., see A. Osuka  Asahi, T., see S. Nishikawa  Atrei, A., see J. Singh    Baba, M., T. Kamei, M. Kiritani, S. Yamauchi and N. Hirota, A phosphorescence study  of jet-cooled xanthone  Back, R.A., see G.A. McRae  Baker, J., see M. Barnes  Balasubramanian, K., see D. Dai  Baldwin, JE., see Y. Yamaguchi  Barbarossa, V., F. Galluzzi, R. Tomaciello and A. Zanobi, Raman spectra of microcrys-  talline graphite and a-C: H films excited at 1064 nm  Barnes, M., J. Baker, J.M. Dyke and R. Richter, A study of the F2~ Rydberg state of NS  by resonance-enhanced multiphoton-ionization spectroscopy  Bartlett, R.J., see KF. Ferris  Becerra, R., H.M. Frey, B.P. Mason and R. Walsh, Absolute rate constant and temperature  dependence for the reaction of silylene with nitrous oxide  Bendazzoli, G.L. and S. Evangelisti, Full-CI calculations of alternant cyclic polyenes (CH )N  N=2,4,6,...18, in the PPP approximation  Beutel, V., G.L. Bhale, M. Kuhn and W. Demtroder, The ionization potential of Ag2  Bhale, G.I.., see V. Beutel  Billing, G.D., see M. Rakovshik  Borowicz, P., see A. Grabowska  Braslavsky, SE., see A. Grabowska  185 (1991) 215  185 (1991) 220  185 (1991) 461  185 (1991) 303  185 (1991) 244  185 (1991) 505  185 (1991) 65  185 (1991) 455  185 (1991) 310  185 (1991) 256  185 (1991) 440  185 (1991) 256  185 (1991) 88  185 (1991) 237  185 (1991) 426  185 (1991) 354  185 (1991) 95  185 (1991) 433  185 (1991) 165  185 (1991) 143  185 (1991) 53  185 (1991) 433  185 (1991) 251  185 (1991) 415  185 (1991) 125  185 (1991) 313  185 (1991) 313  185 (1991) 1  185 (1991) 206  185 (1991) 206  576  Author Index to Volume 185  Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  25 October 1991  Briand, J. and R.R. Ernst, Computer-optimized homonuclear TOCSY experiments with  suppression of cross relaxation  Brickell, A., see C.G. Hickman  Brunner, H., see M. Ditto  Buckingham, A.D. and I.D. Rands, The three-body contribution to the polarizability of a  trimer of inert gas atoms using a dipole induced-dipole model  Buenker, R.J., see I.D. Petsalakis  Bumann, D., see O. Burghaus  Burghaus, O., M. Plato, D. Bumann, B. Neumann, W. Lubitz and K. Mobius, 3 mm EPR  investigation of the primary donor cation radical P~5 in single crystals of Rhodobacter  sphaeroides R-26 reaction centers  Burns, WA,, see M.A. Dvorak    Camarillo, E., J. Garcia-Sole, F. Cusso, F. Agullo-Lopez, J.A. Sanz-Garcia, T.P.J. Han,  F.H. Jaque and B. Henderson, Polarization spectroscopy of Cr3~ ions in LiNbO3 single  crystals: effect of Mg2~ ions  Carroll, T.X., see T.D. Thomas  Carter, FA., see C.J. Wu  Castanheira, EMS. and J.M.G. Martinho, Solvatochromic shifts of pyrene excimer  fluorescence  Castleman Jr., A.W., see X. Zhang  Chandran, L,, see L. Jansen  Cheng, X., K. Ichimura, D. Fichou and T. Kobayashi, Nanosecond time-resolved absorp-  tion spectra of thin films of a-conjugated lhiophene oligomers  Chupka, W.A., see Y. Wang  Cioslowski, J., see iV. Ortiz  Ciullo, G., M. Rosi, A. Sgamellotti and C. Floriani, On the relative stability of side-on and  end-on coordination of dinitrogen to nickel (0):  ab initio  calculations on the model  compounds [NiN2] and [Ni(PH3)2N2]  Clark, R.J.H. and T.J. Dines, Analysis of the excitation profiles of Raman bands of linear-  chain mixed-valence complexes. The geometry of [Pt(en)2][Pt(en)2Br2]Br4 in the in-  tervalence state  Craven, I.E., M.R. Hesling and G.L.D. Ritchie, Frequency dependence of the Rayleigh de-  polarization ratio and polarizability anisotropy of cyclohexane  Curtiss, L.A. and J.A. Pople, A re-examination of the Be OH2 complex  Cusso, F., see E. Camarillo    Daadoch, N.M., see V. Spirko  Dagdigian, P.J., see D. Patel-Misra  Dai, D. and K. Balasubramanian, Potential energy surfaces for the insertion of Os~ into    Das, G.P. and D.S. Dudis, An approximate ab initio study of the polarizability and hy-  perpolarizabilities of organic molecules  Davidsson, J., see J.H. Gutow  Demtroder, W., see V. Beutel  Dias, JR., Series of fluorenoid/fluoranthenoid hydrocarbons having a constant number  of isomers  185 (1991) 276  185 (1991) 101  185 (1991) 61    185 (1991) 544  185 (1991) 359  185 (1991) 381      185 (1991) 381  185 (1991) 399        185 (1991) 505  185 (1991) 31  185 (1991) 172    185 (1991) 319  185 (1991) 298  185 (1991) 403    185 (1991) 286  185 (1991) 478  185 (1991) 270      185 (1991) 522      185 (1991) 490    185 (1991) 371  185 (1991) 159  185 (1991) 505  185 (1991) 265    185 (1991) 387    185 (1991) 165    185 (1991) 151  185 (1991) 120  185 (1991) 313    185 (1991) 10  577  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETEERS  25 October 1991  Volume 185, number 5,6  185 (1991) 490    185 (1991) 212   185 (1991) 61   185 (1991) 75    185 (1991) 184  185 (1991) 184  185 (1991) 151    185 (1991) 399  185 (1991) 433    185 (1991) 189  185 (1991) 409  185 (1991) 47      185 (1991) 193  185 (1991) 276  185 (1991) 125    185 (1991) 393    185 (1991) 251  185 (1991) 286    185 (1991) 199  185 (1991) 522    185 (1991) 421  185 (1991)251  185 (1991) 415  185 (1991) 101  185 (1991) 550  185 (1991) 501  185 (1991) 105    185 (1991) 53  185 (1991) 505      185 (1991) 82  185 (1991) 440      185 (1991) 206  Dines, T.J., see R.J.H. Clark  Di Stefano, G., M. Lenzi, G. Piciacchia and A. Ricci, Transition moments active in the  PH(b ~~ e =0-.*X3~  v =O) emission  Ditto, M., H. Brunner and ME. Lippitsch, Picosecond spectroscopy of dihydro biliverdin  Dravid, V.P., S. Liu and MM. Kappes, Transmission electron microscopy of chromato-  graphically purified solid state C60 and C70  Dreger, Z.A., J.M. Lang and HG. Drickamer, Thermoluminescence, photoluminescence  and optical absorption of auramine O under high pressure  Drickamer, HG., see Z.A. Dreger  Dudis, D.S., see G.P. Das  Dvorak, M.A., S.W. Reeve, WA. Burns, A. Grushow and K.R. Leopold, Observation of  three intermolecular vibrational states of Ar HF  Dyke, J.M., see M. Barnes    Ebbesen, T.W., see K. Tanigaki  Edwards, PP., see N.C. Pyper  Eisenthal, K.B., see F.H. Long  El-Shall, M.S., SR. Olafsdottir, M. Meot-Ner (Mautner) and L.W. Sieck, Energy effects  on cluster ion distributions: beam expansion and thermochemical studies on mixed  clusters of methanol and acetonitrile  Ernst, R.R., see J. Briand  Evangelisti, S., see G.L. Bendazzoli    Faurskov Nielsen, O., see F. Sobron  Ferris, K.F., J.A. Franz, C.P. Sosa and R.J. Bartlett, Theoretical investigation of the rel-  ative stabilities of singlet and triplet disulfides  Fichou, D., see X. Cheng  Fielding, H.H. and T.P. Softley, Observation of the Stark effect in autoionising Rydberg  states of molecular hydrogen  Floriani, C., see G. Ciullo  Fontana, M.P., B. Rosi and N. Micali, Temperature and concentration dependence of on-  entational correlations of nitrate ions in Cu(N03)2 aqueous solutions  Franz, J.A., see KF. Ferris  Frey, H.M., see R. Becerra  Frey, J.G., see C.G. Hickman  Fueno, T., see M. Nakano  Fujishima, A., see Z-F. Liu  Furlani, A., see G. Polzonetti    Galluzzi, F.. see V. Barbarossa  Garcia-Sol~, J., see E. Camarillo  Gilabert, E., R. Lapouyade and C. Rulliere, Time-resolved dual fluorescence of push pull  stilbenes at high solute concentration and excitation intensity: evidence for an emitting  bicimer  Gislason, E.A., see U. van Slooten  Grabowska, A., P. Borowicz, DO. Martire and S.E. Braslavsky, Triplet states of molecules  undergoing internal double-proton transfer in the S1 state: 2,2-bipyridyl-diol and its  5,5  -dimethylated derivative  578  Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  25 October 1991  Graener, H. and G. Seifert, Infrared transient hole-burning in liquids  Gritsenko, 0V., see IV. Kurnikov  Gromoy, S.P., see M.V. Alfimov  Grushow, A., see M.A. Dvorak  Gutman, I. and S. Markovie, Almost-isospectral benzenoid systems  Gutow, J.H., J. Davidsson and R.N. Zare, Photoacoustic measurement of absolute over-  tone cross sections    Halicioglu, T., Model functions for carbon in calculating properties of small clusters  Han, T.P,J., see E. Camarillo  Hands, I.D., see A.D. Buckingham  Handy, N.C., see R.D. Amos  Hashimoto, K., see Z.-F. Liu  Helgaker, T., see V. ~pirko  Henderson, B., see E. Camarillo  Herman, M., M. Abbouti Temsamani, J. Vander Auwera and R. Ottinger, Near-infrared  absorption spectroscopy: the n =4 polyad of C2HD  Herman, M., M. Abbouti Temsamani, D. Lemaitre and J. Vander Auwera, The Fourier-  transform vibrational spectrum of acetylene in the visible range  Hesling, MR., see I.E. Craven  Hickman, C.G., A. Brickell and J.G. Frey, The 248 nm photodissociation of DOCI: laser  excitation fluorescence spectra of OD  Hiraya, A., Y. Achiba, K. Kimura and E.C. Lim, Multiphoton ionization photoelectron  spectroscopy of molecular excited states in supersonic jet: low-lying electronic states of  isoquinoline  Hirota, N., see M. Baba  Hochstrasser, R.M., see R.J. Sension  Howard, S.L., Possible resonance scattering window for CO symmetric charge transfer    Ichimura, K., see X. Cheng  Ikegami, Y., see K. Akiyama  Inaba, R., H. Okamoto, K. Yoshihara and M. Tasumi, Femtosecond time-resolved coher-  ent anti-Stokes Raman scattering from acetonitrile: solvent effects on the vibrational  dephasing of the C~N stretching band  Ito, H., see K. Kanda  lucci, G.. see G. Polzonetti  Ivanco, M., see GA. McRae    Jansen, L. and L. Chandran, Comment on  The characteristic electronic structure needed  for high-temperature superconductivity   Jaque, F.H., see E. Camarillo  Jensen, H.J.Aa., see V. ~pirko  Joachim, C., see P. Sautet  Joachim, C., Tuning of through-bond electronic coupling by donor and acceptor substi-  tutions in the [(NH3) 5Ru- 1  4-dicyanobenzene-Ru (NH3)5]5~ complex  Jonker, S.A. and J.M. Warman, Highly dipolar excited states of a symmetrical bound di-  mer of dimethylaminobenzonitrile observed by TRMC  185 (1991) 68  185 (1991) 365  185 (1991) 455  185 (1991) 399  185 (1991) 473    185 (1991) 120    185 (1991) 136  185 (1991) 505  185 (1991) 544  185 (1991) 256  185 (1991) 501  185 (1991) 265  185 (1991) 505    185 (1991) 215    185 (1991) 220  185 (1991) 371    185 (1991) 101      185 (1991) 303  185 (1991) 354  185 (1991) 179  185 (1991) 452    185 (1991) 286  185 (1991) 65      185 (1991) 56  185 (1991) 225  185 (1991) 105  185 (1991) 95      185 (1991) 403  185 (1991) 505  185 (1991) 265  185 (1991) 23    185 (1991) 569    185 (1991) 36  579  25 October 1991  Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  185 (1991) 111  185 (1991) 265  Jorgensen, C.K, see M. Lenglet  Jorgensen, P., see V. ~pirko  Kakitani, T., see S. Nishikawa  Kaldor, U., Symmetry breaking in radicals: NO2, NS2 and NO3  Kamei, T., see M. Baba  Kanda, K., H. Ito, K. Suzuki, T. Kondow and K. Kuchitsu, Formation of CN(A2111) frag-  ment from BrCN in an argon flowing afterglow  Kappes, M.M., see V.P. Dravid  Kikuchi, K., M. Yoshida, T. Maekawa and H. Watanabe, Metropolis Monte Carlo method  as a numerical technique to solve the Fokker Planck equation  Kimura, K., see A. Hiraya  King, D.A., see J. Singh  Kiritani, M., see M. Baba  KJeyn, A.W., see U. van Slooten  Knowles, P.J., see R.D. Amos  Knowles, P.J., K. Stark and H-J. Werner, A full-CI study of the energetics of the reaction  F+H2-*HF+H  Kobayashi, T., see X. Cheng  Kondow, T., see K. Kanda  Kondow, T., see T. Tsukuda  Kuchitsu, K., see K. Kanda  Kuhn, M., see Y. Beutel  Kurnikov, I.V. and 0.V. Gritsenko, On the influence of wavefunction asymptotics in cal-  culations of bridge-mediated electron-transfer interactions  Kuroshima, S., see K. Tanigaki  Kuskov, V,L., see G.G. I..azarev    Lago, S., see C. Vega  Laidig, K.E., The atomic basis of the molecular quadrupole moments of benzene and  hexafluorobenzene  Lang, J.M., see Z.A. Dreger  Lapouyade, R., see E. Gilabert  Lazarev, G.G., V.L. Kuskov, Ya.S. Lebedev, AI. Prokof ev and A. Rieker, Radical pairs  during photolysis of I H-2,4,6,8-tetrakis ( (-butyl )phenoxazin- 1-one in single crystals of  3, 5-di-i-butylpyrocatechol  Lebedev, Ya.S., see G.G. Lazarev  Lednev, 1.K., see M.Y. Alfimov  Lee, Y.S., see U. Ryu  Lemaitre, D., see M. Herman  Lenglet, M. and C.K. Jorgensen, Optical spectra of Ni (II) in Ni2GeO4 and germanate spinels  Lenzi, M., see G. Di Stefano  Leopold, KR., see M.A. Dvorak  Levchuk, Y.N., 1.1. Sheykhet and B.Ya. Simkin, Calculation of the hydration energy of  ethanol by the Monte Carlo method  Li, L., see Y. Wang  Lim, E.C., see A. Hiraya  185 (1991) 237  185 (1991) 131  185 (1991) 354  185 (1991) 225  185 (1991) 75  185 (1991) 335  185 (1991) 303  185 (1991) 426  185 (1991) 354  185 (1991) 440  185 (1991) 256  185 (1991) 555  185 (1991) 286  185 (1991) 225  185 (1991) 511  185 (1991) 225  185 (1991) 313  185 (1991) 365  185 (1991) 189  185 (1991) 375  185 (1991) 516  185 (1991) 483  185 (1991) 184  185 (1991) 82  185 (1991) 375  185 (1991) 375  185 (1991) 455  185 (1991) 562  185 (1991) 220  185 (1991) 111  185 (1991) 212  185 (1991) 399  185 (1991) 339  185 (1991) 478  185 (1991) 303  580  Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  25 October 1991  Lindh, R., see U. Ryu  Lippitsch, M.E., see M. Ditto  Liu, S., see V.P. Dravid  Liu, Z.-F., K. Hashimoto and A. Fujishima, Thermal cis trans isomerization kinetics of  azo compound in the assembled monolayer film: an electrochemical approach  Long, F.H,, H. Lu, X. Shi and K.B. Eisenthal, Intensity dependent geminate recombina-  tion in water  Lu, H., see F.H. Long  Lubitz, W., see O. Burghaus    Maekawa, T., see K. Kikuchi  Markovie, S., see I. Gutman  Martinho, J.M.G., see E.M.S. Castanheira  Mai-tire, D.O., see A. Grabowska  Maruyama, K., see A. Osuka  Mason, B.?., see R. Becerra  Mataga, N., see A. Osuka  Mataga, N., see S. Nishikawa  McRae, GA., M. Ivanco and R.A. Back, Laser initiated thermal reactions and isotopically  selective decomposition of 1,1, 1-trichloroethane  Meot-Ner (Mautner), M., see M.S. El-Shall  Micali, N., see M.P. Fontana  Mikhaeli, AM., see M.S. Mikhelashvili  Mikhelashvili, MS. and A.M. Mikhaeli, Energy and charge transfer in solutions. The role  of donor excitation natural decay  Mitrushenkov, A.O., see A.V. Titov  Mobius, K., see 0. Burghaus  Mochizuki, Y., T. Takada and A. Murakami, A theoretical study of the CuOH molecule  Morelli, G., G. Ricciardi and A. Roviello, Discotic mesomorphism of the  2,3,7,8,12,13,17,1 8-octakis ( octyl-thio )tetraazaporphyrin copper (II) complex  Murakami, A., see Y. Mochizuki    Nagata, T., see A. Osuka  Nakano, M., K. Yamaguchi and T. Fueno, Coupled-Hartree Fock calculations of the third-  order hyperpolarizabilities of substituted polydiacetylenes  Neumann, B., see O. Burghaus  Nicolaides, C.A., see ID. Petsalakis  Nicolaides, C.A., see E.D. Simandiras  Nishikawa, S., T. Asahi, T. Okada, N. Mataga and T. Kakitani, Determination of the bi-  molecular rate constant of photoinduced charge separation in the energy gap region where  the reaction is diffusion controlled   analysis of the transient effect in the course of flu-  orescence quenching reaction  Nishimura, Y., see A. Osuka  Nyberg, C. and L. Westerlund, Adsorption of CO on the Pd( lOO)p( 1 xl )H surface at low  temperatures: altered CO coordination    Okada, T., see S. Nishikawa  185 (1991) 562  185 (1991) 61  185 (1991) 75    185 (1991) 501    185 (1991) 47  185 (1991) 47  185 (1991) 381    185 (1991) 335  185 (1991) 473  185 (1991) 319  185 (1991) 206  185 (1991) 88  185 (1991) 415  185 (1991) 88  185 (1991) 237    185 (1991) 95  185 (1991) 193  185 (1991) 421  185 (1991) 347    185 (1991) 347  185 (1991) 330  185 (1991) 381  185 (1991) 535    185 (1991) 468  185 (1991) 535    185 (1991) 88    185 (1991) 550  185 (1991) 381  185 (1991) 359  185 (1991) 529        185 (1991) 237  185 (1991) 88    185 (1991) 445    185 (1991) 237  581  Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  25 October 1991  Okamoto, H., see R. Inaba  Olafsdottir, S.R., see M.S. El-Shall  Ortiz, JY. and J. Cioslowski, Molecular similarity indices in electron propagator theory  Osuka, A., T. Nagata, K. Maruyama, N. Mataga, T. Asahi, I. Yamazaki and Y. Nishimura,  Intramolecular photoinduced electron transfer in fixed distance triads consisting of free-  base porphyrin, zinc porphyrin, and electron acceptor  Ottinger, R., see M. Herman    Palmer III, A.G., P.E. Wright and M. Rance, Measurement of relaxation time constants  for methyl groups by proton-detected heteronuclear NMR spectroscopy  Pan, H.-Y., The charge fluctuation model for the conductivity of a microemulsion  Patel-Misra, D. and P.J. Dagdigian, Dynamics of the O(3P) H-NH2 reaction: the HNO+H  product channel  Personette, W., see J. Szczepanski  Persson, B.N.J. and A.1. Volokitin, On the origin of anti-absorption resonances in adsor-  bate vibrational spectroscopy  Petsalakis, I.D., G. Theodorakopoulos, C.A. Nicolaides and R.J. Buenker, Nearly diabatic  states by maximization of the non-orthonormal overlap between model-diabatic and  M RD-Cl wavefunctions  Piciacchia, G., see G. Di Stefano  Plato, M., see O. Burghaus  Polzonetti, G., MV. Russo, A. Furlani and G. Iucci, Interaction of H20, 02 and CO2 with  the surface of polyphenylacetylene films: an XPS investigation  Pople, J.A., see L.A. Curtiss  Pradeep, T. and C.N.R. Rao, An ultraviolet photoelectron spectroscopic study of the H2S  dimer, a van der Waals molecule  Prokof ev, A.I., see G.G. Lazarev  Provenzano, P.L. and W.B. White, Luminescence of Mn-activated SrLa2S4  Puebla, F., see F. Sobron  Pyper, N.C. and PP. Edwards, Reply to the Comment on  The characteristic electronic  structure needed for high-temperature superconductivity     Rakovshik, M. and G.D. Billing, On the coupling of phonons and electron hole pair ex-  citation in molecule surface scattering  Rance, M., see A.G. Palmer III  Rao, C.N.R., see T. Pradeep  Reeve, S.W., see MA. Dvorak  Renge, I., Solvent dependence of the visible absorption maxima of meso-  tetraphenylporphine  Ricci, A., see G. Di Stefano  Ricciardi, G., see G. Morelli  Richter, R., see M. Barnes  Rieker, A., see G.G. Lazarev  Ritchie, G.L.D., see I.E. Craven  Rosi, B., see M.P. Fontana  Rosi, M., see G. Ciullo  Roviello, A., see G. Morelli  185 (1991) 56  185 (1991) 193  185 (1991) 270      185 (1991) 88  185 (1991) 215      185 (1991) 41  185 (1991) 344    185 (1991) 387  185 (1991) 324    185 (1991) 292      185 (1991) 359  185 (1991) 212  185 (1991) 381    185 (1991) 105  185 (1991) 159    185 (1991) 496  185 (1991) 375  185 (1991) 117  185 (1991) 393    185 (1991) 409   185 (1991) 1  185 (1991) 41  185 (1991) 496  185 (1991) 399    185 (1991) 231  185 (1991) 212  185 (1991) 468  185 (1991) 433  185 (1991) 375  185 (1991) 371  185 (1991) 421  185 (1991) 522  185 (1991) 468  582  Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  25 October 1991  Rull, F., see F. Sobron  Rulliere, C., see E. Gilabert  Russo, M.V., see G. Poizonetti  Ryu, U., Y.S. Lee and R. Lindh, An efficient method of implementing the horizontal re-  currence relation in the evaluation of electron repulsion integrals using Cartesian Gaus-  sian functions    Sanz-GarcIa, JA., see E. Camarillo  Sautet, P. and C. Joachim, Calculation of the benzene on rhodium STM images  Schaefer III, H.F., see Y. Yamaguchi  Schwartz, S.D., A density matrix formulation for potential scattering in an oscillating/con-  trolled potential a model for some biophysical systems  Seifert, G., see H. Graener  Sension, R.J., AZ. Szarka, G.R. Smith and R.M. Hochstrasser, Ultrafast photoinduced  electron transfer to C60  Sgamellotti, A., see G. Ciullo  Sheykhet, I.!., see V.N. Levchuk  Shi, X., see F.H. Long  Sieck, LW., see MS. El-Shall  Simandiras, E.D. and C.A. Nicolaides, Nonclassical hydrogen complexes of the alkaline  earths  Simkin, B.Ya., see V.N. Levchuk  Singh, J., W.K. Walter, A. Atrei and DA. King, The influence of soft mode adsorbate vi-  brations on NEXAFS analyses: NO on Pd{ Il 0}  Smith, G.R., see R.J. Sension  Sobron, F., F. Puebla, F. Rull and O. Faurskov Nielsen, Temperature dependence of the  depolarized low frequency Raman spectra of water  Softley, T.P., see H.H. Fielding  Sosa, C.P., see K.F. Ferris  ~pirko, V., N.M. Daadoch, H.J.Aa. Jensen, P. Jorgensen and T. Helgaker, An ab initio in-  vestigation of the potential energy function and rotation vibration energies of H2ONa~  Stark, K., see P.J. Knowles  Sundstrom, V., see U. Aberg  Suzuki, K.. see K. Kanda  Szarka, A.Z., see R.J. Sension  Szczepanski, J., W. Personette and M. Vala, Pulsed-glow discharge/matrix isolation method  for the production and trapping of organic ions: application to para-dimethoxybenzene    Takada, T., see Y. Mochizuki  Tanigaki, K., T.W. Ebbesen and S. Kuroshima, Picosecond and nanosecond studies of the  excited state properties of C70  Tasumi, M., see R. Inaba  Tero-Kubota, S., see K. Akiyama  Theodorakopoulos, G., see l.D. Petsalakis  Thomas, T.D. and T.X. Carroll, Inner-sheLl lifetimes from lifetime-vibrational interference  Titov, A.V., A.O. Mitrushenkov and II. Tupitsyn, Effective core potential for pseudo-or-  bitaIs with nodes   185 (1991) 393   185 (1991) 82   185 (1991) 105   185 (1991) 562   185 (1991) 505   185 (1991) 23   185 (1991) 143   185 (1991) 16   185 (1991) 68   185 (1991) 179   185 (1991) 522   185 (1991) 339   185 (1991) 47   185 (1991) 193   185 (1991) 529   185 (1991) 339    185 (1991)426   185 (1991) 179   185 (1991) 393   185 (1991) 199   185 (1991) 251   185 (1991) 265   185 (1991) 555   185 (1991) 461   185 (1991) 225   185 (1991) 179   185 (1991) 324    185 (1991) 535   185 (1991) 189   185 (1991) 56   185 (1991) 65   185 (1991) 359   185 (1991) 31   185 (1991) 330  583  Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  25 October 1991  Tomaciello, R., see V. Barbarossa  Tsukuda, T. and T. Kondow, Observation of acrylonitrile molecular anion in the gas phase  Tupitsyn, 1.1., see A.V. Titav    Vala, M., see J. Szczepanski  VanderAuwera, J., see M. Herman  Vander Auwera, J., see M. Herman  Van Slooten, U., D. Andersson, A.W. Kleyn and E.A. Gislason, Scaling law for dissocia-  tion of fast molecular hydrogen scattered from Ag( ILl)  Vega, C. and S. Lago, Improved perturbation theory of Kihara fluids  Verges, J., see C. Amiot  Volokitin, AI., see B.N.J. Persson    Wakayama, N.1., Effect of a decreasing magnetic field on the flow of nitrogen gas  Walsh, R., see R. Becerra  Walter, W.K., see J. Singh  Wang, Y., L. Li and W.A. Chupka, Rotationally resolved photofragmentation spectroscopy  of CH~ formed by resonance-enhanced multiphoton ionization  Warman, J.M., see S.A. Jonker  Watanabe, H., see K. Kikuchi  Werner, H.-J., see P.J. Knowles  Westerlund, L., see C. Nyberg  White, W.B., see P.L. Provenzano  Wright, P.E., see A.G. Palmer III  Wu, C.J. and E.A. Carter, Adsorption of hydrogen atoms on the Si(l0O)-2Xl surface: im-  plications for the H2 desorption mechanism    Yamaguchi, K., see M. Nakano  Yamaguchi, Y., HF. Schaefer III and JE. Baldwin, Reappraisal of the disrotatory tran-  sition state for the ring opening of cyclopropane  Yamauchi, S., see M. Baba  Yamazaki, I., see A. Osuka  Yang, X., see X. Zhang  Yoshida, M., see K. Kikuchi  Yoshihara, K., see R. Inaba    Zanobi, A., see V. Barbarossa  Zare, R.N., see J.H. Gutow  Zhang, X., X. Yang and A.W. Castleman Jr., Study of protonated methanol cluster ions  under thermal conditions   185 (1991) 53   185 (1991) 511   185 (1991) 330    185 (1991) 324   185 (1991) 215  185 (1991) 220    185 (1991) 440   185 (1991) 516  185 (1991) 310   185 (1991) 292      185 (1991) 449  185 (1991) 415  185 (1991) 426   185 (1991) 478   185 (1991) 36    185 (1991) 335  185 (1991) 555  185 (1991) 445  185 (1991) 117  185 (1991) 41    185 (1991) 172    185 (1991) 550    185 (1991) 143  185 (1991) 354  185 (1991) 88   185 (1991) 298  185 (1991) 335  185 (1991) 56    185 (1991) 53  185 (1991) 120    185 (1991) 298  584  Levchuk  Singh, J., W.K. Walter, A. Atrei and DA. King, The influence of soft mode adsorbate vi-  brations on NEXAFS analyses: NO on Pd{ Il 0}  Smith, G.R., see R.J. Sension  Sobron, F., F. Puebla, F. Rull and O. Faurskov Nielsen, Temperature dependence of the  depolarized low frequency Raman spectra of water  Softley, T.P., see H.H. Fielding  Sosa, C.P., see K.F. Ferris  ~pirko, V., N.M. Daadoch, H.J.Aa. Jensen, P. Jorgensen and T. Helgaker, An ab initio in-  vestigation of the potential energy function and rotation vibration energies of H2ONa~  Stark, K., see P.J. Knowles  Sundstrom, V., see U. Aberg  Suzuki, K.. see K. Kanda  Szarka, A.Z., see R.J. Sension  Szczepanski, J., W. Personette and M. Vala, Pulsed-glow discharge/matrix isolation method  for the production and trapping of organic ions: application to para-dimethoxybenzene    Takada, T., see Y. Mochizuki  Tanigaki, K., T.W. Ebbesen and S. Kuroshima, Picosecond and nanosecond studies of the  excited state properties of C70  Tasumi, M., see R. Inaba  Tero-Kubota, S., see K. Akiyama  Theodorakopoulos, G., see l.D. Petsalakis  Thomas, T.D. and T.X. Carroll, Inner-sheLl lifetimes from lifetime-vibrational interference  Titov, A.V., A.O. Mitrushenkov and II. Tupitsyn, Effective core potential for pseudo-or-  bitaIs with nodes   185 (1991) 393   185 (1991) 82   185 (1991) 105   185 (1991) 562   185 (1991) 505   185 (1991) 23   185 (1991) 143   185 (1991) 16   185 (1991) 68   185 (1991) 179   185 (1991) 522   185 (1991) 339   185 (1991) 47   185 (1991) 193   185 (1991) 529   185 (1991) 339    185 (1991)426   185 (1991) 179   185 (1991) 393   185 (1991) 199   185 (1991) 251   185 (1991) 265   185 (1991) 555   185 (1991) 461   185 (1991) 225   185 (1991) 179   185 (1991) 324    185 (1991) 535   185 (1991) 189   185 (1991) 56   185 (1991) 65   185 (1991) 359   185 (1991) 31   185 (1991) 330  583  Volume 185, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  25 October 1991  Tomaciello, R., see V. Barbarossa  Tsukuda, T. and T. Kondow, Observation of acrylonitrile molecular anion in the gas phase  Tupitsyn, 1.1., see A.V. Titav    Vala, M., see J. Szczepanski  VanderAuwera, J., see M. Herman  Vander Auwera, J., see M. Herman  Van Slooten, U., D. Andersson, A.W. Kleyn and E.A. Gislason, Scaling law for dissocia-  tion of fast molecular hydrogen scattered from Ag( ILl)  Vega, C. and S. Lago, Improved perturbation theory of Kihara fluids  Verges, J., see C. Amiot  Volokitin, AI., see B.N.J. Persson    Wakayama, N.1., Effect of a decreasing magnetic field on the flow of nitrogen gas  Walsh, R., see R. Becerra  Walter, W.K., see J. Singh  Wang, Y., L. Li and W.A. Chupka, Rotationally resolved photofragmentation spectroscopy  of CH~ formed by resonance-enhanced multiphoton ionization  Warman, J.M., see S.A. Jonker  Watanabe, H., see K. Kikuchi  Werner, H.-J., see P.J. Knowles  Westerlund, L., see C. Nyberg  White, W.B., see P.L. Provenzano  Wright, P.E., see A.G. Palmer III  Wu, C.J. and E.A. Carter, Adsorption of hydrogen atoms on the Si(l0O)-2Xl surface: im-  plications for the H2 desorption mechanism    Yamaguchi, K., see M. Nakano  Yamaguchi, Y., HF. Schaefer III and JE. Baldwin, Reappraisal of the disrotatory tran-  sition state for the ring opening of cyclopropane  Yamauchi, S., see M. Baba  Yamazaki, I., see A. Osuka  Yang, X., see X. Zhang  Yoshida, M., see K. Kikuchi  Yoshihara, K., see R. Inaba    Zanobi, A., see V. Barbarossa  Zare, R.N., see J.H. Gutow  Zhang, X., X. Yang and A.W. Castleman Jr., Study of protonated methanol cluster ions  under thermal conditions   185 (1991) 53   185 (1991) 511   185 (1991) 330    185 (1991) 324   185 (1991) 215  185 (1991) 220    185 (1991) 440   185 (1991) 516  185 (1991) 310   185 (1991) 292      185 (1991) 449  185 (1991) 415  185 (1991) 426   185 (1991) 478   185 (1991) 36    185 (1991) 335  185 (1991) 555  185 (1991) 445  185 (1991) 117  185 (1991) 41  </xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="mis" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>9180262V</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(91)80262-V</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(91)80262-V</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="other" year="1991"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Author index to volume 185</ce:title>
         </head>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>