<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/0009261488803865</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(88)80386-5</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-0009261488803865</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(88)80386-5</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(88)80386-5</pii><dc:title>Author index to volume 149 </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>149</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>5-6</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>577</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>586</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>577-586</prism:pageRange><prism:number>5-6</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1988-09-02</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>2 September 1988</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1988  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:description/><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/0009261488803865" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/0009261488803865" rel="scidir"/></coredata><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20011113">2001-11-13</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20011113">2001-11-13</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2016-06-10T08:35:02</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-0009261488803865</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(88)80386-5</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>0009261488803865</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(88)80386-5</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.2</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-ONLY</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X11451</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20160610">2016-06-10T04:29:30.076445-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19880902</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1988</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1005609600">2001-11-13T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav articletitle</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>149</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>149</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>5</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:iss-last>6</xocs:iss-last>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>5</xocs:issue>
         <xocs:issue>6</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 149, Issues 5–6</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>25</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>577</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>586</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>577</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>586</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19880902</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>2 September 1988</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1988-09-02</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1988</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>mis</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1988  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>AUTHORINDEXVOLUME149</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:refkeys/>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(88)80386-5</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>0009261488803865</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-0009261488803865</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(88)80386-5</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2016-06-10T04:29:30.076445-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1988-09-02</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-0009261488803865-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:0009261488803865/MAIN/application/pdf/5f321a02e28b0d3edeff55f66b5edd10/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:0009261488803865/MAIN/application/pdf/5f321a02e28b0d3edeff55f66b5edd10/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>684226</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>10</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-0009261488803865-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:0009261488803865/PREVIEW/image/png/52f035295ea94189f289d7d02dfaa712/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:0009261488803865/PREVIEW/image/png/52f035295ea94189f289d7d02dfaa712/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>61948</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  AUTHOR INDEX TO VOLUME 149  Abdel-Raouf, M.A., Possible positronium formation in the collisions of positrons with cal-  cium positive ions  Allen, J.M., M.N.R. Ashfold, C.L. Bennett and C.M. Western, Double-resonance multi-  photon ionisation studies of Franck Condon disfavoured vibronic levels of the ~ and  ~  Rydberg states of ammonia  Andaloro, G., M.A. Palazzo, M. Migliore and S.L. Fornili, Hydration of the hydroxide ion:  ab initio calculations and Monte Carlo simulation  Apkarian, V.A., see J. Khademi  Apostol, M., see S. Svirschevsky  Arai, T., T. Karatsu, M. Tsuchiya, H. Sakuragi and K. Tokumaru, Triplet energy surfaces  of one-way isomerizing olefins as studied by singlet oxygen luminescence technique  Arun Kumar, B.S., K.V. Ramanathan and C.L. Khetrapal, Side-band intensities in the  deuterium magnetic resonance spectra of oriented molecules spinning near the magic  angle  Ashfold, MN.R., see J.M. Allen  Asimov, M.M., V.M. Nikitchenko, AI. Novikov and A.N. Rubinov, New high-efficiency  biscoumarin laser dyes  Attard, P. and M.T. Batchelor, A mechanism for the hydration force demonstrated in a  model system  149 (1988) 217      149 (1988) 1    149 (1988) 201  149 (1988) 145  149 (1988) 521    149 (1988) 161      149 (1988) 306  149 (1988) 1    149 (1988) 140    149 (1988) 206  Bagchi, B., see CS. Poornimadevi  Bai, J., I-I. Okabe and J.B. Halpern, Fluorescence spectrum and lifetime of i-C3H70 radical  Ballard, R.E., J. Jones, A. Inchley and M. Cranmer, He (I) photoelectron studies of mixed  surfactant films on liquid surfaces  Barmashenko, B.D. and V.A. Kochelap, IR chemical lasers: active medium formation via  the combustion of finely disperse metal particles in an oxidizing atmosphere  Barr, J.R.M., see P.A. Hatherly  Barra, AL. and J.B. Robert, 31P magnetic shielding tensor components of a phosphirane.  Angular dependence of the 3 P magnetic shielding anisotropy  Batchelor, M.T., see P. Attard  Bauder, A., see L. Martinache  Beaman, R., see G. Lo  Becker, M., see U. Gaubatz  Belli, M., see G. Onori  Bennett, C.L., see J.M. Allen  Berg, D., see F.-W. Breitbarth  Bergmann, K., see U. Gaubatz  Bernhardt, J.R., see LR. Slagle  Berreby, L., C. Dreyfus and E. Dayan, Validity of the method of measurement of the mean-  squared torque in linear molecule atom systems at intermediate densities  Bianconi, A., see G. Onori  149 (1988) 411  149 (1988) 37    149 (1988) 29    149 (1988) 68  149 (1988) 477  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  (1988) 363  (1988) 206  (1988) 424  (1988) 384  (1988) 463  (1988) 289  (1988) 1  (1988) 334  (1988) 463  (1988) 180  149 (1988) 63  149 (1988) 289  577  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYStCS LETTERS  2 September 1988  Billing, G.D., see N.E. Henriksen  Birk, H., see U. Magg  Blasse, G., see H. Matthies  Bonazzola, L., J.-P. Michaut and J. Roncin, The structure of the CFCI3 radical anion  Botar, L. and I. Ruff, On the general and special form of Fick s second law with concen-  tration-dependent diffusion coefficients  Bouman, T.D. and A.E. Hansen, Iterative LORG calculations of nuclear magnetic shield-  ings.  3C shielding tensors in 2-norbornenone  Bourmada, N., P. Devolder and L.-R. Sochet, Rate constant for the termolecular reaction  of OH + toluene + helium in the fall-off range below 10 Ton  Bower, J.E., see M.F. Jarrold  Breitbarth, F.-W. and D. Berg, A continuous emission in weakly excited CC14 discharges.  CC13 as possible emitter  Broeckhove, J., L. Lathouwers, E. Kesteloot and P. Van Leuven, On the equivalence of time-  dependent variational principles  Brouard, M. and J. O Mahony, Photodissociation dynamics of HCOOH(A)  Brucat, P.J., see D. Lessen  Brucat, P.J., see D. Lessen  Bruley, J., see R. Brydson  Brumer, P., see M. Shapiro  Brydson, R., J. Bruley and J.M. Thomas, Further evidence for core-hole effects in the near-  edge structures of light element K-edges  Brzezinski, B., L. Celewiez, J. Spychala and K. Golankiewicz, Intramolecular  OH...N O - ...H ~N hydrogen bonds in N- (1 H-2-oxo-4-pyrimidinyl) amino acids  Butler, P.H., see B.T. Thole    Carrington, A., I.R. McNab and C.A. Montgomerie, Spectroscopic observation of rota-  tionally quasibound HD + ions  Celewicz, L., see B. Brzezinski  Child, M.S. and D.J. Nesbitt, RKR-based inversion of rotational progressions  Chou, J.Z., see J.F. Hershberger  CI~ek, J. and F. Vinette, Lower bounds for the ground state energy for the PPP and Hub-  bard models of the benzene molecule  Codling, K., see P.A. Hatherly  Coffer, J.L., J.R. Shapley and H.G. Drickamer, A pressure tuning spectroscopie study of  cis-diammine ct-pyridone platinum blue  Cohen, L.K. and H.O. Pritchard, Comparison of translational energy distributions cal-  culated classically and quantally for the same reaction  Cranmer, M., see R.E. Ballard  Crookell, A., M. Fleischmann, M. Hanniet and P.J. Hendra, Surface-enhanced Fourier  transform Raman spectroscopy in the near infrared  Cummins, P.G., see E.J. Staples    Dayan, E., see L. Berreby  Del Barrio, J.I., J.R. Rebato and F.M. 0.-Tablas, Solvatochromic shifts of triplet triplet  transitions of aeridine and phenazine  Della Longa, S., see G. Onori  149 (1988) 397  149 (1988) 321  149 (1988) 167   149 (1988) 316   149 (1988) 99   149 (1988) 510   149 (1988) 339   149 (1988) 433   149 (1988) 334   149 (1988) 547   149 (1988) 45   149 (1988) 10   149 (1988) 473   149 (1988) 343   149 (1988) 451   149 (1988) 343   149 (1988) 348   149 (1988) 295   149 (1988) 326  149 (1988) 348  149 (1988) 404  149 (1988) 51    149 (1988) 516  149 (1988) 477    149 (1988) 487    149 (1988) 543  149 (1988) 29    149 (1988) 123  149 (1988) 191    149 (1988) 63    149 (1988) 150  149 (1988) 289  578  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  DePristo, A.E., see K. Raghavan  Devolder, P., see N. Bourmada  Dirksen, G.J., see H. Matthies  Dorigo, A., see K. Yamaguchi  Dreyfus, C., see L. Berreby  Driekamer, H.G., see J.L. Coffer  Duportail, G. and P. Lianos, Fractal modeling of pyrene excimer quenching in phospho-  lipid vesicles    Engel, V., see S. Hennig  Erturk, U. and A. Otto, Surface-enhanced Raman scattering of C2H4 on silver induced by  surface defects    Fernandez, A., Assembling of random inhomogeneous polymers: a grand ensemble ap-  proach using the replica method  Filimonova, S.V., see V.M. Mastikhin  Fleisehmann, M., see A. Crookell  Flood, M.J., see R.H. Lipson  Flynn, G.W., see J.F. Hershberger  Flytzanis, C., see F. Vallee  Fornili, S.L., see G. andaloro  Fowler, P.W. and P. Tole, The polarisability of the sulphide ion in MgS  Frasinski, L.J., see P.A. Hatherly  Freedman, T.B., see K.M. Spencer  Freude, D., J. Klinowski and H. Hamdan, Solid-state NMR studies of the geometry of  Bronsted acid sites in zeolitie catalysts  149  149  149  149  149  149  (1988) 89  (1988) 339  (1988) 167  (1988) 537  (1988) 63  (1988) 487  149 (1988) 73    149 (1988) 455    149 (1988) 284  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  113  175  123  155  51  572  201  273  477  367  149 (1988) 355    149 (1988) 150  149 (1988) 572  0.-Tablas, F.M., see J.I. del Barrio  Gale, G.M., see F. Vallee  Gaubatz, U., P. Rudeeki, M. Becker, S. Schiemann, M. Kulz and K. Bergmann, Popula-  tion switching between vibrational levels in molecular beams  Golankiewicz, K., see B. Brzezinski  Goodman, D.W., see E.M. Stuve  Gopidas, K.R., see P.V. Kamat  Gryczynski, I., see J.R. Lakowicz  Gupta, D. and C.S. Hirtzel, Monte Carlo simulation of temperature-programmed desorp-  tion of molecules from solid surfaces  Gutman, D., see I.R. Slagle  149  149  149  149  149  (1988) 463  (1988) 348  (1988) 557  (1988) 491  (1988) 134  149 (1988) 527  149 (1988) 180  Halpem, J.B., see J. Bai  Hamdan, H., see D. Freude  Hanniet, M., see A. Crookeil  Hansen, A.E., see T.D. Bouman  Hansen, F.Y., see N.E. Henriksen  Hatherly, P.A., L.J. Frasinski, K. Codling and J.R.M. Barr, Multiphoton ionisation of n-  alkanes using an intense sub-picosecond laser  Hendra, P.J., see A. Crookell  Hennig, S., V. Engel, R. Schinke and V. Staemmler, Emission spectroscopy of photodis-  sociating water molecules: a time-independent ab initio study  149 (1988)  149 (1988)  149 (1988)  149 (1988)  149 (1988)  37  355  123  510  397  149 (1988) 477  149 (1988) 123    149 (1988) 455    579  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  Henriksen, N.E., G.D. Billing and F.Y. Hansen, Phase space representation of quantum  mechanics: approximate dynamics of the Morse oscillator  Hepbum, J.W., see M. Shapiro  Hershberger, J.F., J.Z. Chou, G.W. Flynn and R.E. Weston Jr., Rotational state depen-  dence of transient linewidths in the CO2 00 l vibrational level due to translational en-  ergy recoil from hot H and D atom collisions  Hirota, N., see K. Tominaga  Hirtzel, CS., see D. Gupta  Hopkins, J.B., see L.K. Orman  Houk, K.N., see K. Yamaguehi  Howard, N.W. and A.C. Legon, Cl and D nuclear quadrupole coupling in the rotational  spectrum of  5N2...DC1 and the dynamics of the DC1 subunit  Howorka, F., see T.D. Mark  Hoy, A.R., see R.H. Lipson  149 (1988) 397  149 (1988) 451  149  149  149  149  149  (1988) 51  (1988) 32  (1988) 527  (1988) 375  (1988) 537  149 (1988) 57  149 (1988) 230  149 (1988) 155    149 (1988) 185  Ichikawa, T., see M. Shiotani  Ilisca, E. and S. Sugano, Optical studies in ortho para conversion of a hydrogen molecule  on a magnetic surface  Imre, D.G., see J. Zhang  Inchley, A., see R.E. Ballard  Ingersoll, D., see E.M. Stuve  Isaka, H., see T. Ohzeki  Israelachvili, J.N., see P.M. McGuiggan  Itoh, M. and M. Sasaki, Transformation of van der Waals complex to the exciplex in jet-  cooled 1 -cyano-4-methylnaphthalene and triethylamine  (1988) 20  (1988) 233  (1988) 29  (1988) 557  (1988) 379  (1988) 469  149  149  149  149  149  149  149 (1988) 40    149 (1988) 300  149 (1988) 300  149 (1988) 424    149 (1988) 433  Jameson, AK., see C.J. Jameson  Jameson, C.J. and A.K. Jameson, Absolute shielding scale for 29Si  Jans-Burli, S., see L. Martinache  Jarrold, M.F. and J.E. Bower, Surface chemistry on metal clusters: observation of multiple  structures for C2H4 ehemisorbed on aluminum clusters  Jaszunski, M., A. Rizzo and D.L. Yeager, Ab initio linear response calculations of the di-  pole polarizability of the acetylene molecule  Jensen, F., see K. Yamaguchi  Jin, Z., see Q. Qin  Jones, H., see U. Magg  Jones, J., see R.E. Ballard    Kamat, P.V., K.R. Gopidas and D. Weir, Photoeleetrochemistry in particulate systems.  Photosensitized charge injection into opaque TiO2 semiconductor powder as probed by  time-resolved diffuse reflectance laser flash photolysis  Karatsu, T., see T. Arai  Katsumoto, M., see A. Morita  Kesteloot, E., see J. Broeckhove  Khademi, J., H. Kunttu and V.A. Apkarian, Spectral hole buming in the inhomogeneous  w3 absorption profile in CH3F isolated in mixed Ar: Kr matrices  (1988) 79  (1988) 537  (1988) 128  (1988) 321  (1988) 29          (1988) 491  (1988) 161  (1988) 95  (1988) 547  149  149  149  149  149          149  149  149  149  149 (1988) 145  580  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEiTERS  2 September 1988  Khetrapal, C.L., see B.S. Arun Kumar  King, R.B., Chemical bonding in two-dimensional islands of silver and gold on graphite  surfaces  Kjellander, R. and S. Sarman, On the statistical mechanics of inhomogeneous fluids in nar-  row slits. An application to a hard-sphere fluid between hard walls  Klinowski, J., see D. Freude  Koch, H., G.E. Seuseria, A.C. Schemer and H.F. Schaefer III, The infrared spectrum of  water. Basis set dependence at the single and double excitation coupled cluster (CCSD)  level of theory  Kochelap, V.A., see B.D. Barmashenko  Kormann, C., M. Lewerenz and M. Quack, Band strengths of fundamentals and overtones  of the CF and CH chromophores in CHD2F  Kresa, W., see L. Martinache  Kubach, C., see W.J. van der Zande  Kulander, K.C., Spectroscopy of SO  Kulz, M., see U. Gaubatz  Kunttu, H., see J. Khademi    Lakowicz, J.R., I. Gryczynski and W.M. Wiczk, Anisotropie rotational diffusion of indole  in cyclohexane studied by 2 GHz frequency-domain fluorometry  Lathouwers, L., see J. Broeckhove  Lecuyer, I., see D. Markovitsi  Legon, A.C., see N.W. Howard  Leng, F., see E.J. Staples  Lessen, D. and P.J. Brucat, The unique stability of CoArt: coordination complex or close-  packed structure?  Lessen, D. and P.J. Brucat, Estimation of the Nid  bond energy from the photodissociation  of Ni2Ar~  Lewerenz, M., see C. Kormann  Li, Y., see Q. Qin  Lianos, P., see G. Duportail  Lin, S.H., see K. Nishikawa  Lipson, R.H., A.R. Hoy and M.J. Flood, Direct vibrational numbering of the D0,t ion-pair  state of Br2  Liu, X., see Q. Qin  Lo, G., R. Beaman and D.W. Setser, Radiative lifetime, electronic quenching and spin   orbit state relaxation rate constants for SO (A 3fl012, y  = 0)  Los, J., see W.J. van der Zande  Lovejoy, C.M. and D.J. Nesbitt, Infrared-active combination bands in ArHC1, Chem. Phys.  Letters 146 (1988) 582. Erratum    Maas, W.E.J.R. and W.S. Veeman, Natural abundance  3C spin diffusion enhanced by    magie-angle spinning 149 (1988)170  Mack, J.X., see L.B. Schein 149 (1988) 109  Magg, U., H. Birk and H. Jones, The ground-state infrared spectrum of four isotopic forms    of barium monohydride (BaH) 149 (1988) 321  Maricq, M.M., see J.J. Tanner 149 (1988) 503  149 (1988) 306    149 (1988) 562    149 (1988) 102  149 (1988) 355      149 (1988) 118  149 (1988) 68  149  149  149  149  149  149  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  (1988)  429  424  14  392  463  145  149 (1988) 134  149 (1988) 547  149 (1988) 330  149 (1988) 57  149 (1988) 191    149 (1988) 10    149 (1988) 473  149 (1988) 429  149 (1988) 128  149 (1988) 73  149 (1988) 243    149 (1988) 155  149 (1988) 128    149 (1988) 384  149 (1988) 14    149 (1988) 122  581  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  Mark, T.D., A. Stamatovic, F. Howorka and P. Scheier, Photodissociation of neutral van  der Waals clusters with visible laser light  Markovitsi, D. and I. Lecuyer, Laser-induced triplet excitons in the columnar phases of an  octasubstituted zinc phthalocyanine  Marsagishvili, T.A., M.G. Zakaraya and J. Ulstrup, Reversibility conditions in radiative  single-photon molecular and solid-state electronic transitions  MartIn, F., A. Riera and M. Yaiiez, Continuum versus discretized wavefunctions. The im-  portance of being well normalized  Martinache, L., S. Jans-Burli, B. Vogelsanger, W. Kresa and A. Bauder, Microwave mi-  crowave double resonance experiments with pulsed molecular beams in crossed Fabry   Perot cavities  Mastikhin, V.M., I.L. Mudrakovsky and S.V. Filimonova, Probing the Lewis acidity of  heterogeneous catalysts by  N NMR of adsorbed N2O  Matthies, H., K. Reeker, F. Wallrafen, G.J. Dirksen and G. Blasse, Luminescence of cop-  per in barium zinc fluoride (Ba2ZnF5 Cu)  MeGuiggan, P.M. and J.N. Israelaehvili, Adhesion of two solid surfaces in water: effect of  rotational mismatch of surface lattices  MeNab, I.R., see A. Carrington  Merehen, M., see J. Planelles  Miehaut, J.-P., see L. Bonazzola  Migliore, M., see G. andaloro  Miller, W.H., see A.C. Peet  Montgomerie, C.A., see A. Carrington  Monta, A. and M. Katsumoto, Fluctuation increases in transient processes  Mudrakovsky, I.L., see V.M. Mastikhin    Nafie, L.A., see K.M. Spencer  Natanson, G.A., Centrifugal oscillator as a self-consistent model for treating bending an-  harmonieities in nearly linear triatomic complexes  Nesbitt, D.J., see C.M. Lovejoy  Nesbitt, D.J., see MS. Child  Nikitehenko, V.M., see M.M. Asimov  Nikitin, E.E. and A.I. Reznikov, Theoretical total cross section and branching ratio for  Kr + (2P,12, 2P,,2) ions produced in low-energy charge-exchange collisions of Kr2 + ( So)  with He( S0)  Nishikawa, K. and S.H. Lin, Quantum mechanical calculations on the decomposition of  H2O2  Novikov, A.I., see M.M. Asimov    Ohgusa, H., see T. Ohzeki 149 (1988)379  Ohta, N., see M. Shiotani 149 (1988) 185  Ohzeki, T., H. Ohgusa, H. Isaka, S. Suzuki and H. Takahashi, Time-resolved resonance    Raman studies of transient species in the photoenolization of 2-methylbenzophenone    and 2-benzylbenzophenone 149 (1988) 379  Okabe, H., see J. Bai 149 (1988) 37  O Mahony, J., see M. Brouard 149 (1988) 45  149 (1988) 230    149 (1988) 330    149 (1988) 417    149 (1988) 85      149 (1988) 424    149 (1988) 175    149 (1988) 167  (1988) 469  (1988) 326  (1988) 222  (1988) 316  (1988) 201  (1988) 257  (1988) 326  (1988) 95  (1988) 175  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149 (1988) 367  149  149  149  149  (1988) 551  (1988) 122  (1988) 404  (1988) 140  149 (1988) 212    149 (1988) 243  149 (1988) 140  582  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  Onori, G., A. Santueei, A. Scafati, M. Belli, S. Della Longa, A. Bianeoni and L. Palladino,  Cu K-edge XANES of Cu (II) ions in aqueous solution: a measure of the axial ligand  distances  Orman, L.K. and J.B. Hopkins, Re-evaluation of the Raman assignments in the ground  and excited metal to ligand charge transfer state of tris-2,2  -bipyridine Ru (II)  Otto, A., see U. Ertunk    Paffett, M.T., see E.M. Stuve  Palazzo, M.A., see G. andaloro  Palladino, L., see G. Onori  Panas, I,, J. Schule, P. Siegbahn and U. Wahlgren, On the cluster convergence of ehemi-  sorption energies  Peet, A.C. and W.H. Miller, A pointwise representation of the S-matrix Kohn variational  principle for quantum scattering  Penfold, J., see E.J. Staples  Persson, B.N.J., On the nature of the fmstrated translations for CO on metal surfaces  Peterson, J.R., see W.J. van den Zande  Petsalakis, I.D., see G. Theodorakopoulos  Planelles, J., M. Merehdn and F. Tomas, On the low-lying states of the copper methylene  (CuCH2) complex. A MO CI study  Poornimadevi, C.S. and B. Bagehi, Fractional power dependence of rate on activation en-  ergy for reactions with very low internal bathers  Pritchard, H.O., see L.K. Cohen    Qin, Q., Y. Li, Z. Jin, X. Liu and Q. Zheng, Effect of translational energy on laser-assisted  reaction of GaAs with chlorine  Quack, M., see C. Kormann  149 (1988) 289    149 (1988) 375  149 (1988) 284  149 (1988) 557  149 (1988) 201  149 (1988) 289    149 (1988) 265  149  149  149  149  149  (1988) 257  (1988) 191  (1988) 278  (1988) 14  (1988) 196  149 (1988) 222    149 (1988) 411  149 (1988) 543  149 (1988) 128  149 (1988) 429  Raghavan, K., M.S. Stave and A.E. DePristo, Dissociation dynamics of D, on Ni1, clus-  ters: structural dependence  Ramanathan, K.V., see B.S. Arun Kumar  Rebato, J.R., see J.!. del Barrio  Recker, K., see H. Matthies  Reilly, J.P., see E. Sekreta  Reznikov, A.I., see E.E. Nikitin  Riera, A., see F. Martin  Rizzo, A., see M. Jaszunski  Robert, J.B., see A.L. Barra  Rogers Jr., J.W., see E.M. Stuve  Ronein, J., see L. Bonazzola  Rosen, A., see E. Westin  Rubinov, A.N., see M.M. Asimov  Rudecki, P., see U. Gaubatz  Ruff, I., see L. Botar  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149  149   (1988) 89   (1988) 306   (1988) 150   (1988) 167   (1988) 482   (1988) 212   (1988) 85   (1988) 79   (1988) 363   (1988) 557   (1988) 316  (1988) 239   (1988) 140   (1988) 463   (1988) 99  Sakuragi, H., see T. Arai  Santueci, A., see G. Onori  Sarman, S., see R. Kjellander  149 (1988) 161  149 (1988) 289  149 (1988) 102  583  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  Sasaki, M., see M. Itoh  Seafati, A., see G. Onori  Schaefer III, HF., see H. Koch  Seheier, P., see T.D. Mark  Schein, L.B. and J.X. Mack, Adiabatic and non-adiabatic small polaron hopping in mo-  lecularly doped polymers  Schemer, A.C., see H. Koch  Schiemann, S., see U. Gaubatz  Schinke, R., see S. Hennig  Sehule, J., see I. Panas  Scuseria, G.E., see H. Koch  Sekreta, E. and J.P. Reilly, Direct observation of intersystem crossing in benzene by laser  photoelectron spectroseopy  Setser, D.W., see G. Lo  Shapiro, M., J.W. Hepbum and P. Brumer, Simplified laser control of unimolecular re-  actions: simultaneous (coi, ru3) excitation  Shapley, J.R., see J.L. Coffer  Shiotani, M., N. Ohta and T. Ichikawa, Structure and reaction of methylcyclohexane rad-  ical cation: ESR studies  Siegbahn, P., see I. Panas  Sims, I.R. and I.W.M. Smith, Rate constants for the reactions CN (y= 0),  CN(v= 1) +H2D2 *HCN, DCN+H, D between 295 and 768 K, and comparisons with  transition state theory calculations  Singh, J., Drastic reduction in band gap due to pairing of carriers and exeiton lattice in-  teraction in non-metallic solids  Slagle, I.R., J.R. Bemhardt and D. Gutman, Kinetics of the reactions of SiH, with 02 and  N2O  Slanina, Z., A sum rule for harmonic vibrational frequencies valid within a series of pairs  of isomeric isotopomers  Smith, I.W.M., see I.R. Sims  So, S.P., Structures and energetics of some low-lying electronic states of FCS  Sochet, L.-R., see N. Bourmada  Sofer, I. and A. Yogev, Bimolecular reaction of CHFC1, with olefins induced by infrared  multiphoton excitation  Spencer, K.M., T.B. Freedman and L.A. Nafie, Scattered circular polarization Raman op-  tical activity  Spychala, J., see B. Brzezinski  Stace, A.J., Comment on  Raman-indueed photodissociation of neutral (CO,)~ van der  Waals clusters with visible laser light   Staemmler, V., see S. Hennig  Stamatovic, A., see T.D. Mark  Staples, E.J., P.G. Cummins, F. Long and J. Penfold, Neutron scattering of mixed micelles  under shear  Stave, M.S., see K. Raghavan  Stuke, M., see Y. Zhang  Stuve, E.M., J.W. Rogers Jr., D. Ingersoll, D.W. Goodman, M.L. Thomas and M.T. Paffett,  Ultrahigh vacuum and electrochemical co-characterization studies of Cu on Ru (0001)  149  149  149  149    149  149  149  149  149  149  (1988) 40  (1988) 289  (1988) 118  (1988) 230    (1988) 109  (1988) 118  (1988) 463  (1988) 455  (1988) 265  (1988) 118  149 (1988) 482  149 (1988) 384    149 (1988) 451  149 (1988) 487    149 (1988) 185  149 (1988) 265      149 (1988) 565    149 (1988) 447    149 (1988) 180  (1988) 497  (1988) 565  (1988) 534  (1988) 339  149  149  149  149  149 (1988) 439    149 (1988) 367  149 (1988) 348    149 (1988) 228  149 (1988) 455  149 (1988) 230    149 (1988) 191  149 (1988) 89  149 (1988) 310    149 (1988) 557  584  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  Sugano, S., see E. Ilisca  Sundholm, D., Two-dimensional, fully numerical solution of the molecular Dirac equa-  tion. Dirac Slater calculations on LiH, Li2, BH and CH~  Suzuki, S., see T. Ohzeki  Svirschevsky, S. and M. Apostol, Solvent and pressure effects on transition rates of en-  zymatic reactions    Takahashi, H., see T. Ohzeki  Tanner, J.J. and M.M. Marieq, Far IR dissociation of a highly excited Morse oscillator  Theodorakopoulos, G. and I.D. Petsalakis, Ab initio calculations on the ground and ex-  cited electronic states of KrH  Thole, B.T., G. van der Laan and P.H. Butler, Spin-mixed ground state of Fe phthalocy-  anine and the temperature-dependent branching ratio in X-ray absorption spectroscopy  Thomas, J.M., see R. Brydson  Thomas, M.L., see E.M. Stuve  Tokumaru, K., see T. Arai  Tole, P., see P.W. Fowler  Tomas, F., see J. Planelles  Tominaga, K., S. Yamauchi and N. Hirota, The CIDEP spectrum of a radical pair of the  acetone ketyl radical in solution. Effect of deuteration  Tsuchiya, M., see T. Arai    Ulstrup, J., see T.A. Marsagishvili    Vallee, F., G.M. Gale and C. Flytzanis, Biphonon dynamics in ordered ammonium chloride  Van der Laan, G., see B.T. Thole  Van der Zande, W.J., J. Los, J.R. Peterson and C. Kubach, Decay of the C2Z~ quasibound  states of HeH: an experimental and theoretical study  Van Leuven, P., see J. Broeckhove  Veeman, W.S., see W.E.J.R. Maas  Vinette, F., see J. ~i~ek  Vogelsanger, B., see L. Martinache    Wahlgren, U., see I. Panas  Wallrafen, F., see H. Matthies  Weir, D., see P.V. Kamat  Westem, C.M., see J.M. Allen  Westin, E. and A. Rosen, Local density theory calculations of the ionization energies and  optical transitions in BaF and BaCI  Weston Jr., R.E., see J.F. Hershberger  Wiczk, W.M., see J.R. Lakowicz    Yamaguchi, K., F. Jensen, A. Dorigo and K.N. Houk, A spin correction procedure for un-  restricted Hartree Fock and Moller Plesset wavefunctions for singlet diradicals and  polyradicals  Yamauchi, S., see K. Tominaga  Yafiez, M., see F. Martin  149 (1988) 20    149 (1988) 251  149 (1988) 379    149 (1988) 521  149 (1988) 379  149 (1988) 503    149 (1988) 196  149  149  149  149  149  149  (1988) 295  (1988) 343  (1988) 557  (1988) 161  (1988) 273  (1988) 222  149 (1988) 32  149 (1988) 161  149 (1988) 417    149 (1988) 572  149 (1988) 295    149 (1988) 14  149 (1988) 547  149 (1988) 170  149 (1988) 516  149 (1988) 424    149 (1988) 265  149 (1988) 167  149 (1988) 491   149 (1988) 1    149 (1988) 239  149 (1988) 51  149 (1988) 134          149 (1988) 537  149 (1988) 32  149 (1988) 85  585  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  Yeager, D.L., see M. Jaszunski  Yogev, A., see I. Sofer    Zakaraya, M.G., see T.A. Marsagishvili  Zhang, J. and D.G. Imre, OH/OD bond breaking selectivity in HOD photodissociation  Zhang, Y. and M. Stuke, Laser mass spectrometric detection of A1H molecules as collision-  free exeimer laser photoproducts from aluminum alkyls  Zheng, Q., see Q. Qin  Zubek, M., Deexeitation of vibrationally excited CO (a fl) and N2 (A  E.7) metastable states  at a metal surface  149 (1988) 79  149 (1988) 439    149 (1988) 417  149 (1988) 233    149 (1988) 310  149 (1988) 128    149 (1988) 24  586  see K. Raghavan  Stuke, M., see Y. Zhang  Stuve, E.M., J.W. Rogers Jr., D. Ingersoll, D.W. Goodman, M.L. Thomas and M.T. Paffett,  Ultrahigh vacuum and electrochemical co-characterization studies of Cu on Ru (0001)  149  149  149  149    149  149  149  149  149  149  (1988) 40  (1988) 289  (1988) 118  (1988) 230    (1988) 109  (1988) 118  (1988) 463  (1988) 455  (1988) 265  (1988) 118  149 (1988) 482  149 (1988) 384    149 (1988) 451  149 (1988) 487    149 (1988) 185  149 (1988) 265      149 (1988) 565    149 (1988) 447    149 (1988) 180  (1988) 497  (1988) 565  (1988) 534  (1988) 339  149  149  149  149  149 (1988) 439    149 (1988) 367  149 (1988) 348    149 (1988) 228  149 (1988) 455  149 (1988) 230    149 (1988) 191  149 (1988) 89  149 (1988) 310    149 (1988) 557  584  Volume 149, number 5,6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 September 1988  Sugano, S., see E. Ilisca  Sundholm, D., Two-dimensional, fully numerical solution of the molecular Dirac equa-  tion. Dirac Slater calculations on LiH, Li2, BH and CH~  Suzuki, S., see T. Ohzeki  Svirschevsky, S. and M. Apostol, Solvent and pressure effects on transition rates of en-  zymatic reactions    Takahashi, H., see T. Ohzeki  Tanner, J.J. and M.M. Marieq, Far IR dissociation of a highly excited Morse oscillator  Theodorakopoulos, G. and I.D. Petsalakis, Ab initio calculations on the ground and ex-  cited electronic states of KrH  Thole, B.T., G. van der Laan and P.H. Butler, Spin-mixed ground state of Fe phthalocy-  anine and the temperature-dependent branching ratio in X-ray absorption spectroscopy  Thomas, J.M., see R. Brydson  Thomas, M.L., see E.M. Stuve  Tokumaru, K., see T. Arai  Tole, P., see P.W. Fowler  Tomas, F., see J. Planelles  Tominaga, K., S. Yamauchi and N. Hirota, The CIDEP spectrum of a radical pair of the  acetone ketyl radical in solution. Effect of deuteration  Tsuchiya, M., see T. Arai    Ulstrup, J., see T.A. Marsagishvili    Vallee, F., G.M. Gale and C. Flytzanis, Biphonon dynamics in ordered ammonium chloride  Van der Laan, G., see B.T. Thole  Van der Zande, W.J., J. Los, J.R. Peterson and C. Kubach, Decay of the C2Z~ quasibound  states of HeH: an experimental and theoretical study  Van Leuven, P., see J. Broeckhove  Veeman, W.S., see W.E.J.R. Maas  Vinette, F., see J. ~i~ek  Vogelsanger, B., see L. Martinache    Wahlgren, U., see I. Panas  Wallrafen, F., see H. Matthies  Weir, D., see P.V. Kamat  Westem, C.M., see J.M. Allen  Westin, E. and A. Rosen, Local density theory calculations of the ionization energies and  optical transitions in BaF and BaCI  Weston Jr., R.E., see J.F. Hershberger  Wiczk, W.M., see J.R. Lakowicz    Yamaguchi, K., F. Jensen, A. Dorigo and K.N. Houk, A spin correction procedure for un-  restricted Hartree Fock and Moller Plesset wavefunctions for singlet diradicals and  polyradicals  Yamauchi, S., see K. Tominaga  Yafiez, M., see F. Martin  149 (1988) 20    149 (1988) 251  149 (19</xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="mis" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>88803865</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(88)80386-5</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(88)80386-5</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="other" year="1988"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Author index to volume 149</ce:title>
         </head>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>