<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/0009261490801524</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(90)80152-4</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-0009261490801524</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)80152-4</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(90)80152-4</pii><dc:title>Author index to volume 172 </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>172</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>6</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>530</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>538</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>530-538</prism:pageRange><prism:number>6</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1990-09-21</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>21 September 1990</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1990  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:description/><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/0009261490801524" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/0009261490801524" rel="scidir"/></coredata><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20020115">2002-01-15</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20020115">2002-01-15</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2015-10-03T20:21:36</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-0009261490801524</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(90)80152-4</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>0009261490801524</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)80152-4</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.3</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-ONLY</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X09487</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20151005">2015-10-05T04:53:56.039075-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19900921</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1990</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1011052800">2002-01-15T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav articletitle</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>172</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>172</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>6</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>6</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 172, Issue 6</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>19</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>530</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>538</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>530</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>538</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19900921</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>21 September 1990</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1990-09-21</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1990</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>mis</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1990  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>AUTHORINDEXVOLUME172</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:refkeys/>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(90)80152-4</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>0009261490801524</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-0009261490801524</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)80152-4</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2015-10-05T04:53:56.039075-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1990-09-21</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-0009261490801524-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:0009261490801524/MAIN/application/pdf/5d49b2be06edf1a8fbd718230d8957ed/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:0009261490801524/MAIN/application/pdf/5d49b2be06edf1a8fbd718230d8957ed/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>630088</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>9</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-0009261490801524-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:0009261490801524/PREVIEW/image/png/98160440c19472ed4cc9f6a8ea877b40/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:0009261490801524/PREVIEW/image/png/98160440c19472ed4cc9f6a8ea877b40/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>60738</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LE~fERS  21 September 1990  Author Index to Volume 172  Abboud, J.-LM., see M. Alcami  Adams, G.F., see J.O. Jensen  AlcamI, M., 0. MO, M. Yanez, J.-L.M. Abboud and J. Elguero, Bond activation by pro-  tonation in the gas phase  Amos, A.T., T.F. Palmer, A. Walters and B.L. Burrows, Atom atom potential parameters  for van der Waals complexes of aromatics and rare-gas atoms  Anderson, M.W. and J. Klinowski, Monitoring organic products of catalytic reactions on  zeolites by two-dimensional f-resolved solid-state NMR  Angyan, J.G., see F Colonna  Attard, P., D. Wei and G.N. Patey, Critical comments on the nonlocal dielectric function  employed in recent theories of the hydration force  Axon, S.A., K. Huddersman and J. Klinowski, Gallium EXAFS and solid-state NMR stud-  ies of Ga-substituted MR-type zeolites    Balasubramanian, K., see K.K. Das  Bancroft, G.M., see Z.F. Liu  Banerjee, S.B., see P. Jana  Batova, E.E., see Y,Ya, Shafirovich  Behera, L., T. Kar and A.B. Sannigrahi, Effect of basis-set superposition on the atomic  charges and valencies in hydrogen- and lithium-bonded complexes  Berezhkovskii, A.M. and V.Yu. Zitserman, Solvent slow-mode influence on chemical re-  action dynamics: a multidimensional Kramers-theory treatment  Bergmann, 1., see T.P. Martin  Billing, G.D., see N. Markovic  Boldyrev, A.I. and P. von R. Schleyer, The electron affinity of LiBO2 and the structure of  its negative ion, LiBOj  Bouvet, M. and J. Simon, Electrical properties of rare earth bisphthalocyanine and bis-  naphthalocyanine complexes  Bowman, R.M., see M.H.M. Janssen  Brauman, J.I., R.N. Zare and R.D. Levine, Fragment isotope distribution as a signature of  molecular fluxionality  Brienne, J., see I. Ledoux  Bulatov, A. and V. Fetisov, Nonstationary nucleation in the supersaturated vapor  Burrow, P.D., see S.C. Chu  Burrows, B.L., see A.T. Amos   172 (1990) 471   172 (1990) 379   172 (1990) 471   172 (1990) 503    172 (1990) 275   172 (1990) 55   172 (1990) 69   172 (1990) 398  172 (1990)  172 (1990)  172 (1990)  172 (1990)  372  421  158  10  172 (1990) 487    172 (1990) 235  172 (1990) 209  172 (1990) 509    172 (1990) 193    172 (1990) 299  172 (1990) 99    172 (1990) 231  172 (1990) 440  172 (1990) 388  172 (1990) 17  172 (1990) 503  Cannistraro, S., see R. Lamanna  Carnie, S.L., see G.A. Christos  Castellani, L., see G. Zerbi  Cavell, R.G., see Z.F. Liu  Chabalowski, CF., see J.0. Jensen  172 (1990) 312  172 (1990) 249  172 (1990) 143  172 (1990) 421  172 (1990) 379  530  Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LE1TERS  21 September 1990  Chaudhuri, R., see D. Mukhopadhyay Jr.  Chibante, L.P.F., see L. Wang  Chierichetti, B., see (3. Zerbi  Christos, G.A. and S.L. Camie, Computer simulation of semi-dilute polyelectrolyte solutions  Chu, S.C. and P.D. Burrow, Dissociative attachment of electrons in the chloromethanes  Chung, C. and S. Wimperis, Three- and five-quantum filtration experiments in 25Mg NMR  of a macromolecular system  Colonna, F., J.G. Angyan and 0. Tapia, Modelling the electric field of water obtained from  accurate SCF wave functions  Cong, P., A. Mokhtari and A.H. Zewail, Femtosecond probing of persistent wave packet  motion in dissociative reactions: up to 40 ps  Cooksy, A.L., see A. O Keefe  Craw, J.S. and M.A.C.Nascimento, Ab initio  3C shielding parameters in acetylene clusters  Curl, R.F., see L. Wang  Cutler, J.N., see Z.F. Liii    Das, K.K. and K, Balasubramanian, Spectroscopic constants and potential energy curves  of electronic states of LaH  Davis, R.W., see CD. Paulse  Delmeile, M., see R. Lamanna  Dickinson, E., see D.J. McClements  Dietz, F., see K. Schoffel  Dodsworth, E.S. and A.B.P. Lever, The use of optical electronegativities to assign elec-  tronic spectra of semiquinone complexes  Doge, G.,D. Lindner, W. Richter and D. Schiel, The effect of resonant vibrational cou-  pling on the frequency of the v2 mode of liquid methyl iodide in Raman scattering and  infrared absorption  Dreger, Z., see J. Kalinowski    Ehara, M., see H. Nakatsuji  Elguero, J., see M. Alcami  Engels, B., see K. Funken  Eychmllller, A., see L. Katsikas    Fain, B., Supertunneling in dissipative media  Fenistein, S., M. Heninger, R. Man, 0. Mauclaire and Y.M. Yang, Radiative relaxation of  N0~(X, v=l 4)  Fetisov, V., see A. Bulatov  Field, M.J., Simulated annealing, classical molecular dynamics and the Hartree Fock  method: the NDDO approximation  Franchy, R., see P. Sjovall  Francois, J.P., see J.M.L. Martin  Francois, J.P., see J.M.L. Martin  Fujino, T., see Y. Hinatsu  Fujitsuka, M., see K. Nakamura  Funken, K., B. Engels, S.D. Peyerimhoff and F. Grein, Study of the hyperfine coupling con-  stants of the molecules NH2, NHD and ND2   172 (1990) 515   172 (1990) 335   172 (1990) 143   172 (1990) 249   172 (1990) 17   172 (1990) 94   172 (1990) 55   172 (1990) 109   172 (1990) 214   172 (1990) 265   172 (1990) 335   172 (1990) 421   172 (1990) 372   172 (1990) 43   172 (1990) 312   172 (1990) 449   172 (1990) 187   172 (1990) 151   172 (1990) 453   172 (1990) 522   172 (1990) 261   172 (1990) 471   172 (1990) 180   172 (1990) 201   172 (1990) 393   172 (1990) 89   172 (1990) 388  172 (1990) 83  172 (1990) 125   172 (1990) 346  172 (1990) 354   172 (1990) 131   172 (1990) 205   172 (1990) 180  531  Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEflERS  21 September 1990  Gallazzi, C., see 0. Zerbi  Ganguly, T., see P. Jana  Gburski, Z., see A. Moe  Ohosh, S.K., Energy derivatives in density-functional theory  Giersig, M., see L. K.atsikas  Gijbels, R., see J.M.L. Martin  Gijbels, R,, see J.M.L. Martin  Godlewski, J., see J. Kalinowski  Gbhlich, H., see T.P. Martin  Gonul, B., see E. Kasap  Goodman, D.W., see W.K. Kuhn  Graener, H., 0. Seifert and A. Laubereau, Direct observation of rotational relaxation times  by time-resolved infrared spectroscopy  Grein, F., see K. Funken  Guyot-Sionnest, P. and A. Tadjeddine, Spectroseopic investigations of adsorbates at the  metal electrolyte interface using sum frequency generation    Handy, N.C., see W.H. Miller  Harano, A., J. Kinoshita and S. Koda, Decomposition of gaseous hydrocarbons in a laser-  induced plasma as a novel carbonaceous source for cluster formation  He, J.-W., see W.K. Kuhn  Heath, J., see A. O Keefe  Heninger, M., see S. Fenistein  Hernandez, R., see W.H. Miller  Hess, B., see A.M. Zhabotinsky  Hinatsu, Y. and T. Fujino, Study of electron paramagnetic resonance on Ce01U0,902 solid  solution  Hjorth, J., see J. Skibsted  Ho, W., see P. SjOvall  Holloway, S. and B. Jackson, Rotational state distributions as a probe of dissociative  adsorption  Horn, M., see J.M. Warman  Huang, J.Y., see R. Superfine  Huddersman, K., see S.A. Axon    Inganas, 0., see 0. Zerbi  Ito, Y., see I. Suzuka    Jackson, B., see S. Holloway  Jakobsen, H.J., see J. Skibsted  Jana, P., O.K. Mallik, T. Ganguly and S.B. Banerjee, Heavy-atom effect on emission from  free and hydrogen-bonded complexes of excited 1,2,3,4-tetrahydroquinoline  Janssen, M.H.M., R.M. Bowman and A.H. Zewail, Femtosecond temporal spectroscopy of  ICE: inversion to the A3fl1 state potential  Jayatilaka, D., see W.H. Miller  Jensen, J.O., G.F. Adams and C.F. Chabalowski, Ab initio study of the electric dipole tran-  sition moment for the C~ t electronic transition in acetylene: theoretical predictions  of the absorption and magnetic circular dichroism intensities  172 (1990) 143  172 (1990) 158  172 (1990) 73  172 (1990) 77  172 (1990) 201  172 (1990) 346  172 (1990) 354  172 (1990) 522  172 (1990) 209  172 (1990) 499  172 (1990) 331   172 (1990) 435   172 (1990) 180   172 (1990) 341   172 (1990) 62   172 (1990) 219   172 (1990) 331   172 (1990) 214   172 (1990) 89   172 (1990) 62   172 (1990) 445   172 (1990) 131   172 (1990) 279   172 (1990) 125   172 (1990) 40   172 (1990) 114   172 (1990) 303  172 (1990) 398    172 (1990) 143  172 (1990) 409    172 (1990) 40    172 (1990) 279    172 (1990) 158    172 (1990) 99    172 (1990) 62    172 (1990) 379  532  21 September 1990  Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LE~FERS  Kabbaj, O.K., M.-B. Lepetit and 3.-P. Malrieu, Inclusion of dynamical polarization effects  is sufficient to obtain reliable energies and structures of Het clusters  Kajimoto, 0., see K. Yamasaki  Kakitani, T., see M. Saito  Kalinowski, J., Z. Dreger, J. Godlewski and P. Mondalski, Structural transformations in N-  isopropylcarbazole crystal monitored by pressure-induced luminescence  Kar, t, see L. Behera  Kasap, E., B. GonUl and M. Sim~ek, Supersymmetric WKB solutions for pseudoharmonic  and Mie-type potentials  Kasemo, B., see P. SjOvall  Katada, M., see H. Ohe  Katsikas, L., A. EychmUller, M. Giersig and H. Weller, Discrete excitonic transitions in  quantum-sized CdS particles  Keniry, M.A. and B.C. Sanctuary, Experimental verification of the exact response of nu-  clear spins to an exponentially shaped pulse  Kinoshita, J., see A. Harano  Kitajima, M., see K. Nakamura  Kitamura, T., see T. Yamanaka  Klinowski, J., see M.W. Anderson  Klinowski, J., see S.A. Axon  Klobukowski, M., Atomic correlation energies from effective-core-potential and model-po-  tential calculations  Kloc, A. and Z. Gburski, Interaction-induced absorption in rare-gas/liquid mixture: a two-  body contribution  Kobayashi, Y., Effect of external pressure on the reactivity of nitrobenzene toward posi-  tronium in hexane and benzene solutions  ICoth, S., see A. Harano  Koepke, Cz. and A. Lempicki, Excited state  photochromism  in bismuth germanate  Koepke, Cz. and A. Lempicki, Excited state absorption in Bi4Ge3O12  Koga, N. and K. Morokuma, A simple scheme of estimating substitution or substituent ef-  fects in the ab initio MO method based on the shift operator  Koyama, Y., see E. Nishizawa  Krausz, E., see H. Riesen  Kroon, 3., see J.M. Warman  Krossner, T., see K. Schoffel  Kubo, A., see H. Ohe  Kuhn, W.K., J.-W. He and D.W. Goodman, JR study of CO surface diffusion on sub-  monolayer mctal overlayers  Kunst, M., see K.-M. Schindler    Lamanna, R., M. Delinelle and S. Cannistraro, A near-infrared study of hydrogen bonding  in human albumin aqueous solutions  Lange, T., see T.P. Martin  Laubereau, A., see H. Graener  Laverdet, G., G. La Bras, A. Mellouki and Ci. Poulet, The Br+ HO2 reactiOn revisited: ab-  solute determination of the rate constant at 298 K  Leahey, 3., see B.H. Loo  Le Bras, 0., see U. Laverdet  172 (1990) 483  172 (1990) 271  172 (1990) 169    172 (1990) 522  172 (1990) 487    172 (1990) 499  172 (1990) 125  172 (1990) 284    172 (1990) 201    172 (1990) 295  172 (1990) 219  172 (1990) 205  172 (1990) 29  172 (1990) 275  172 (1990) 398    172 (1990) 361    172 (1990) 73    172 (1990) 307  172 (1990) 219  172 (1990) 224  172 (1990) 227    172 (1990) 243  172 (1990) 317  172 (1990) 5  172 (1990) 114  172 (1990) 187  172 (1990) 284    172 (1990) 331  172 (1990) 137      172 (1990) 312  172 (1990) 209  172 (1990) 435    172 (1990) 430  172 (1990) 33  172 (1990) 430  533  Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEflERS  21 September 1990  Ledoux, 1., J. Zyss, 3.5. Siegel, J. Brienne and J.-M. Lehn, Second-harmonic generation from  non-dipolar non-centrosymmetric aromatic charge-transfer molecules  Lee, Y.G., see B.H. Leo  Lehn, J.-M., see I. Ledoux  Lempicki, A., see Cz. Koepke  Lempicki, A., see Cz. Koepke  Lepetit, M.-B., see A. Sanchez de Meras  Lepetit, M.-B., see O.K. Kabbaj  Lever, A.B.P., see E.S. Dodsworth  Levin, P.P., see V.Ya. Shafirovich  Levine, R.D., see J.I. Brauman  Lindner, D., see U. Doge  Liu, Z.F., J.N. Cutler, G.M. Bancroft, K.H. Tan, R.G. Cavell and J.S. Tse, High resolution  gas phase photoabsorption spectra and multiple-scattering Xix study of PX3 (X=H, CH3,  CF3) compounds at the P L~ edge  Leo, B.H., 3. Leahey and Y.G. Lee, Enhanced Raman spectroscopic study of the adsorption  of thiocarboliydrazide on silver and copper electrode surfaces    Mahmood, M.F., Collisional behavior of HgX (B2~ X 2E) formation involving CO~ and  Cot ions and HgX2 (X = Cl, Br) molecules  Mallik, G.K., see P. Jana  Malrieu, 3.-P., see A. Sanchez de Meras  Malrieu, 3.-P., see O.K. Kabbaj  Markovic, N., G.D. Billing and J.T. Muckerman, On the use of grid methods for the so-  lution of reactive scattering problems in hyperspherical coordinates  Martin, J.M.L., J.P. Francois and R. Gijbels, On size-consistency corrections for limited  configuration-interaction calculations  Martin, J.M.L., J.P. Francois and R. Gijbels, Some cost-effective approximations to CCSD  and QCISD  Martin, T.P., T. Bergmann, H. GOhlich and T. Lange, Observation of electronic shells of  atoms in large Na clusters  Marx, R., see S. Fenistein  Matsuoka, 0., Basis-set expansion method for relativistic atoms in the atomic-nucleus model  of a finite sphere of constant electric field  Mauclaire, 0., see S. Fenistein  McClements, D.J., E. Dickinson and M.J.W. Povey, Crystallization in hydrocarbon-in-water  emulsions containing a mixture of solid and liquid droplets  Meletov, K.P., High-pressure study of the crystal-field-induced mixing of exciton states in  a naphthalene crystal  Mellouki, A., see 0. Laverdet  Merkt, F. and T.P. Softley, Resonance-enhanced sum-frequency generation of XUY ra-  diation in CO. Chem. Phys. Letters 165 (1990) 477. Erratum  Miller, W.H., R. Hernandez, N.C. Handy, D. Jayatilaka and A. Willetts, Ab initio calcu-  lation of anharmonic constants for a transition state, with application to semiclassical  transition state tunneling probabilities  Mo, 0., see M. Alcamf  Mokhtari, A., see P. Cong  172 (1990) 440  172 (1990) 33  172 (1990) 440  172 (1990) 224  172 (1990) 227  172 (1990) 163  172 (1990) 483  172 (1990) 151  172 (1990) 10  172 (1990) 231  172 (1990) 453      172 (1990) 421    172 (1990) 33      172 (1990) 23  172 (1990) 158  172 (1990) 163  172 (1990) 483    172 (1990) 509    172 (1990) 346    172 (1990) 354    172 (1990) 209  172 (1990) 89    172 (1990) 175  172 (1990) 89    172 (1990) 449    172 (1990) 147  172 (1990) 430    172 (1990) 529      172 (1990) 62  172 (1990) 471  172 (1990) 109  534  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETFERS  21 September 1990  Volume 172, number 6  Mondaiski, P., see J. Kalinowski  Morokuma, K., see N. Koga  Moss, R.E., Calculations on the 0,1 and 0,3 vibration rotation levels of Ht  Muckerman, J.T., see N. Markovic  Mukheijee, D., see D. Mukhopadhyay Jr.  Mukhopadhyay Jr., D., R. Chaudhuri and D. Mukhe~jee, A new nonperturbative theory of  core-hole ionizations: a compact duster-expansion technique for treating relaxation effects  MUller, B., M. Schuler and J. Reinhold, Ab initio SCF calculations on the potential surfaces  of phosphine hydrogen halide complexes in the gas phase  MUller, S.C., see A.M. Zhabotinsky    Naaman, R., see Y. Paz  Nakamura, K., M. Fujitsuka and M. Kitajima, Finite size effect on Raman scattering of  graphite microcrystals  Nakatsuji, H. and M. Ehara, Collision-induced absorption spectra of CsXe system studied  by SAC-C! theory  Narita, S., see T. Shibuya  Nascimento, M.A.C., see J.S. Craw  Nicolaides, C.A., see P. Valtazanos  Nishizawa, E. and Y. Koyama, The T1 Raman spectra of bacteriochlorophyll a: changes in  the bond orders of the conjugated macrocycle upon triplet excitation    Ohe, H., A. Kubo, M. Katada and H, Sano, Motional narrowing of  3C dipolar magic-an-  gle-spinning nuclear magnetic resonance spectra  Okamoto, H. and K. Yoshihara, Theoretical study on polarized time-resolved resonance  coherent anti-Stokes Raman scattering: effects of ultrafast molecular rearrangement in  the electronically excited state  O Keefe, A., J.J. Scherer, A.L Cooksy, R. Sheeks, J. Heath and R.J. Saykally, Cavity ring  down dye laser spectroscopy of jet-cooled metal clusters: Cu2 and Cu3  Oliver, A.M., see J.M. Warman  Osad ko, I.S., Density matrix approach to optical dephasing in solids: nonperturbative the-  ory for dephasing processes, Chem. Phys. Letters 167 (1990) 412. Erratum    Paddon-Row, M.N., see J.M. Warman  Palmer, T.F., see A.T. Amos  Patey, U.N., see P. Attard  Paulse, CD., R.A. Poirier and R.W. Davis, The molecular structures and harmonic force  fields of SO2, S20, and S202 from combined spectroscopic and SCF results  Paz, Y. and R. Naaman, Vibrational energy distribution in aniline scattered from surfaces  covered with organized organic monolayers  Peyerimhoff, S.D., see K. Funken  Poirier, R.A., see C.D. Paulse  Poulet, 0., see 0. Laverdet  Povey, M.J.W., see D.J. McClements  Pratum, T.K., Correction for anisotropic off-resonance decoupling effects in CPMAS of  moderate susceptibility materials  172 (1990) 522  172 (1990) 243  172 (1990) 458  172 (1990) 509  172 (1990) 515    172 (1990) 515    172 (1990) 478    172 (1990) 445    172 (1990) 120    172 (1990) 205    172 (1990) 261  172 (1990)494  172 (1990) 265  172 (1990) 254    172 (1990) 317      172 (1990) 284      172 (1990) 323  172 (1990) 214    172 (1990) 114    172 (1990) 330    172 (1990) 114  172 (1990) 503  172 (1990) 69    172 (1990) 43    172 (1990) 120  172 (1990) 180  172 (1990) 43  172 (1990) 430  172 (1990) 449    172 (1990) 291  535  Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEflERS  21 September 1990  Reinhold, 3., see B. MUller  Richter, W., see 0. DOge  Riesen, H. and E. Krausz, Resonant line narrowing in Ru(ll) tris( 3,3 -biisoquinoline)    Saito, M. and T. Kakitani, Monte Carlo simulation study on solvation energy of polar  solutions  Salzner, U. and P. von R. Scbleyer, Ab initio studies of the geometries and electronic struc-  tures of CaF2 and CaC12  Sanchez de Meras, A., M.-B. Lepetit and 3.-P. Maliieu, Discontinuity of valence CASSCF  wave functions around wealdy avoided crossing between valence configurations  Sanctuary, B.C., see M.A. Keniry  SandstrOm, M., see D. Stromberg  Sannigrahi, A.B., see L. Behera  Sano, H., see H. Ohe  Saykally, R.J., see A. O Keefe  Scherer, J.J., see A. O Keefe  Schiel, D., see G. Doge  Schindler, K.-M. and M. Kunst, Gas adsorption and the charge-carrier kinetics in ZnO  powder  Schleyer, P. von R., see A.!. Boldyrev  Schleyer, P. von R., see U. Salzner  SchOffel, K., F. Dietz and T. Krossuer, Model mechanisms for the thermal cis trans iso-  merization of cyanines  Schuler, M., see B. MUller  Seifert, G., see H. Graener  Shafirovich, V.Ya., E.E. Batova and P.P. Levin, Magnetic field effect on the recombination  of the triplet radical ion pair state of the Zn-porphyrin viologen dyad: the influence of  the supramolecule microenvironment  Sheeks, R., see A. O Keefe  Shen, Y.R., see R. Superfine  Shibuya, T. and S. Narita, On the Coulomb repulsion integrals used in the parametrized  equations-of-motion method for ~t ~.ic~ transitions  Siegel, J.S., see I. Ledoux  Simon, J., see M. Bouvet  Simsek, M., see E. Kasap  Sjovall, P., S.K. So, B. Kasemo, R. Franchy and W. Ho, NO2 adsorption on graphite at 90  K  Skibsted, 3., 1. Hjorth and H.J. Jakobsen, Correlation between  Si NMR chemical shifts  and mean Si-O bond lengths for calcium silicates  Slanina, Z., Water-dimer structure, energetics and harmonic vibrations in flexible BJH and  MCYL potentials  Smalley, R.E., see L. Wang  So, S.K., see P. SjOvall  Softley, T.P., see F. Merkt  StrOmberg, D., M. SandstrOm and U. Wahlgren, Theoretical calculations on the structure  of the hexahydrated divalent zinc, cadmium and mercury ions  172 (1990) 478  172 (1990) 453  172 (1990) 5      172 (1990) 169    172 (1990) 461    172 (1990) 163  172 (1990) 295  172 (1990) 49  172 (1990) 487  172 (1990) 284  172 (1990) 214  172 (1990) 214  172 (1990) 453    172 (1990) 137  172 (1990) 193  172 (1990) 461    172 (1990) 187  172 (1990) 478  172 (1990) 435      172 (1990) 10  172 (1990) 214  172 (1990) 303    172 (1990) 494  172 (1990) 440  172 (1990) 299  172 (1990) 499    172 (1990) 125    172 (1990) 279    172 (1990) 367  172 (1990) 335  172 (1990) 125  172 (1990) 529    172 (1990) 49  536  Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  21 September 1990  Superfine, R., IX. Huang and Y.R. Shen, Experimental determination of the sign of mo-  lecular dipole moment derivatives: an infrared visible sum frequency generation ab-  solute phase measurement study  Suzuka, 1., T. Tomioka andY. Ito, Ion-induced sensitized phosphorescence excitation spec-  tra of halobenzenes in supersonic jets  172 (1990) 303    172 (1990) 409    172 (1990) 341  172 (1990) 29  172 (1990) 405  172 (1990) 421  172 (1990) 55  172 (1990) 416  172 (1990) 335  172 (1990) 409  172 (1990) 421    172 (1990) 29  172 (1990) 405  172 (1990) 254  172 (1990) 49  172 (1990) 503  172 (1990) 335  172 (1990) 114  172 (1990) 69  172 (1990) 201  172 (1990) 416  172 (1990) 62  172 (1990) 94  172 (1990) 29  172 (1990) 405  172 (1990) 271  172 (1990) 471  172 (1990) 89  172 (1990) 323  172 (1990) 231  172 (1990) 143  537  Tadjeddine, A., see P. Guyot-Sionnest  Talcahashi, Y., see T. Yamanaka  Takahashi, Y.,see T. Yamanalca  Tan, KH., see Z.F. Liu  Tapia, 0., see F. Colonna  Thiemens, M.H., see J. Wen  Tittel, FL, see L. Wang  Tomioka, T., see I. Suzuka  Tse, J.S., see Z.F. Liu  Uchida, K., see T. Yamanalca  Uchida,, K., see T. Yamanaka  Valtazanos, P. and CIA. Nicolaides, Local minima of ground hypersurfaces. The cases of  Her and of the BeHr nonclassical dihydrogen complex    Wahigren, U., see D. Stromberg  Walters, A., see A.T. Amos  Wang, L., L.P.F. Chibante, F,K. Tittel, R.F. Curl and R.E. Smalley, Ammonia chemisorp-  tion on gallium arsenide clusters  Warman, J.M., M. Horn, M.N. Paddon-Row, A.M. Oliver and J. Kroon, (Sub )nanosecond  intramolecular hole transfer through a rigid, 10-sigma-bond, saturated-hydrocarbon  bridge  Wei, D., see P. Attard  Weller, H., see L. K..atsikas  Wen, 3. and M.H. Thiemens, An apparent new isotope effect in a molecular decomposition  and implications for nature  Willetts, A., see W.H. Miller  Wirnperis, S., see C. Chung    Yamanaka, 1., Y. Takahashi, T. Kitamura and K. Uchida, Time-resolved fluorescence  spectra of pyrene doped in amorphous silica glasses  Yamanaka, T., Y. Takabashi and K. Uchida, Time-resolved fluorescence spectra of naph-  thalene doped in amorphous silica glasses  Yamasaki, K. and 0. Kajimoto, Solvent effect in supercritical fluids: keto enol equilibria  of acetylacetone and ethylacetoacetate  Yaflez, M., see M. Alcami  Yang, Y.M., see S. Fenistein  Yoshihara, K., see H. Okamoto    Zare, R.N., see J.I. Brauman  Zerbi, 0., L. Castellani, B. Chierichetti, C. Ciallazzi and 0. IngAnas, Non-equilibrium  structures and geometry relaxation in polyoctyltbiophene  Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEITERS  21 September 1990  Zewail, A.H., see M.H.M. Janssen  Zewail, A.H., see P. Cong  Zhabotinsky, A.M., S.C. Muller and B. Hess, Interaction of chemical waves in a thin layer  of microheterogeneous gel with a transversal chemical gradient  Zitserman, V~Yu., see A~M. Berezhkovskii  Zyss, J., see I. Ledoux  172 (1990) 99  172 (1990) 109    172 (1990) 445  172 (1990) 235  172 (1990) 440  538    K  Skibsted, 3., 1. Hjorth and H.J. Jakobsen, Correlation between  Si NMR chemical shifts  and mean Si-O bond lengths for calcium silicates  Slanina, Z., Water-dimer structure, energetics and harmonic vibrations in flexible BJH and  MCYL potentials  Smalley, R.E., see L. Wang  So, S.K., see P. SjOvall  Softley, T.P., see F. Merkt  StrOmberg, D., M. SandstrOm and U. Wahlgren, Theoretical calculations on the structure  of the hexahydrated divalent zinc, cadmium and mercury ions  172 (1990) 478  172 (1990) 453  172 (1990) 5      172 (1990) 169    172 (1990) 461    172 (1990) 163  172 (1990) 295  172 (1990) 49  172 (1990) 487  172 (1990) 284  172 (1990) 214  172 (1990) 214  172 (1990) 453    172 (1990) 137  172 (1990) 193  172 (1990) 461    172 (1990) 187  172 (1990) 478  172 (1990) 435      172 (1990) 10  172 (1990) 214  172 (1990) 303    172 (1990) 494  172 (1990) 440  172 (1990) 299  172 (1990) 499    172 (1990) 125    172 (1990) 279    172 (1990) 367  172 (1990) 335  172 (1990) 125  172 (1990) 529    172 (1990) 49  536  Volume 172, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  21 September 1990  Superfine, R., IX. Huang and Y.R. Shen, Experimental determination of the sign of mo-  lecular dipole moment derivatives: an infrared visible sum frequency generation ab-  solute phase measurement study  Suzuka, 1., T. Tomioka andY. Ito, Ion-induced sensitized phosphorescence excitation spec-  tra of halobenzenes in supersonic jets  172 (1990) 303    172 (1990) 409    172 (1990) 341  172 (1990) 29  172 (1990) 405  172 (1990) 421  172 (1990) 55  172 (1990) 416  172 (1990) 335  172 (1990) 409  172 (1990) 421    172 (1990) 29  172 (1990) 405  </xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="mis" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>90801524</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(90)80152-4</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)80152-4</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="other" year="1990"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Author index to volume 172</ce:title>
         </head>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>