<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926149087039T</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(90)87039-T</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-000926149087039T</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)87039-T</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(90)87039-T</pii><dc:title>Author index to volume 165 </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>165</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>6</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>555</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>563</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>555-563</prism:pageRange><prism:number>6</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1990-02-02</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>2 February 1990</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1990  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:description/><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926149087039T" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/000926149087039T" rel="scidir"/></coredata><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20020115">2002-01-15</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20020115">2002-01-15</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2015-09-28T15:49:59</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926149087039T</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(90)87039-T</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926149087039T</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)87039-T</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.2</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-ONLY</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X09128</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20150929">2015-09-29T20:34:15.649222-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19900202</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1990</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1011052800">2002-01-15T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav articletitle</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>165</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>165</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>6</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>6</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 165, Issue 6</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>19</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>555</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>563</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>555</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>563</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19900202</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>2 February 1990</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1990-02-02</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1990</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>mis</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1990  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>AUTHORINDEXVOLUME165</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:refkeys/>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(90)87039-T</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926149087039T</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926149087039T</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)87039-T</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2015-09-29T20:34:15.649222-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1990-02-02</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926149087039T-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926149087039T/MAIN/application/pdf/69bc8d8becdb9c82e9d2517e12bb452e/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926149087039T/MAIN/application/pdf/69bc8d8becdb9c82e9d2517e12bb452e/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>601706</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>9</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926149087039T-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926149087039T/PREVIEW/image/png/cabdb4bfe4ae871d5005d57bd8bbee21/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926149087039T/PREVIEW/image/png/cabdb4bfe4ae871d5005d57bd8bbee21/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>59787</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>Volume 165, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 February 1990  AUTHOR INDEX TO VOLUME 165    Adachi, K., see K. Saito  Akiyama, Y., K. Tanaka and T. Tanaka, Infrared diode laser spectroscopy of the GeF4 ion  Alberts, I.L. and H.F. Schaefer III, The boron carbon triple bond ( fl~C ): some theo-  retical predictions  Alcock, N.W., The bond energy in a metal is a linear function of atomic size  Alsac, E., C. Laroche, E. Lemaire and H. Van Damme, Viscochemical fingering in a col-  loidal fluid  Andino, J.M., see T.J. Wallington  Andrews, L, see Z. Mielke  Anisimov, 0.A., see V.0. Saik  Arnau, F., see J.J. Novoa  Auger, M. and H.C. Jarrell, Elucidation of slow motions in glycoglycerolipid bilayers by  two-dimensional solid-state deuteron NMR  Azumi, T., see N. Okabe  165 (1990) 383  165 (1990) 335    165 (1990) 250  165 (1990) 339  165  165  165  165  165  (1990) 277  (1990) 189  (1990) 146  (1990) 142  (1990) 503  165 (1990) 162  165 (1990) 24  Bachhuber, K., see J. Barthel  Bagchi, B., see A. Chandra  Balihausen, C.J. and M. Gajhede, The tunnel effect and scattering by a negative Kratzer  potential  Bancroft, G.M., see J.D. Bozek  Barra, AL., L.C. Brunel and J.B. Robert, EPR spectroseopy at very high field  Barrat, J.-L, Numerical simulation of Brownian motion with frequency-dependent friction  Barthel, J., K. Bachhuber, R. Buchner and H. Hetzenauer, Dielectric spectra of some com-  mon solvents in the microwave region. Water and lower alcohols  Bartlett, R.J., J.D. Watts, SA. Kucharski and J. Noga, Non-iterative fifth-order triple and  quadruple excitation energy corrections in correlated methods  Barzoukas, M., see S. Norvez  Bassler, H., see R.F. Mahrt  Bastiaens, P., see R. Leenders  Bauschlicher Jr., C.W., H. Partridge and S.R. Langhoff, Comparison of the bonding be-  tween ML~ and ML~ (M=metal, L=noble gas)  Bauschlicher Jr., C.W. and M. Rosi, Addendum to  On the bonding in Be~~   Bernardi, M., see F.A. Giantureo  Besley, S., P.M. Cullis, R. Partridge, M.C.R. Symons and R.T. Wheelhouse, Motion of po-  lyammonium ions on aqueous solutions of DNA  Binning Jr., R.C., see Y. Ishikawa  Block, J.H., see M. Ehsasi  Bodenhausen, G., see L. Emsley  Bozek, J.D., J.N. Cutler, G.M. Bancroft, L.L. Coatsworth, K.H. Tan, D.S. Yang and  R.G. Cavell, High resolution molecular gas phase photoelectron spectra of core levels  using synchrotron radiation   vibrational and ligand field splittings   165 (1990) 369   165 (1990) 93   165 (1990) 449   165 (1990) 1   165 (1990) 107   165 (1990) 551   165 (1990) 369   165 (1990) 513   165 (1990) 41   165 (1990) 125   165 (1990) 315   165 (1990) 272   165 (1990) 501   165 (1990) 344   165 (1990) 120   165 (1990) 237   165 (1990) 115   165 (1990) 469   165 (1990) 1  555  Volume t65, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 February 1990  Brouard, M., M.T. Martinez, C.J. Milne, J.P. Simons and J.-X. Wang, Near threshold stereo-  dynamics of molecular photodissociation: the visible and near ultraviolet photodisso-  ciation of H202  Broyer, M., see G.-H. Jeung  Brudzynski, R.J., R.J. Sension and B. Hudson, Resonance Raman study of the first ab-  sorption band of H2S  Brum, J.L., S. Deshmukh and B. Koplitz, Substantial H-atom production from the 193 nm  photolysis of triethylaluminum  Brunel, L.C., see A.L. Barra  Buchner, R., see J. Barthel  Bunker, P.R., see P.C. Gomez  Burshtein, AI. and V.A. Morozov, Activationless photoionization reactions    Campbell, E.E.B. and A. Tittes, Observation of highly excited electronic states of (CO2)m  clusters  Cavell, R.G., see J.D. Bozek  Cederbaum, L.S., see H.-D. Meyer  Chambaud, G. and P. Rosmus, Theoretical radiative lifetimes in NO~ (X  ~)  Chandra, A. and B. Bagchi, Relationship between energy gap time correlation and fluo-  rescence Stokes shift correlation functions in solvation dynamics  Chen, K. and C. Pci, Exact evaluation of two-dimensional Franck Condon integrals under  the Duschinsky mixing effect  Christmann, K., see M. Ehsasi  Chu, S.-I., see K. Wang  Coalson, R.D., Application of the time-dependent Hartree grid method to inelastic mo-  lecular scattering problems  Coatsworth, L.L., see J.D. Bozek  Cullis, P.M., see S. Besley  Cutler, J.N., see J.D. Bozek    Davidenko, N.A., see N.G. Kuvshinsky  De Boer, S. and D.A. Wiersma, Dephasiog-induced damping of superradiant emission in  J-aggregates  Dehmer, J.L., see S.T. Pratt  Dehmer, P.M., see S.T. Pratt  DeLeeuw, Bi., see R.S. Grey  Depasse, F. and J.M. Vigoureux, The use of the stationary perturbation method in cal-  culations of surface-induced dynamic polarizability, Chem. Phys. Letters 160 (1989)  311. Erratum  Deshmukh, S., see J.L. Brum  Diehl, P. and J. Jokisaari,  31Xe NMR in probing electric field gradients in thermotropic  nematogens  Donovan, R.J., see A.J. Yencha  Duncan, J.L., G.D. Nivellini, F. Tullini and L. Fusina, CH stretching anharmonicity in  CH2=CF2 and CH2=CCI2  Duportail, G. and P. Lianos, Phospholipid vesicles treated as fractal objects. A fluorescence  probe study  Dupuis, M., see P. Mougenot   165 (1990) 423   165 (1990) 494   165 (1990) 487   165 (1990) 413   165 (1990) 107   165 (1990) 369   165 (1990) 351   165 (1990) 432   165 (1990) 289   165 (1990) 1   165 (1990) 73   165 (1990) 429   165 (1990) 93   165 (1990) 523   165 (1990) 115   165 (1990) 199   165 (1990) 443   165 (1990) 1   165 (1990) [20   165 (1990) 1   165 (1990) 323   165 (1990) 45   165 (1990) 131   165 (1990) 131   165 (1990) 257   165 (1990) 554   165 (1990) 413   165 (1990) 389   165 (1990) 283   165 (1990) 362   165 (1990) 35   165 (1990) 87  556  Volume 165, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 February 1990  Ehsasi, M., 0. Frank, J.H. Block and K. Christmann, Coupled chemical oscillators in cat-  alytic oxidation of CO on Pd (110) surfaces  Elsaesser, T., see M. Wiechmann  Emsley, L. and G. Bodenhausen, Gaussian pulse cascades: new analytical functions for rec-  tangular selective inversion and in-phase excitation in NMR  Ewig, C.S., see J. Tellinghuisen    Fain, B. and 5.1-I. Lin, General asymptotic behaviors for amplitude and frequency depen-  dence of multiphoton ionization rates  Fontijn, A., see A.G. Slavejkov  Fowler, P.W., P. Lazzeretti and R. Zanasi, Electric and magnetic properties of the aromatic  sixty-carbon cage  Frank, 0., see M. Ehsasi  Freund, H.-J., see H.H. Graen  Frey, W., see M. Wiechmann  Fusina, L., see J.L. Duncan    Gajhede, M., see C.J. Ballhausen  GantefOr, G., H.R. Siekmann, H.O. Lutz and K.H. Meiwes-Broer, Pure metal and metal-  doped rare gas clusters grown in a pulsed arc cluster ion source  Geacintov, N.E., see M. Zielinski  Gharavi, A., see C.K. Teh  Gianturco, FA., M. Bernardi and M. Venanzi, Accuracy of the lOS approximation for highly  inelastic RET collisions  Giroud, M., see O. Nedelec  Gislason, E.A., see K.M. Sluis  Goez, M., Evaluation of flash CIDNP experiments by iterative reconvolution  Gomez, P.C. and P.R. Bunker, Tunneling splittings in C2H~  Gozashti, S., L-T. Zhang, X.M. Wu, F. Zhou and M.J. Ondrechen, A hybrid Hubbard model  for discrete and periodic backbonded complexes  Graen, H. H., M. Neumann, J. Wambach and H-J. Freund, Identification of precursor states  in the dissociation of adsorbed benzene on Os(000l): a HREELS study  Graener, H., The equilibration of vibrational excess energy  Grey, RS., B.J. DeLeeuw and H.F. Schaefer III, Germanium germanium multiple bonds;  the singlet electronic ground state of Ge2H2  Grobner, G., see C. Mayer  Gullidge, P.M.N. and G.W. Neilson, The cation structure of Ni-ATP in aqueous solution    Hama, Y., see M. Yamaji  Hashimoto, H., see M. Kuki  Hatano, M., see H. Konami  Henstra, k, t-S. Lin, J. Schmidt and W.Th. Wenekebach, High dynamic nuclear polari-  zation at room temperature  Herwig, KW., see B.S. Schirato  Hetzenauer, H., see J. Barthel  Heydtmann, H., B. Hildebrandt and M. Vartholomu, HF infrared emission from the re-  active systems F+CH3CF3 and F+CH3CCI3   165 (1990) 115   165 (1990) 28   165 (1990) 469   165 (1990) 355   165 (1990) 229   165 (1990) 375   165 (1990) 79   165 (1990) 115   165 (1990) 137   165 (1990) 28   165 (1990) 362   165 (1990) 449   165 (1990) 293   165 (1990) 297   165 (1990) 460   165 (1990) 344   165 (1990) 329   165 (1990) 195   165 (1990) Il   165 (1990) 351   165 (1990) 208   165 (1990) 137   165 (1990) 110   165 (1990) 257   165 (1990) 155   165 (1990) 457   165 (1990) 309   165 (1990) 417   165 (1990) 397   165 (1990) 6   165 (1990) 453   165 (1990) 369   165 (1990) 379  557  Volume 165, number 6  CHEMECAL PHYSICS LE~~ERS  2 February 1990  Hildebrandt, B., see H. Heydtmann  Hirano, T., N. Nakagawa, A. Murakami and O. Nomura, The lowest state of HC2N: po-  tentiality of triangular singlet  A, Chem. Phys. Letters 162 (1989) 89. Erratum  Hollenstein, H., M. Lewerenz and M. Quack, Isotope effects in the Fermi resonance of the  CH chromophore in CHX, molecules  Hopkirk, A., see A.J. Yencha  Horvath, C., see M. Zielinski  Hoshino, M., see M. Yamaji  Hudson, B., see R.J. Brudzyoski    Ikeyama, T., see N. Okabe  Imamura, A., see K. Saito  Ishikawa, Y., H. Sekino and R.C. Binning Jr., Effects of basis set contraction in relativistic  calculations on neon, argon, and germanium  Ishikawa, Y. and H. Sekino, Variational bounds in Dirac Fock basis set expansion  calculations  Itoh, M., see Y. Tanimoto  165 (1990) 100  165 (1990) 189  165 (1990) 162  165 (1990) 494  165 (1990) 389  Kaino, T., see T. Kurihara  Kalenik, J., I. Majerz, Z. Malarski and L. Sobczyk, Isotopic effect on  Cl NQR spectra of  pentaehlorophenol amine hydrogen-bonded complexes  Kato, T., see H. Kawashima  Katsuki, S., An ab initio effective Hamiltonian method applied to a relativistic molecule,  AgH  Kawashima, H., T. Kato and T. Shida, Resonance Raman study of the radical cation of  naphthalene in a glassy matrix at 77 K  Kela, D.K., see A.J. Yencha  Kita, A., see Y. Tanimoto  Knoll, W., see F.-J. Schmitt  Kobayashi, H., see T. Kurihara  Kobayashi, N., see H. Konami  Konami, H., M. Hatano, N. Kobayashi and T. Osa, Redox potentials of a series of lan-  thanide-bisphthalocyanine sandwich complexes  Koplitz, B., see J.L. Brum  Koptyug, A.V., see V.0, Saik  Kothe, G., see C. Mayer  Koyama, Y., see M. Kuki  Krausz, E., G. Moran and H. Riesen, Temperature-dependent lifetimes, MCPL and shifts  of the luminescence in the materials [Ru (bpy )~(bpy-d8 ]2+, x= 0 3, in dilute systems  Krausz, E., Transients in the luminescence of [Ru(bpy),j2~ and selectively deuterated  analogues at low temperatures  165 (1990) 379    165 (1990) 374  165  165  165  165  165  (1990) 175  (1990) 283  (1990) 297  (1990) 309  (1990) 487   165 (1990) 24   165 (1990) 383   165 (1990) 237    165 (1990) 243  165 (1990) 184  Jakubetz, W., J. Manz and H.-J. Schreier, Theory of optimal laser pulses for selective tran-  sitions between molecular eigenstates  Japar, S.M., see T.J. Wallington  Jarrell, H.C., see M. Auger  Jeung, G.-H., M. Broyer and P. Labastie, Lowest electronic states of Nat  Jokisaari, J., see P. Diehl  165 (1990) 171    165 (1990) 15  165 (1990) 59    165 (1990) 535  165  165  165  165  165  165    165  165  165  165  165  (1990) 59  (1990) 283  (1990) 184  (1990) 54  (1990) 171  (1990) 397    (1990) 397  (1990) 413  (1990) 142  (1990) 155  (1990) 417  165 (1990) 401    165 (1990) 407  558  Vnlume 165, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 February 1990  Kubodera, K., see T. Kurihara  Kucharski, SA., see R.J. Bartlett  Kuki, M., H. Hashimoto and Y. Koyama, The 2  A~ state of a carotenoid bound to the  chromatophore membrane of Rhodobacter sphaeroides 2.4.1 as revealed by transient res-  onance Raman spectroscopy  Kurihara, T., H. Kobayashi, K. Kubodera and T. Kaino, x~3~ evaluation for the molecular  crystals of 4- (N,N-diethylamino )-4  -nitrostilbene (DEANS)  Kuvshinsky, N.G., N.A. Davidenko, V.V. Reshetnyak, LI. Savransky and V.L. Sheptun,  The influence of radical-anion electron density distribution on the dissociation effi-  ciency of a bound electron hole pair in carbazole-containing semiconductors  Kuzmin, V.A., see P.P. Levin  Kvaran, A., see A.J. Yencha    Labastie, P., see G.-H. Jeung  Laermer, F., see M. Wiechmann  Langhoff, SR., see C.W. Bauschlicher Jr.  Langkilde, F.W., R. Wilbrandt, F. Negri and G. Orlandi, Time-resolved resonance Raman  spectra of trans- and cis-stilbene in the lowest excited triplet state  Laroche, C., see E. Alsac  Lazzeretti, P., see P.W. Fowler  Lebed, I.V., Equations of pair distribution functions  Leenders, R., P. Bastiaens, R. Lunsche, A. yam Hock and A.JW.G. Visser, Rotational res-  olution of methyl-group substitution and anisotropic rotation of flavins as revealed by  picosecond-resolved fluorescence depolarization  Lemaire, E., see E. Alsac  Levin, P.P. and V.A. Kuzmin, Spin orbit coupling and paramagnetic relaxation in mied-  Iizcd triplet radical pairs. Determination of relaxation parameters from magnetic field  dependences of the decay kinetics  Lewerenz, M., see H. Hollenstein  Leyte, J.C., Some solutions of the Bloch equations  Lianos, P., see G. Duportail  Lin, S.H., see B. Fain  Lin, T.-S., see A. Henstra  Lopes de Magalhaes, A. and M.J. Ramos, Calculation of hyperfine coupling constants of  muonated radicals  Lunsche, R., see R. Leenders  Lutz, H.O., see G. Gantefdr    Mahrt, R.F. and H. Bassier, Vibronic hole-burning in acene-doped MTHF glasses  Majerz, 1., see J. Kalenik  Malarski, Z., see J. Kalenik  Manthe, U., see H.-D. Meyer  Manz, J., see W. Jakubeiz  Martinez, M.T., see M. Brouard  Maruyama, K., see A. Osuka  Mayer, C., G. Grobner, K. Muller, K. Weisz and G. Kothe, Orientation-dependent deu-  teron spin lattice relaxation times in bilayer membranes: characterization of the overall  lipid motion   165 (1990) 171   165 (1990) 513   165 (1990) 417   165 (1990) 171   165 (1990) 323   165 (1990) 302   165 (1990) 283   165 (1990) 494   165 (1990) 28   165 (1990) 272   165 (1990) 66   165 (1990) 277   165 (1990) 79   165 (1990) 226      165 (1990) 315  165 (1990) 277   165 (1990) 302   165 (1990) 175   165 (1990) 213   165 (1990) 35   165 (1990) 229   165 (1990) 6    165 (1990) 528  165 (1990) 315  165 (1990) 293  165  165  165  165  165  165  165   (1990) 125   (1990) 15   (1990) 15   (1990) 73   (1990) 100   (1990) 423   (1990) 392  165 (1990) 155  559  Volume 165, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 February 1990  McCluskey, M., see Z. Mielke  McKee, M.L., A theoretical study of (N2O)t, (CO2)t and N,O~CO,. Comparison of the  two-center three-electron bond and the ion dipole complex  Mehring, M., see S. Zhang  Meiwes-Broer, K.H., see G. Gantefar  Merkt, F. and T.P. Softley, Resonance-enhanced sum-frequency generation of XUV ra-  diation in CO  Meyer, H.-D., U. Manthe and L.S. Cederbaum, The multi-configurational time-dependent  Hartree approach  Mielke, Z., M. McCluskey and L. Andrews, Matrix reactions of P2 and 03 molecules  Mime, C.J., see M. Brouard  Miyawaki, J., T. Tsuchizawa, K. Yamanouchi and S. Tsuchiya, Spin orbit state distribu-  tion of atomic oxygen ( P  produced by photodissociation of nitrogen dioxide  Mohn, Yu.N., see V.0. Saik  Moran, G., see E. Krausz  Morozoy, V.A., see A.I. Burshtein  Muta, F., see J.J. Novoa  Mougenot, P. and M. Dupuis, Electronic structure of hydroxyl-vinoxy radical HOCHCHO  Muller, K., see C. Mayer  Murakami, A., see T. Hirano    Nagakura, S., see Y. Tanimoto  Nakagaki, R., see Y. Tanimoto  Nakagawa, N., see T. Hirano  Nedelec, O. and M. Giroud, Temperature dependence of the Hgt(63P,) quenching cross-  section for collision with H2 or D2  Negri, F., see F.W. Langkilde  Neilson, G.W., see P.M.N. Gulhidge  Neumann, M., see H.H. Graen  Nivellini, G.D., see J.L. Duncan  Noga, J., see R.J. Bartlett  Nomura, 0., see T. Hirano  Norvez, S. and M. Barzoukas, Nonlinear optical properties of triptycene derivatives  Novoa, J.J., F. Mota and F. Arnau, A full-Cl analysis of the single- and multi-reference  Moller Plesset methods for the computation of electron affinities    Okabe, N., T. Ikeyama and T. Azumi, Spin-sublevel properties of the  te triplet state of  2,2 -bipyridine. Is the out-of-plane component most emissive?  Qkazaki, M.,see Y. Tanimoto  Ondrechen, M.J., see S. Gozashti  Orlandi, G., see F.W. Langkilde  Osa, T., see H. Konami  Osuka, A., K. Maruyama, I. Yamazaki and N. Tamai, Singlet excitation energy transfer in  conformationally restricted zinc free-base hybrid diporphyrins    Partridge, H., see C.W. Bauschhicher Jr.  Partridge, R., see S. Besley  165 (1990) 146    165 (1990) 265  165 (1990) 386  165 (1990) 293    165 (1990) 477    165 (1990) 73  165 (1990) 146  165 (1990) 423    165 (1990) 168  165 (1990) 142  165 (1990) 401  165 (1990) 432  165 (1990) 503  165 (1990) 87  165 (1990) 155  165 (1990) 374    165 (1990) 184  165 (1990) 184  165 (1990) 374    165 (1990) 329  165 (1990) 66  165 (1990) 457  165 (1990) 137  165 (1990) 362  165 (1990) 513  165 (1990) 374  165 (1990) 41    165 (1990) 503      165 (1990) 24  165 (1990) 184  165 (1990) 208  165 (1990) 66  165 (1990) 397    165 (1990) 392    165 (1990) 272  165 (1990) 120  560  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 February 1990  Volume 165, number 6  Pei, C., see K. Chen  Peng, B., see C. Wang  Phillips, L.F., Collision-theory calculations for reactions of atomic oxygen with OH, ChO,  CH, NO2 and PH,  Pope, M., see M. Zielinski  Port, H., see M. Wiechmann  Pratt, S.T., P.M. Dehmer and J.L. Dehmer, Two-photon spectroscopy of autoionizing states  of Xe, near threshold   165 (1990) 523  165 (1990) 19   165 (1990) 545   165 (1990) 297   165 (1990) 28   165 (1990) 131   165 (1990) 175    165 (1990) 528  165 (1990) 323   165 (1990) 401   165 (1990) 107   165 (1990) 501  165 (1990) 429  Quack, M., see H. Hollenstein  Ramos, M.J., see A. Lopes de Magalhaes  Reshetnyak, V.V., see N.G. Kuvshinsky  Riesen, H., see E. Krausz  Robert, .J.B., see A.L. Barra  Rosi, M., see C.W. Bauschlicher Jr.  Rosmus, P., see G. Chambaud  Saik, V.0., 0.A. Anisimov, A.V. Koptyug and Yu.N. Mohn, Quantum beats in singlet trip-  let transitions of radical pairs induced by a radio-frequency field  Saito, K., K. Adachi, M. Watanabe, K. Shimofuji and A. Imamura, The thermal unimo-  hecular decomposition of 3,4-dihydro-2H-pyran behind reflected shock waves  Savransky, L.I., see N.G. Kuvshinsky  Schaefer III, H.F., see I.L. Alberts  Schaefer III, H.F., see R.S. Grey  Schirato, B.S., K.W. Herwig, P.E. Sokol and J.W. White, Deep inelastic neutron scattering  from chemisorbed hydrogen in potassium intercalated graphite  Schmidt, J., see A. Henstra  Schmitt, F.-J. and W. Knoll, Epitaxial growth of two-dimensional cyanine dye single crys-  tals by adsorption at a pre-conditioned fatty acid monolayer  Schreier, H.-J., see W. Jakubetz  Sekino, H., see Y. Ishikawa  Sekino, H., see Y. Ishikawa  Sension, R.J., see R.J. Brudzynski  Sheptun, V.L., see N.G. Kuvshinsky  Shida, T., see H. Kawashima  Shimofuji, K., see K. Saito  Siekmann, H.R., see G. Gantefdr  Silbey, R. and H.P. Trommsdorff, Two-phonon relaxation in tunneling systems: an anom-  alous energy gap dependence  Simons, J.P., see M. Brouard  Slavejkov, A.G. and A. Fontijn, HTFFR kinetics studies of the reactions of AIC1 and BC1  with HCI at high temperatures  Sluis, K.M. and E.A. Gislason, A variational procedure to estimate resonance energies and  widths using square-integrable functions  Sobczyk, L., see J. Kalenik  Softley, T.P., see F. Merkt  165 (1990) 142  165  165  165  165  (1990) 383  (1990) 323  (1990) 250  (1990) 257  165 (1990) 453  165 (1990) 6  165  165  165  165  165  165  165  165  165   (1990) 54   (1990) 100   (1990) 237  (1990) 243  (1990) 487   (1990) 323   (1990) 59   (1990) 383   (1990) 293  165 (1990) 540  165 (1990) 423    165 (1990) 375   165 (1990) 195   165 (1990) 15   165 (1990) 477  561  Volume 165, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  2 February 1990  Sokol, P.E., see B.S. Schirato  Spohr, E. and M. Wolfsberg, Vibrational and rotational excitation in collisions of diatomic  molecules with rigid surfaces  Sulkes, M., see C.K. Teh  Symons, M.C.R., see S. Besley    Takeshita, K., A theoretical study on the ionic states and the photoelectron spectra of di-  fluoromethane (CH,F,)  Tamai, N., see A. Osuka  Tan, K.H., see J.D. Bozek  Tanaka, K., see Y. Akiyama  Tanaka, T., see Y. Akiyama  Tanimoto, Y., A. Kita, M. Itoh, M. Okazaki, R. Nakagaki and S. Nagakura, Effects of tri-  valent lanthanide complexes on the lifetimes of methylene-ehain-linked biradicals in  magnetic fields  Teh, C,K., A. Gharavi and M. Sulkes, Lifetime measurements in jet-cooled indoles: ad-  ditional evidence for the  La state  Tellinghuisen, J. and C.S. Ewig, Ab initio studies of molecular anions stabilized in point-  charge lattices: excited electronic states of OH  Tittes, A., see E.E.B. Campbell  Trommsdorff, H.P., see R. Silbey  Tsuchiya, S., see J. Miyawaki  Tsuchizawa, T., see J. Miyawaki  Tullini, F., see J.L. Duncan    Yam Hoek, A., see R. Leenders  Van Damme, H., see E. Alsac  Vartholomu, M., see H. Heydtmann  Venanzi, M., see F.A. Giantureo  Vigoureux, J.M., see F. Depasse  Visser, A.J.W.G., see R. Leenders    Wallington, T.J., J.M. Andino and S.M. Japar, FTIR product study of the self-reaction of  CH2C1CH2O2 radicals in air at 295 K  Wallqvist, A., Polarizabhe water at a hydrophobic wall  Wambach, J., see H.H. Graen  Wang, C., J. Yue, T. Yan and B. Peng, The influence of iodide ions on the behaviour of  photoelectrons in T-grain AgBr(I) emulsions  Wang, J.-X., see M. Brouard  Wang, C., J. Yue, T. Yan and B. Peng, The influence of iodide ions on the behaviour of  photoelectrons in T-grain AgBr(I) emulsions  Wang, N., see M. Zielinski  Watanabe, M., see K. Saito  Watts, J.D., see R.J. Bartlett  Weisz, K., see C. Mayer  Wenckebach, W.Th., see A. Henstra  Wheelhouse, R.T., see S. Besley   165 (1990) 453    165 (1990) 221   165 (1990) 460   165 (1990) 120   165 (1990) 232   165 (1990) 392   165 (1990) 1   165 (1990) 335   165 (1990) 335      165 (1990) 184    165 (1990) 460    165 (1990) 355  165 (1990) 289  165 (1990) 540   165 (1990) 168  165 (1990) 168  165 (1990) 362    165 (1990) 315  165 (1990) 277  165 (1990) 379  165 (1990) 344   165 (1990) 554  165 (1990) 315      165 (1990) 189  165 (1990) 437  165 (1990) 137    165 (1990) 19  165 (1990) 423    165 (1990) 199  165 (1990) 297  165 (1990) 383  165 (1990) 513  165 (1990) 155  165 (1990) 6  165 (1990) 120  562  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LE117ERS  2 February 1990  Volume 165, number 6  White, J.W., see B.S. Schirato  Wiechmann, M., H. Port, F. Laermer, W. Frey and T. Elsaesser, Excited-state proton trans-  fer in a benzotriazole photostabilizer investigated by femtosecond spectroscopy  Wiersma, D.A., see S. de Boer  Wilbrandt, R,, see F.W. Langkilde  Wolfsberg, M., see E. Spohr  Wu, X., see S. Zhang  Wu, X.M., see S. Gozashti    Yamaji, M., Y. Hama and M. Hoshino, Photodissociation monopyridinate of chloro-  chromium(IIt) tetraphenylporphyrin in acetone. Studies on the reactive state and li-  gand exchange reaction by laser photolysis  Yamanouchi, K., see J. Miyawaki  Yamazaki, I., see A. Osuka  Yan, T., see C. Wang  Yang, D.S., see J.D. Bozek  Yencha, A.J., D.K. Kela, R.J. Donovan, A. Hopkirk and A. Kvaran, Ion pair (Br~ + Br )  formation from photodissociation of Br, near the first ionisation limit  Yue, J., see C. Wang    Zanasi, R., see P.W. Fowler  Zhang, H., see S. Zhang  Zhang, L.-T., see S. Gozashti  Zhang, S. and M. Mehring, Measurement of the effective pulse flip angle of distorted pulses  Zhang, S., X. Wu, H. Zhang and X. Wu, Quantitative measurement of rare spins in solid  state cross polarization NMR  Zhou, F., see S. Gozashti  Zielinski, M., M. Pope, N. Wang, C. Horvath and N.E. Geacintov, Photoemission from ad-  enine crystal: solvation of a pre-ionizing state   165 (1990) 453   165 (1990) 28   165 (1990) 45   165 (1990) 66   165 (1990) 221  165 (1990) 465  165 (1990) 208   165 (1990) 309   165 (1990) 168  165 (1990) 392   165 (1990) 19   165 (1990) 1    165 (1990) 283  165 (1990) 19    165 (1990) 79  165 (1990) 465   165 (1990) 208  165 (1990) 386   165 (1990) 465  165 (1990) 208    165 (1990) 297  563  .K. Teh  Symons, M.C.R., see S. Besley    Takeshita, K., A theoretical study on the ionic states and the photoelectron spectra of di-  fluoromethane (CH,F,)  Tamai, N., see A. Osuka  Tan, K.H., see J.D. Bozek  Tanaka, K., see Y. Akiyama  Tanaka, T., see Y. Akiyama  Tanimoto, Y., A. Kita, M. Itoh, M. Okazaki, R. Nakagaki and S. Nagakura, Effects of tri-  valent lanthanide complexes on the lifetimes of methylene-ehain-linked biradicals in  magnetic fields  Teh, C,K., A. Gharavi and M. Sulkes, Lifetime measuremen</xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="mis" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>9087039T</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(90)87039-T</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)87039-T</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="other" year="1990"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Author index to volume 165</ce:title>
         </head>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>