<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/0009261484802833</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(84)80283-3</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-0009261484802833</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(84)80283-3</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(84)80283-3</pii><dc:title>Author index to volume 111 </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>111</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>6</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>613</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>623</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>613-623</prism:pageRange><prism:number>6</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1984-10-16</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>16 October 1984</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1984  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:description/><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/0009261484802833" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/0009261484802833" rel="scidir"/></coredata><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20011126">2001-11-26</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20011126">2001-11-26</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2015-10-03T19:57:27</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-0009261484802833</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(84)80283-3</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>0009261484802833</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(84)80283-3</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.2</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-ONLY</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X06033</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20151005">2015-10-05T03:00:42.486765-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19841016</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1984</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1006732800">2001-11-26T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav articletitle</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>111</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>111</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>6</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>6</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 111, Issue 6</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>22</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>613</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>623</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>613</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>623</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19841016</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>16 October 1984</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1984-10-16</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1984</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>mis</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1984  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>AUTHORINDEXVOLUME111</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:refkeys/>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(84)80283-3</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>0009261484802833</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-0009261484802833</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(84)80283-3</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2015-10-05T03:00:42.486765-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1984-10-16</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-0009261484802833-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:0009261484802833/MAIN/application/pdf/32b852e66f825d5058c7288955c39b9e/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:0009261484802833/MAIN/application/pdf/32b852e66f825d5058c7288955c39b9e/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>785955</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>11</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-0009261484802833-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:0009261484802833/PREVIEW/image/png/1166f0bb333e53bcb5abf6a21ebd9fb6/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:0009261484802833/PREVIEW/image/png/1166f0bb333e53bcb5abf6a21ebd9fb6/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>53492</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>Volume 111. number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  AUTHOR INDEX TO VOLUME 111  Aaviksoo, J., A. Freiberg, S. Savikhin, G.F. Stelmakh and M.P. Tsvirko, Picosecond fluorescence  study of the lifetimes of metalloporphyrin SJ and S^ states  Abraham, B.M., see M. Prakash  Abrahmsen, L-, see P. Politzer  Abu-Zeid, M.E., see K- Razi Naqvi  Adam, M.Y., see S- Svensson  Adili, M.S., see K. Razi Naqvi  Akimoto, H., see H. Bandow  Akiyama, S-, see H. Bandow  Almlof.J., see H.P- Luthi  Aniirav, A., see E. Kolodney  Andersson, D-, B. Kasemo and L. Wallden, Surface chemiluminescence spectrum from the  reaction of chlorine with potassium films  Andersson, S-, see M. Persson  Arita, H., see T. Fujii  Ashfold, M.N.R., R.N. Dixon and RJ- Stickland, Multiphoton ionisation detection of PH (PD)  radicals in their b ^S"1" electronic state  Balzani, V., see M. Maestri  Bandow, H., H. Akimoto, S. Akiyama and T. Tezuka, Photolysis ofasym-NSC&gt;4 (ONONO,)  isolated in an argon matrix at 11 K  Baronavski, A.P., see B-A- Waite  Bates, D.R., lon—dipole collisions: ADO treatment  Bell, S- and E.R. McNee, Near-IR electronic absorption spectrum ofONCN  Belser, P., see M. Maestri  Bersuker, LB., see S.O. Borshch  Bhattacharyya, K. and D. Mukherjee, Some aspects of the convergence behaviour of the  Brillouin—Wigner perturbation scheme  Bissonnette, M. and D. Vocelle, Interactions ofcarboxylic acids with all-trans-retinylidene  tert-butylamine  Bitto, H., see J. Muhlbach  Boens, N., M. van den Zegel and F.C. de Schryver, Picosecond lifetime determination of the  second excited singlet state ofxanthione in solution  Bondybey, V.E. and J.H. English, Laser-induced fluorescence of the calcium dimerin supersonic  jet: the red spectrum ofCa^  Bondybey, V.E., see M. Rasanen  Boog, C-C., see M.A. van Dijk  Borshch, S.O., I.N. Kotov and I.B. Bersuker, A vibronic model for exchange-coupled mixed-  valence dimers  Broquier, M. and A. Picard-Bersellini, Overlapping effects and collisional narrowing in  rotational doublets ofOCS in the infrared  113 (1984)275  111 (1984)395  111(1984) 75  111 (1984)279  [II (1984)574  111 (1984)279  111 (1984)496  111 (1984)496  111(1984)  1  111 (1984)366  111 (1984)593  III (1984)597  111 (1984)350  111 (1984)226  111 (1984)514  1 (1984)496  1 (1984)544  1 1(1984)428  1(1984)105  1 (1984)514  1 (1984) 264  111 (1984)421  111 (1984)506  111 (1984)288  111 (1984)340  111(1984)195  111 (1984)515  111 (1984)571  111 (1984)264  111 (1984)602  613  Volume 111, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  Caprace, G., see R. Locht  Carberry, J.J., see G.C. Kuczynski  Carlier, M., see P. Devolder  Casteleijn, G.. see M.A. van Dijk  Castleman Jr., A.W., see P.D. Dao  Castleman Jr., A.W., see F-J. Schelling  Castleman Jr., A.W., see B.L. Upschulte  Chang, T., H. Kim and H. Yu, Spacial harmonic analysis of transient optical grating  Cliattaraj, P.K., see S. Haq  Chawla, G-K., see H.J. Vedder  Chimori, T., see Y. Hidaka  Chow, D.K., Calculation of diffusion coefficients of relatively large particles from Mie  scattering spectra  Cohen.M. and S. Kais, Scaling, renormalisation and accuracy of perturbation calculations,  Chem. Phys. Letters 105 (1984) 295. Erratum  Cool, T.A. and PJ.H. Tjossem, Direct observations ofchemi-ionization in hydrocarbon flames  enhanced by laser excited CH*(A2^) and CH*(B 2S-)  Cooper, I.L. and J.A. Harrison, The self-consistent determination of ion-pair distribution  functions within the Debye—Huckel framework  Cremasclii, P. and J.L. Whitten, Ti—H interactions in small metal clusters  Dao, P.D., S. Morgan and A.W. Castleman Jr., Resonance-enhanced multiphoton ionization  of van der Waals molecules: studies of spectroscopic shifts ofphenyl acetylene clustered  witli molecules and atoms  Davidson, E.R. and K. Morokuma, On the proton field gradient of ice Ih  Davis. C.L. and H.J. Monkhorst, Accurate Hartree—Fock wavefunctions without exponent  optimization. Limits to accuracy with constraints on orbitais near nuclei  Deb, B.M., see S. Haq  Dedieu, A., see S. Nakamura  Delimer, J.L., sec E.D. Poliakoff  De Jongh, LJ., see B. van der Griendt  DeLeon, R.L. and J.S. Muenter, Vibrational relaxation of linear molecules in a nozzle  expansion  Delgado-Barrio, G., see F.A. Gianturco  De Martino, A., R- Frey and F. Pradere, Double resonance observation of the (3v^, A^) state  of methane  DC Menorval. L.C.. see T. Ito  Derouard.J. and N. Sadeghi, Resonant excitation of Li atoms to the (2 2P) state by collisions  with Li^(Al^, u',J') molecules  De Schryver, P.C., see N. Boens  Dcspres, A., V. Lcjeune, E. Migirdicyan and W. Siebrand, Site-selected fluorescence and  fluorescence-excitation spectra ofo-durylene-Aj-, and -dy^ in M-hexane at 5—10K  Destombes, J.L., see B. Lemoine  Devolder, P., M. Carlier, J.F. Pauwels and L.R. Sochet, Rate constant for the reaction of  OH with nitric acid: a new investigation by discharge flow resonance fluorescence  Dewar. M.J.S. and J.J .P. Stewart, A new procedure for calculating molecular polarizabilities;  applications using MNDO  Distler, D., see G. Hohlneicher  111 (1984)560  111 (1984)445  111(1984) 94  111 (1984)571  111(1984) 38  111 (1984) 47  111 (1984)389  111 (1984) 64  111(1984) 79  111(1984)303  111(1984) 181  111(1984) 69  111(1984)185  111(1984) 82  111 (1984)487  11 1 (1984)215  11  11  (1984) 38  (1984)  7  11 (1984)526  11 (1984) 79  11 (1984)243  II (1984)128  111(1984)161  III (1984)147  111 (1984)399  111(1984) 113  111(1984)271  111 (1984)353  111 (1984)340  111(1984)201  111(1984)284  111(1984) 94  111(1984)416  111 (1984)151  614  Volume 111, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  Dixon, R.N., see M.N.R. Ashfold  Domcke, W., see J. Senekowitsch  Dubs, M-, see J. Muhlbach  Dunlap, B.I;, see B.A. Waite  Dutta, P., see M. Prakash  Dyke, J.M., A.R. Ellis, N. Jonathan, N. Keddar and A. Morris, Observation of the CH^OH  radical in the gas phase by vacuum ultraviolet photoelectron spectroscopy  Dyksira, C.E., Vibrational and rotational transition frequencies and the stability of the  HeHNCH-1- ion  Eberhardt, W., see V. Murgai  Eiber, R., see E. Kolodney  Ellis, A.R., see J.M. Dyke  English, J.H., see V.E. Bondybey  Esser, M., Role of time-reversal symmetry in the graphical representation of Gelfand basis  sets within the relativistic CI approach  Fsgri Jr., K., see H.P. Lutlii  Feng, W.L-, 0. Novaro and J. Garci'a-Prieto, A comparative study of three-body terms in  ozone and thiozone  Fenzke, D., D. Freude, T. Frohlich and J. Haase, NMR intensity measurements of half-integer  quadrupole nuclei  Field, R.W. see HJ- Vedder  Figari, G., see V. Magnasco  Fink, E.H., see H. Kruse  Fischer, S.F., see E.W. Knapp  Fraissard, J.P., see T. Ito  Freiberg, A., see J. Aaviksoo  Frenking, G., CC triple-bond stabilization in three-niembered ring compounds: boriryne,  dilithiumcyclopropyne and berylliryne  Freude, D., see D. Fenzke  Freund, H.-J., see G. Hohlneicher  Frey, R., see A. de Martino  Frohlich, T-, see D. Fenzke  Fujii, T., S- Suzuki and H. Arita, The influence of molecular conformation on electronic  relaxation processes. Multiple phosphorescence spectra ofw-terphenyl  Gao, Y., see T. Lopez-Rfos  Garci'a-Prieto, J., see W.L. Feng  Gerber, R.B-, see E. Kolodney  Gerslen, J.I., see N. Liver  Gianturco, F.A., A. Palma, P. Villarreal and G. DeIgado-Ban-io, Rotational predissociation  in polar systems: the He-HF example  Goncharov, V.A. and I.V. Ovchinnikov, On the study of the dynamical behaviour of  dielectrics by thermal-noise correlation analysis  German, A.A., I. Hamblett and N.-H. Jensen, Reversible triplet energy transfer between  neo-alloocimene and anthracene  Gotberg, K.E., R.M. Miller and D.S. Tinti, Zero- and low-sseld ODMR spectra of the triplet  state of N02 in NaHCO^  111(1984)226  111 (1984)211  111(1984)288  111(1984)544  111 (1984)395  111 (1984)207  111 (1984)405  111(1984)157  111 (1984)366  111(1984)207  111(1984) 195  111 (1984) 58  111(1984)  1  111 (1984)297  111(1984) 171  11 (1984)303  11 (1984)539  11 (1984)100  11 (1984)481  II (1984)271  111(1984)275  111(1984) 529  III (1984) 171  111 (1984) 151  111(1984)113  111(1984)171  111 (1984)350  111 (1984)249  111(1984)297  111 (1984)366  111 (1984)449  111 (1984)399  111 (1984)521  111 (1984)293  111(1984)578  615  Volume 111. number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  Gottfried, N.H., A. Seilnieier and W. Kaiser, Transient internal temperature of anthracene  after picosecond infrared excitation  Grabowski, A., see A. Mordziriski  G rover, J.R., see E.A. Walter  Guerrier, E., see T. Ito  Gurney, B.A., see L.J. Richter  Gutz, l.G.R., see J.C. Rubim  Haase, J.. see D. Fenzke  Haasnool, J.H., see B. van der Griendt  Hamblett, I., see A.A. German  Handy, N.C.,see P.J. Knowles  Haq, S-, P.K. Chatiaraj and B.M. Deb, A new form for tlie kinetic energy-density functional  for many-electron systems  Harrison, J.A., see I.L. Cooper  liatano, Y., see K. Hirao  Heiberg, A-, see H.P. Luthi  Helvajian, H., see B.A. Waite  Hiclaka, Y., T. Chimori, S. Shiba and M. Suga, Decyclization ofcyclohexene in shock waves  Hilinski, E.F., K.D. Straub and P.M. Rentzepis, Solvent effects on the relaxation mechanism  ofCu(II) protoporphyrin  Hirao, K. and Y. Hatano, Full CI and SAC CI calculations for ionized states, electron-  attached states and triplet excited states ofH.,0  Ho, W., see L.J. Richter  Holilneicher, G.,D. Distier, M. Muller and H.-J. Freund, Identification of shake-up satellites  in valence pliotoelectron spectra of organic compounds by comparison with electronic  absorption spectra of radical cations. Case study: octafluoronaplithalene  Honda, K., see K. Iioh                                                           .  Hrabanski, R., EPR ofMn24' in single crystals of calcium liexuchlurustannate liexaliydrate  Hsu, Y.-C., M.A. Smith and S.C. Wallace, The predissociation dynamics of the A'A" state  ofHCNandDCN  Huber, J.R., see J. Muhlbach  Hulbert, S.L., see V. Murgai  Husson, L.P.J., see H.P.H. Tliijssen  Ito, T., L.C. de Menorval, E. Guerrier and J.P. Fraissard, NMR study of ^Xe adsorbed on  L, Z and ZDM zeolites  Itoli. K., M. Nakao and K. Honda, A new aspect on the mechanism of dye sensitization.  Donor concentration dependence of the photocurrent  I loll, M., see K. Tokumura  iwasaki, M., K. Toriyama and K. Nunome, ESR observation ofisotopic preference in Static  distortions of Jalm—Teller active radical cations: partially deuterated ethane radical  cations in SFg at 4 K  Jcnsen, N.-H.,  Jenscn, N.-H.,  Jensen. N.-H.,  Johnson, P.D.  see R. Wilbrandt  see A.A. Gorman  see F.W. Langkilde  , see V. Murgai  111 (1984)326  111(1984)383  111(1984)190  111 (1984)271  111 (1984)185  111(1984)117  111(1984) 171  111(1984) 161  11 (1984)293  11 (1984)315  11(1984) 79  11(1984)487  11 (1984)533  11(1984)  1  11 (1984)544  11(1984) 181  111 (1984)333  111 (1984)533  111(1984)185  111(1984)151  111 (1984)492  111 (1984)607  111 (1984)219  111 (1984)288  111(1984)157  111(1984) 11  111 (1984)271  111 (1984)492  111 (1984)379  111 (1984)309  111(1984)123  111(1984)293  111 (1984)372  111 (1984) 157  616  Volume 111. number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  Jolly, J., see A. Plain  Jonathan, N., see J.M. Dyke  J0rgensen, C.K-, see R. Reisfeld  Kais, S-, see M. Cohen  Kaiser, W-, see N.H. Gottfried  Kajii, Y., K. Obi, I. Tanaka and S. Tobita, Isotope effects on radiationless transitions from the  lowest excited singlet state of tetraphenylporphin  Kappes, M.M., K.O. Marti, P- Radi, M. Schar and E. Schumacher, Resonant two-photon  ionization of LiNa. Observation and preliminary characterization of five new singlet  states, Chein. Phys. Letters 107 (1984) 6. Erratum  Karlsson, P.-A., see M. Persson  Kasemo, B-, see D. Andersson  Kawazoe, H., see M. Shiotani  Keddar, N., see J.M. Dyke  Keesee, R.G., see B.L. Upschulte  Ketterson, J.B., see M. Prakash  Kirn, H., see T. Chang  Kiniura, K., see S. Tomoda  Kisilev, A., see R. Reisfeld  Knapp, E.W., P.O.J. Scherer and S.F. Fischer, On the lineshapes ofvibronically resolved  molecular aggregate spectra- Application to pseudoisocyanin (PIC)  Knowles, P.J. and N.C. Handy, A new determinant-based full configuration interaction method  Koga, Y., A SAXS study of concentration fluctuations in i-butanol— water system  Kolodney, E., A. Amirav, R. Eiber and R.B. Gerber, Energy transfer and dissociation in  collisions ofl^ with MgO(lOO)  Konowalow.D.D.and L.B. Ratcliff, The vibrational energy spectrum of the 2 ^^ state of Li^  Kotov, I.N., see S.O. Borshch  Kruse, H., R. Winter, E.H. Fink, J. Wildt and F- Zabel, b ^ emissions from group V-VII  diatomic molecules, b O"1' -* X( O'1", X-, 1 band systems ol'AsCI and AsBr  Kuczynski, G.C. and J.J. Carberry, A model of surface enrichment in bimetallic alloys  Kuroda, H., see K. Yakushi  Kwok. H.S-, see P. Mukhcrjee  Lablanquie, P., see S. Svensson  Langkilde. F.W., see R. Wilbrandt  Langkilde, F.W., R. Wilbrandt and N.-H. Jensen, Time-resolved absorption and resonance  Raman spectra of the lowest excited triplet state ofall-trans-l,2,5-heptatriene  Laporte, P., see R- Reiniger  Laurence, P.R., see P. Politzer  Legon, A.C. and L.C. Willoughby. First-order Stark effect and electric dipole moment of  HgP—HC^N by pulsed-nozzle Fourier-transform microwave spectroscopy  Lejeune, V., see A. Despres  Lemoine, B. and J.L. Destombes, Infrared spectroscopy of molecular ions m a magnetically  confined glow discharge  Lendzian, F., K. Mobius, M. Plato, U.H. Smith, M.C- Thurnauer and W. Lubitz, ^Mg  ENDOR and TRIPLE resonance in liquid solution of the bacteriochlorophyll a cation  and anion radicals  111(1984)133  111 (1984)207  111(1984) 19  111(1984) 185  111 (1984)326  111(1984)347  111(1984)514  111 (1984)597  111(1984) 593  111 (1984)254  111 (1984)207  111 (1984)389  111 (1984)395  111(1984) 64  111(i984) 434  111(1984) 19  111(1984)481  111 (1984)315  111 (1984)176  111 (1984)366  111 (1984)413  111 (1984)264  111(1984)100  111 (1984)445  111(1984) 165  111(1984) 33  111 (1984)574  111 (1984) 123  111(1984)372  111 (1984)549  111(1984) 75  111 (1934)566  111 (1984)201  lll(l-'l84)284  111 (1984)583  617  Volume 111. number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  Leroi, C.E., see E.D. Poliakoff  Le Thanh. H. and D. Vocelle, Inicraction of'phenylaied carboxylic acids with a conjugated  inline in a study of a model ofrhodopsin  Leugers, M.A., see C.J. Seliskar  Levine, Y.K., see M.A. van Dijk  Linderberg, J., see M. Mishra  Liver, N-, A. Nitzan and J.I. Gersien, Local fields in cavity sites of rough dielectric surfaces  Loclil, R., G. Caprace and J. Momigny,The dissociative ionization of nitrous oxide.  A comparison between electroionization and Hel and Nel photoionization  Lopez-Ribs, T., Y. Gao and G. Vuye, Influence ofAl submonolayers on surface-enhanced  Raman scattering of pyridine on Ag surfaces  Lorincz, A., F.A- Novak and S.A. Rice, Relaxation of large molecules following ultrafast  excitation  Lubitz, W., see F. Lendzian  Luthi, H.P-, P.E.M. Siegbahn, J- Almlof, K. Faegri Jr. and A. Heiberg, The effect of electron  correlation on the metal—ligand bond in ferrocene  Maestri, M., D. Sandrini, V. Balzani, P. Belser and A. von Zelewsky, Rates of virtually  self-exchange energy transfer processes of ruthenium(II) polypyridine complexes,  Chein. Phys. Letters 110 (1984) 611. Erratum  Magnasco, V., see G.F. MUSSO  Magnasco, V. and G. Figaro, Polarizabilities and dispersion coefficients of Ca and Sr atoms  Malmquist, P.-A., see S. Svensson  Marti, K.O., see M.M. Kappes  McCabe. R.W. and D.F. McCready, Formaldehyde oxidation on Pt: kinetic evidence for  adsorbed carbon monoxide intermediate  McCready. D.F., see R.W. McCabe  McNee, E.R., see S. Bell  Migirdicyan, E., see A. Despres  Miller, R.M., see K.E. Gotberg  Mishra, M,, J. Linderberg and Y. Ohrn, Characterization ofadiabatic states in triatomic  collisions  Mobius, K., see F. Lendzian  Momigny,J., see R. Locht  Monkhorst, HJ., see C.L. Davis  Mordzinski, A-, A. Grabowska and K. Teuchner, Mechanism of excited-state proion transfer  in "double" benzoxazoles: bis-2,5-(2-benzoxazolyl)hydroquinone  Morgan, S., see P.D. Dao  Morin, P., see S. Svensson  Morokuma, K„ see E.R. Davidson  Morris, A., see J.M. Dyke  Morion, J.R. and K.F. Preston, The reaction ofH atoms witli Ni(CO)4: EPR spectrum of  (DC^NiCHO in krypton  Muenter, J.S., see R.L. DeLeon  Millilbach, J., M. Dubs, H. Bitto and J.R. Huber, Hyperfine quantum beat spectroscopy of  ;i polyatomic molecule in a weak magnetic field with polarized light  Muklierjee, D., see K. Bhattacharyya  Mukherjee, P. and H.S. Kwok, Coherent inultiphoton excitation ofSFg by picosecond  laser pulses  16 November 1984  111(1984)128  111 (1984)501  111 (1984)141  111 (1984)571  111 (1984)439  111 (1984)449  111(1984)560  111 (1984)249  111 (1984)322  111 (1984)583  111(1984)  1  111 (1984)514  111 (1984)468  111(1984)539  111 (1984)574  111 (1984)514  111(1984) 89  111(1984) 89  111(1984)105  111 (1984)201  111(1984)578  111(1984)439  111 (1984)583  111 (1984)560  111(1984)526  111 (1984)383  111(1984) 38  111 (1984)574  111(1984) 7  111 (1984)207  111 (1984)611  111 (1984)147  111(1984)288  111 (1984)421  111(1984) 33  618  Volume 111, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  Muller, M., see G. Hohlneicher  Murgai, V., S.L. Hulbert, P.D. Johnson, M. Strongin and W. Eberhardt, Photon energy  dependent branching ratios of the inner valence satellites in the photoemission of  solid ethylene  MUSSO, G.F. and V. Magnasco, On the importance ofgeminal effects in rotational barriers  Nagashima, U., see H. Shinohara  Nakamura, S. and A. Dedieu, Theoretical investigation of the hydride migration to  coordinated carbon monoxide  Nakao, M., see K. Itoh  Nenner, I., see S. Svensson  Newman, J-K., see E.A. Walter  Nishi. N., see H. Shinohara  Nitzan, A., see N. Liver  Novak, F.A., see A. Lorincz  Novaro, 0., see W.L. Feng  Nunome, K., see M. Iwasaki  Obi. K.. see H. Ohtoshi  Obi, K., see K. Kajii  Ohrn, Y., see M- Mishra  Ohtoshi, H., K. Tsukiyama, A. Yanagibori, K. Shibuya, K. Obi and K. Tanaka, Laser  induced fluorescence of NCS m the gas phase  Ovchinnikov, I.V., see V.A. Goncharov  Palma, A., see F.A. Gianturco  Parr, A.C., see E.D- Poliakoff  Parr. T., see G. Radhakrishnan  Pauluth, M. and G- Rotzoll, Molecular-beam study of the K + CFgI reaction at colision  energies up to 1.14 eV (c-m.)  Pauwels, J.F., see P. Devolder  Persson, M., S. Andersson and P.-A. Karlsson, Dipole active displacements of ordered  adsorbate layers on metal surfaces  Pettinger, B., The role of energy transfer processes in surface (enhanced) inelastic light  scattering, Chem. Phys. Letters 110 (1984) 576. Erratum  Picard-Bersellini, A., see M. Broquier  Pines, A., see R. Tycko  Pipek, J., Approximate upper bound for two-electron integrals of molecular orbitais  Plain, A. and J. Jolly, Quenching rate constants for N?(B 2^, v = 0,1,2) with N3 and Ne  Plato, M., see F. Lendzian  Poliakoff, E.D., J.L. Dehmer, A.C. Parr and C.E. Leroi, Fluorescence excitation studies of  molecular photoionization in external electric fields  Politzer, P., P.R. Laurence, L. Abrahmsen, B.A. Zilles and P. Sjoberg, The aromatic C-NO^  bond as a site for nucleophilic attack  Pollak, E., Equivalence of vibrational sudden and vibrational adiabatic classical transition  state theory                     -  Pradere, F., see A. de Martino  16 November 1984  111(1984) 151  111(1984) 157  111(1984)468  111(1984)511  111(1984)243  111(1984)492  111 (1984)574  111(1984) 190  111 (1984)511  111(1984)449  111 (1984)322  111 (1984)297  111 (1984)309  111(1984)136  111 (1984)347  111(1984)439  111(1984) 136  111 (1984)521  111 (1984)399  111(1984) 128  111(1984) 25  111(1984)238  111(1984) 94  111 (1984)597  111(1984)514  111(1984)602  111(1984)462  111(1984)430  111(1984) 133  111(1984)583  111(1984) 128  111(1984) 75  111 (1984)473  111(1984) 113  619  Volume 111. number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  Prakash, M., P. Dutta, J.B. Ketterson and B.M. Abraham, X-ray diffraction study of the  in-plane structure of an organic multilayer ("Langmuir-Blodgetf) film  Preston, K.F., see J.R. Morton  Radhakrishnan, G., T. Parr and C. Wittig, Multiple product channels in the collision-free  UV pliotodissociation of 2-nitropropane  Radi, P., see M.M. Kappes  Riisaiien. M. and V.E. Bondybey, Gauche- and Irans-« buianc and their IR-induced  in tercon version in solid neon  Ratciiff, L.B., see D.D. Konowalow  Razi Naqvi, K-, M.S. Adili and M.E. Abu-Zeid, Photoacoustic spectroscopy of naphthalene  and 2-naphthol  Reedijk, J-, see B. van der Griendt  Reiniger, R., V. Saile, P. Laporte and I.T- Steinberger, Enhancement and quenching of  phoioionizaiion in rare gas mixtures  Reisfeld, R., A. Kisilev and C.K. J^rgensen, Luminescence of manganese(II) in 24 phosphate  glasses  Rentzepis, P.M., see E.F. Hilinski  Rice, S.A., see A. Lorincz  Richter, L.J., B.A. Gurney, J.S- Villarrubia and W. Ho. Temperature programmed electron  energy loss spectroscopy: kinetics ofCH30H decomposition on Ni(l 10)  Rohrer, F. and F. Stuhl, Nr^a^-*- X3^;") emission from the gas-phase photolysis ofHNg  Rosmus, P., see J. Senekowitsch  Roizoll, G., see M. Pauluth  Rubim, J.C., I.G.R. Gutz and 0. Sala, Surface-enhanced Raman scattering (SERS) and  fluorescence spectra from mixed copper(i)/pyridine/iodide complexes on a copper  electrode  Sadeghi, N-, see J. Derouard  Saile, V., see R. Reininger  Sala, 0., see J.C. Rubim  Sandrini, D., see M. Maestri  Savikhin, S-, see J. Aaviksoo  Sawamura, S-, K. Suzuki and Y. Taniguchi, Effect of pressure on the conformational  equilibrium of 2-haloethanol in carbon disulfide  Schar. M-, see M.M. Kappes  Schelling, F.J. and A.W. Castleman Jr., A classicai trajectory study of the angular momentum  coupling model. The influence ofanisotropic polarizability on the lifetimes of complexes  formed in ion—molecule collisions  Schelling, FJ., see B.L. Upscliulte  Scherer, P.O.J., see E.W. Knapp  Schumacher, E., see M.M. Kappes  Seilmeier, A., see N.H. Gottfried  Seliskar, C.J. and M.A. Leugers, Identification oftorsional transitions in the 5613 A origin  band of methyl telrazine  Senekowitsch, J., P. Rosmus, W. Domcke and H.-J. Werner, An accurate potential energy  function of the H^ ion at large internuclear distances  Shiba, S., see Y. Hidaka  111 (1984)395  111 (1984)611  111(1984) 25  111 (1984)514  111 (1984)515  111 (1984)413  111 (1984) 279  111 (1984) 161  111 (1984)549  111(1984) 19  111 (1984)333  111 (1984)322  111(1984) 185  111(1984)234  111 (1984)211  111 (1984)238  111(1984)117  111 (1984)353  111 (1984)549  111(1984) 117  111 (1984)514  111 (1984)275  111 (1984)589  111 (1984)514  111 (1984) 47  111 (1984)389  111 (1984)481  111 (1984)514  111 (1984)326  111 (1984) 141  111 (1984)211  111(1984)181  620  Volume 111, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  'JSlnbuya, K.. see H. Ohtoslii  Shin, H.K., Role of frequency clianges in vibrational energy transfer  Sliinohara, H., U. Nagashima and N. Nishi, Mass spectroscopic observation of an enhanced  structural stability of water—ammonia binary clusters at« = 20 in the series (H20)„(NH3)„, H4'  (0&lt;M +772 &lt;32)  Shiotani. M., H. Kawazoe and J. Sohina, The radical cation ofheyafluoro-l,3-butadiene:  an ESR study  Siebrand, W., see A. Despres  Siegbahn, P.E.M., see H.P. Luthi  Sjoberg, P., see P. Politzer  Smith, M.A-, see Y.-C. Hsu  Smith, U.H., see F. Lendzian  Sochet, L.R., see P. Devolder  Sohma, J., see M. Shiotani  Sondag, A.H.M., see G.H. Wegdam  Steinberger, I.T., see R. Reininger  Stelmakh, G.F., see J. Aaviksoo  Stewart, J.J.P., see M.J.S. Dewar  Stickland, R.J., see M.N.R. Ashfold  Straub, K.D., see E-F. Hilinski  Strongin, M-, see V. Murgai  Stuhl, F., see F. Rohrer  Suga, M., see Y. Hidaka  Suzuki, K-, see S- Sawaniura  Suzuki, S., see T. Fujii  Svensson, S-, P.-A. Malmquist,.M.Y. Adam, P. Lablanquie, P. Morin and I- Nenner, Electron  spectroscopy study of the 27.5 eV satellite line in acetylene excited by synchrotron  radiation  Tanaka, I-, see K. Kajii  Tanaka, K., see H. Ohtoshi  Taniguchi, Y., see S. Sawamura  Teuchner, K., see A. Mordzinski  Tezuka, T., see H. Bandow  Thijssen, H.P.H., R. van den Berg, S. Volker, J.H. van der Waals and L.P.J. Husson,  Photoacoustic spectroscopy via resonant detection of second sound m superfluid helium  Thurnauer, M.C., see F. Lendzian  Tinti, D.S., see K.E. Gotberg  Tjossem, P.J.H., see T.A. Cool  Tobita, S-, see K. Kajii  Tokumura, K., Y. Watana'oe and M. Itoh, A transient absorption and two-step laser  excitation fluorescence study of the double proton transfer of7-azaindole H-bonded  dimers in 3-methylpentane  Tomoda, S. and K. Kimura, Do we observe the "adiabatic" ionizations of the water dimer?  An interpretation of the threshold ionization energy and the nature of the ionic states  Toriyama, K., see M. Iwasaki  Tsukiyama, K., see H. Ohtoshi  Tsvirko, MJ*., see J- Aaviksoo  111(1984)136  111(1984)258  111 (1984)511  111 (1984)254  111 (1984)201  111(1984)  I  111(1984) 75  111(1984)219  111(1984)583  111(1984) 94  111 (1984)254  111 (1984)360  111 (1984)549  111 (1984)275  111 (1984)416  111(1984)226  111 (1984)333  111(1984)157  111(1984)234  111 (1984) 181  111 (1984)589  111 (1984)350  111(1984)574  111 (1984)347  111(1984)136  111 (1984)589  111(1984)383  111 (1984)496  111(1984) 11  111 (1984)583  111(1984)578  111(1984) 82  111(1984)347  111 (1984)379  111(1984)434  111(1984)309  111(1984)136  111(1984)275  621  Volume 111. number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  Tycko, R. and A. Pines, Iterative schemes for broad-band and narrow-band population  inversion in NMR  Uniansky, S.Ya., see Ch. Zuhrt  Upschulie, B.L., F.J. Schelling, R.G. Keesee and A.W. Castleman Jr., Thermochemical  properties of gas phase mixed clusters: water and sulfur dioxide with Na"1' and Cl~  Van den Ber", R., see H.P.H. Thijssen  Van den Zegri, M., see N. Boens  Van der Griendt, B-, J.H. Haasnoot, J. Reedijk and L.J- de Jongh, Evidence for a two-  dimensional Ising system from magnetic dilution studies on bis(isothiocyanato)bis( 1,2,4-  iriazole)iron(II)  Van der Waals, J.H.. see H.P.H. Thijssen  Van Dijk, M.A., C.C. Boog, G. Casteleijn and Y.K. Levine, Time domain spectroscopic  dielectric permittivity measurements on AOT/water/iso-octane  Vedder, HJ-, G.K. Chawla and R.W. Field, Observation of the quasibound energy levels and  tunnelling lifetimes in the Na;, B1 liy state  Vicharelli, P.A., Intramolecular coordinate relaxation in a Kratzer—Simons—Finlan potential  energ surface  Villarreal, P., see F.A. Gianturco  Viilarrubia.J.S-.see L.J. Richter  Vocelle, D., see H. Le Thanh  Vocelle, D., see M. Bissonnette  Volker, S„ see H.P.H. Thijssen  Von Zelewsky, A., see M. Maestri  Vuye, G-, see T. Lopez-Ribs  Waite, B.A-, H. Helvajian, B.I. Dunlap and A-P. Baronavski, Classical model studies of  dissociation following linear to bent triatomic photoexcitation  Wallace, S.C.. see Y.-C. Hsu  Wallden, L-, see D. Andersson  Walters, E.A., J.R. Grover, J.K. Newman and M.G. White, Non-statistical behavior in the  dissociative photoionization of the 1,3-butadiene/sulfur dioxide van der Waals complex  Watanabe, Y., see K. Tokumura  Wegdam, G.H. and A.H.M. Sondag, Dicke narrowing in HC1. The possible dependence of  velocity and angular momentum changing collisions  Werner, H.-J., see J. Senekowitsch  While, M.G., see E.A. Walter  Wliitten, J.L., see P. Cremaschi  Wilbrandt, R., N.-H. Jensen and F.W. Langkilde, Time-resolved resonance Raman spectrum  ofall-trans-diphenylbutadiene in the lowest excited singlet state  Wiibrandt, R., see F.W. Langkilde  Wildt, J.. see H. Kruse  Willoughby, L.C., see A.C. Legon  Winter, R., see H. Kruse  Wittig, C., see G. Radharishnan  Woodcock, L.V., Origins of shear dilaiancy and shear thickening phenomena  111 (1984)462  111 (1984)408  111 (1984)389  111(1984) 11  111(1984)340  111 (1984)161  111(1984) II  111 (1984)571  111 (1984)303  111(1984) 53  111 (1984)399  111 (1984) 185  111(1984)501  111 (1984)506  111(1984) 11  111 (1984)514  111 (1984)249  111 (1984)544  111(1984)219  111 (1984)593  111(1984)190  111 (1984)379  111(1984)360  111 (1984)211  111(1984) 190  111 (1984)215  111(1984) 123  111 (1984)372  111(1984) 100  111 (1984)566  111(1984)100  111(1984) 25  111(1984)455  622  Volume 111, number 6                    CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS                       16 November 1984  Yakushi, K. and H. Kuroda, Low-temperature reflectance spectrum or the benzidine—TCNQ  charge-transfer complex                                                             111(1984)165  Yariagibori, A., see H. Ohtoshi                                                          111(1984)136  Yu, H-, see T. Chang                                                                   111 (1984) 64  Zabel, F., see H. Kruse                                                                    111 ( 1984) 100  Zgierski, M.Z., The effect of dimerization on the resonance Raman excitation profiles of  metalloporphyrins                                                                      111(1984)553  Zilles, B.A-, see P. Politzer                                                                 111 (1984) 75  Zuhrt, Ch-, L. Zulicke and S.Ya. Umansky, Investigation of the electronically non-adiabatic  vibrational transitions Ar + OH(u = l) -&gt; Ar + OH(u =0)                                   111(1984) 408  Zulicke, L., see Ch. Zuhrt                                                                111 (1984) 408  623  434  111(1984)309  111(1984)136  111(1984)275  621  Volume 111. number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  16 November 1984  Tycko, R. and A. Pines, Iterative schemes for broad-band and narrow-band population  inversion in NMR  Uniansky, S.Ya., see Ch. Zuhrt  Upschulie, B.L., F.J. Schelling, R.G. Keesee and A.W. Castleman Jr., Thermochemical  properties of gas phase mixed clusters: water and sulfur dioxide with Na"1' and Cl~  Van den Ber", R., see H.P.H. Thijssen  Van den Zegri, M., see N. Boens  Van der Griendt, B-, J.H. Haasnoot, J. Reedijk and L.J- de Jongh, Evidence for a two-  dimensional Ising system from magnetic dilution studies on bis(isothiocyanato)bis( 1,2,4-  iriazole)iron(II)  Van der Waals, J.H.. see H.P.H. Thijssen  Van Dijk, M.A., C.C. Boog, G. Casteleijn and Y.K. Levine, Time domain spectroscopic  dielectric permittivity measurements on AOT/water/iso-octane  Vedder, HJ-, G.K. Chawla and R.W. Field, Observation of the quasibound energy levels and  tunnelling lifetimes in the Na;, B1 liy state  Vicharelli, P.A., Intramolecular coordinate relaxation in a Kratzer—Simons—Finlan potential  energ surface  Villarreal, P., see F.A. Gianturco  Viilarrubia.J.S-.see L.J. Richter  Vocelle, D., see H. Le Thanh  Vocelle, D., see M. Bissonnette  Volker, S„ see H.P.H. Thijssen  Von Zelewsky, A., see M. Maestri  Vuye, G-, see T. Lopez-Ribs  Waite, B.A-, H. Helvajian, B.I. Dunlap and A-P. Baronavski, Classical model studies of  dissociation following linear to bent triatomic photoexcitation  Wallace, S.C.. see Y.-C. Hsu  Wallden, L-, see D. Andersson  Walters, E.A., J.R. Grover, J.K. Newman and M.G. White, Non-statistical behavior in the  dissociative photoionization of the 1,3-butadiene/sulfur dioxide van der Waals complex  Watanabe, Y., see K. Tokumura  Wegdam, G.H. and A.H.M. Sondag, Dicke narrowing in HC1. The possible dependence of  velocity and angular momentum changing collisions  Werner, H.-J., see J. Senekowitsch  While, M.G., see E.A. Walter  Wliitten, J.L., see P. Cremaschi  Wilbrandt, R., N.-H. Jensen and F.W. Langkilde, Time-resolved resonance Raman spectrum  ofall-trans-diphenylbutadiene in the lowest excited singlet state  Wiibrandt, R., see F.W. Langkilde  Wildt, J.. see H. Kruse  Willoughby, L.C., see A.C. Legon  Winter, R., see H. Kruse  Wittig, C., see G. Radharishnan  Woodcock, L.V., Origins of shear dilaiancy and shear thickening phenomena  111 (1984)462  111 (1984)408  111 (1984)389  111(1984) 11  111(1984)340  111 (1984)161  111(1984) II  111 (1984)571  111 (1984)303  111(1984) 53  111 (1984)399  111 (1984) 185  111(1984)501  111 (1984)506  111(1984) 11  111 (1984)514  111 (1984)249  111 (1984)544  111(1984)219  111 (1984)593  111(1984)190  111 (1984)379  111(1984)360  111 (1984)211  111(1984) 190  111 (1984)215  111(1984) 123  111 (1984)372  111(1984) 100  111 (1984)566  111(1984)100  111(1984) 25  111(1984)455  622  Volume 111, number 6                    CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS                       16 November 1984  Yakushi, K. and H. Kuroda, Low-temperature reflectance spectrum or the benzidine—TCNQ  charge-transfer complex                                                             111(1984)165  Yariagibori,</xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="mis" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>84802833</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(84)80283-3</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(84)80283-3</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="other" year="1984"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Author index to volume 111</ce:title>
         </head>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>