<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926149085433D</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(90)85433-D</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-000926149085433D</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)85433-D</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(90)85433-D</pii><dc:title>Equations of pair distribution functions </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>165</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>2-3</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>226</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>228</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>226-228</prism:pageRange><prism:number>2-3</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1990-01-12</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>12 January 1990</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1990 Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:creator>Lebed, I.V.</dc:creator><dc:description>
               Abstract
               
                  A description of a rarefied gas is presented using the method of pair functions. The conception of pair distribution functions is introduced and a heuristical derivation of the equations for pair functions is presented. Unlike the situation with the traditional Boltzmann equation, the hypothesis of molecular chaos was not used during the derivation of the equations for pair functions.
               
            </dc:description><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/000926149085433D" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/000926149085433D" rel="scidir"/></coredata><scopus-id>10444253955</scopus-id><scopus-eid>2-s2.0-10444253955</scopus-eid><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/abstract/scopus_id/10444253955" rel="abstract"/><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20020115">2002-01-15</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20020115">2002-01-15</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2016-06-10T09:33:43</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926149085433D</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(90)85433-D</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926149085433D</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)85433-D</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.3</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-AND-TAIL</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X09712</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20160611">2016-06-11T07:50:38.832504-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19900112</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1990</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1011052800">2002-01-15T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm authfirstinitialnorm authfirstsurnamenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav affil articletitle auth authfirstini authfull authlast primabst ref</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>165</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>165</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>2</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:iss-last>3</xocs:iss-last>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>2</xocs:issue>
         <xocs:issue>3</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 165, Issues 2–3</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>20</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>226</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>228</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>226</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>228</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19900112</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>12 January 1990</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1990-01-12</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1990</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>fla</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1990 Published by Elsevier B.V.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>EQUATIONSPAIRDISTRIBUTIONFUNCTIONS</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:normalized-first-auth-surname>LEBED</xocs:normalized-first-auth-surname>
      <xocs:normalized-first-auth-initial>I</xocs:normalized-first-auth-initial>
      <xocs:references>
         <xocs:ref-info refid="BIB1">
            <xocs:ref-normalized-surname>LIBOFF</xocs:ref-normalized-surname>
            <xocs:ref-pub-year>1969</xocs:ref-pub-year>
            <xocs:ref-normalized-initial>R</xocs:ref-normalized-initial>
            <xocs:ref-normalized-srctitle>INTRODUCTIONTHEORYKINETICEQUATIONS</xocs:ref-normalized-srctitle>
         </xocs:ref-info>
      </xocs:references>
      <xocs:refkeys>
         <xocs:refkey3>LEBEDX1990X226</xocs:refkey3>
         <xocs:refkey4lp>LEBEDX1990X226X228</xocs:refkey4lp>
         <xocs:refkey4ai>LEBEDX1990X226XI</xocs:refkey4ai>
         <xocs:refkey5>LEBEDX1990X226X228XI</xocs:refkey5>
      </xocs:refkeys>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(90)85433-D</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>000926149085433D</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-000926149085433D</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)85433-D</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2016-06-11T07:50:38.832504-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1990-01-12</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926149085433D-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926149085433D/MAIN/application/pdf/5207230a8d4fee7e0ba12b15900d1af4/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926149085433D/MAIN/application/pdf/5207230a8d4fee7e0ba12b15900d1af4/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>239448</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>3</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-000926149085433D-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:000926149085433D/PREVIEW/image/png/fb8f595e85bfe38ab1bbc8f729adb851/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:000926149085433D/PREVIEW/image/png/fb8f595e85bfe38ab1bbc8f729adb851/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>76907</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETI ERS  12 January 1990  Volume 165, number 2,3  EQUATIONS OF PAIR DISTRIBUTION FUNCTIONS    l.V. LEBED  CentralAero-Hydrodynamical Institute, Zjukovsky-3, Moscow District 140160, USSR      Received 6 July 1989; in final form 28 October 1989         A description of a rarefied gas is presented using the method of pair functions. The conception of pair distribution functions is  introduced and a heuristical derivation of the equations for pair functions is presented. Unlike the situation with the traditional  Boltzmann equation, the hypothesis of molecular chaos was not used during the derivation of the equations for pair functions.         The Boltzmann kinetic equation suffers from the defect that during its derivation the hypothesis of molecular  chaos is assumed, which presupposes the statistical independence of the colliding particles. This paper presents  a method which does not involve the hypothesis of molecular chaos and this fact makes it possible to estimate  the error introduced by the hypothesis into the kinetic and hydrodynamic equations.   We consider a rarefied homogeneous gas, containing structureless particles without outside disturbance. The  gas is assumed to be rarefied if the time t between two collisions is much greater than the characteristic collision  time  r~ (triple collisions may be neglected). Our study is limited by the case r &lt;&lt; ~, where ~ is the characteristic  time scale of the flow. Particles move in such a gas without any interaction for most of the time. In the time  interval between two collisions the particle is in a diverging phase with respect to the particle it has collided  with and in an approaching phase with respect to the next particle it is to collide with.   The method is based on division of all the gas particles into approaching and divergent pairs. The production  of a pair of divergent particles is identical with the termination of their collision process, and the disappearance  of the pair is identical with the collision of at least one of the particles of the pair with a third particle.   In much the same way one may isolate pairs of approaching particles in the gas. The disappearance of the  pair of particles is identical with the beginning of the interaction between the particles. The production of the  pair is identified with the termination of the interaction of both particles with third particles. Some particles  at certain times may have no pair, i.e. the particle at this instant is not considered to be approaching another  particles until the particle it is to collide with is produced. This problem will not be discussed in this study  and such situations will be ignored.   Let the probable number of pairs of approaching particles with their inertial centres in a volume element  dX near X at time T, the velocity of the inertial centre of which is in the interval dG near G, and the velocity  of the relative movement of the particles is in the interval dv near v, be f~  ( T, X, G, v) dXdG dv. We denote  by f v  (T, X, G, v) the pair distribution function corresponding to approaching particles. By analogy, we de-  note by f~  (T, X, G, v) the pair distribution function corresponding to divergent particles.   We begin the heuristic derivation of the equations for pair distribution functions by studying the collision  process of some pair. Let us draw a line through the inertial centre of the pair, which is parallel to the vector  u. Let this line be an axis of the cylindrical coordinate system b, e, z. We assume that collision has occurred  if the particle of the reduced mass ~= ~ m, where m is the particle mass, has reached the plane z= 0. Just before  the collision, which is characterized by the azimuthal angle e and the impact parameter b(0~b~d0, d0 is the  length of force range), the pair of particles with relative velocity v will have velocity i  (b, ~, v) if G is constant,  and v  = v~. As follows from the classical equations of motion for a simultaneous change of sign of particle  226  0009-2614/90/s 03.50   Elsevier Science Publishers B.V. (North-Holland)  Volume 165, number 2,3  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 January 1990  velocities and time and for a simultaneous inversion in the coordinate and velocity space,just after the collision  of structureless particles with impact parameter b  = b, azimuthal angle c  = it   c and velocities v  and G, the  pair will have velocities v and 6.   Let us examine a group of pairs of divergent particles with inertial centres in the element dX near X and  velocities in the interval dG dv near G, vat time T, f r ( T, X, G, v) dXdG dv. If the particles of the examined  group collide during the time interval r0 &lt;&lt; dT&lt;&lt;t with any third particles, then by the time T+ dT the inertial  centres of these pairs will be in the volume element dX near the point X+ 6 dT. At the time T+ dT the pairs  involving the colliding particles will leave the group under study. On the other hand, by that time the group  under study will acquire pairs which have been approaching each other at time Tjust after the collision.   We now determine the number of pairs which leave the group under study after the collision. By definition  at least one particle will collide with third particle during the time interval r, this will result in the disappearance  of a pair from the group under study. As a result of this, during the time interval dT.f ~ (T, X, 6, v) dXdG dv dT/  t particles will leave the group under study.   The number of pairs, which belong to the group at time T+ dT may be calculated in the same way. During  the time interval dTf~~~ (T, X, 6, v ) dXdGdv  dT/r particles of the approaching pairs will come into col~  lision, and f;PP ( T, X, 6, ~  ) dXdGdv  dT b  db  dc /~a of them will enter the group under study after the  collision, i=7Ld~. So    fdiv(T+dTx+GdT 6, v)dXdGdv      =fr(T, X, 6, v) dXdGdv+ [1 r(T, X, G, v )b db  dc dv   fr(T, X, 6, v) bdbdc dv] dXdGdT   (1)     In order to calculate the change in the phase volume after collision we study an ensemble of identical pairs,  the parameters for which differ from each other in the small interval limit of the phase volume and make use  of Liouville s theorem [1]. Expanding the left-hand side about dT and retaining only the linear terms gives  ~ (2)       Let v, 0, q be the spherical coordinates of the vector v. Eq. (2) can be integrated with respect to 0, ~i and if  one takes into account the fact that v  = I el, this gives   8 8 \ f~PP(T X G v)_f~(T X G v)      I            I         (3)           The evolution of the distribution function f ~ (T, X, G, v), which describes pairs of approaching particles,  may be followed in the same way. If the pairs of approaching particles, whose inertial centres are in the volume  element dX near the point X GdT at time T dT, and velocities in the interval dGv2 dv near 6, v, do not  collide during the time interval t~ &lt;&lt; dT az t, then by time T these pairs will be in the element dX near X. How-  ever a partf~PP(T, X, G, v)dXdGv2dudT/t of the pairs are not in the groupf~(T dT, X GdT, 6,  v) dXdG v2 dv under study at time T dT. On the other handf~ (T, X, G, v) dXdG v2 dvdT/t of the formerly  divergent pairs are now in the group at time T. This results in the equation  ( a a faPP(T X G v)_fd~(T X 6 v)   p        (4)             In order to solve eqs. (3) and (4), we transform to a coordinate system which moves evenly and rectilinearly  227  Volume 165, number 2,3  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 January 1990  with the inertial centre velocity G of the two groups of pairs under study, which are described by functions  f ~  (T, X, G, v) and f ~ ( T, X, 6, v). Under such conditions T  = T, X  = X  GT. Then the solution of the  equations will take the form  f~~=C1T +C2, fdivC(T~  r)+C2. (5)     In eq. (5) C1 = C~ (X ), C2 = C2 (X ) are the values which are conserved along the inertial centre trajectory;  moreover C~ is bound to be equal to zero, Otherwise, the result becomes physically absurd: either the number  of pairs of the groups under study will grow without limit, or it will take a negative value.   Thus the distribution functionsf~ ( T, X, G, v) andfr ( T, X, 6, v) which have the sense of probable num-  bers of pairs of approaching and divergent particles in a unit element volume and a unit velocity interval, does  not change along the trajectory of the centre of inertial, i.e.    f~(T,X,G,v)=f~(T0,X G(T T0),6,v), f~iv(T,x,G,v)fr(To,xG(T_To),6,v).     Note that this result does not depend on the choice for r in eqs. (3) and (4). This problem is not considered  in this study.   One can trace the analogy between the pair functionsfr (T, X, G, v) and f~ (T, X, 6, v) in the homo-  geneous medium and one-particle distribution functionf1 in a free molecular flow. Howeverf1, conserving along  the particle trajectory, refers to the population of particles [1], at the same time the pairs f ~ (T, X, 6, v)  and f~ ( T, X, 6, v), which conserve along the inertial centre s trajectory, refer to the population of the con-  tinuously created and annihilated pairs.   The validity of the principal property of pair distribution functions   their constancy along the pair inertial  centre trajectory, is verified by solving the classic hydrodynamic problems; Couette flow, Poiseuille flow, Stokes   problem, gas motion among rotating cylinders, heat transfer among infinite plates. In order to prove these and  subsequent results one must connect the hydrodynamic values with pair distribution functions and derive the  hydrodynamic equations from the equations obtained in the study. These considerations will be presented in  later papers.     The author wishes to thank Dr. S.Ya. Umansky for discussions regarding the results of this work.      Reference    Ill R.L. Liboff, Introduction to the theory of kinetic equations (Wiley, New York, 1969).  228  up under study after the  collision, i=7Ld~. So    fdiv(T+dTx+GdT 6, v)dXdGdv      =fr(T, X, 6, v) dXdGdv+ [1 r(T, X, G, v )b db  dc dv   fr(T, X, 6, v) bdbdc dv] dXdGdT   (1)     In order to calculate the change in the phase volume after collision we study an ensemble of identical pairs,  the parameters for which differ from each other in the small interval limit of the phase volume and make use  of Liouville s theorem [1]. Expanding the left-hand side about dT and retaining only the linear terms gives  ~ (2)       Let v, 0, q be the spherical coordinates of the vector v. Eq. (2) can be integrated with respect to 0, ~i and if  one takes into account the fact that v  = I el, this gives   8 8 \ f~PP(T X G v)_f~(T X G v)      I            I         (3)           The evolution of the distribution function f ~ (T, X, G, v), which describes pairs of approaching particles,  may be followed in the same way. If the pairs of approaching particles, whose inertial centres are in the volume  element dX near the point X GdT at time T dT, and velocities in the interval dGv2 dv near 6, v, do not  collide during the time interval t~ &lt;&lt; dT az t, then by time T these pairs will be in the element dX near X. How-  ever a partf~PP(T, X, G, v)dXdGv2dudT/t of the pairs are not in the groupf~(T dT, X GdT, 6,  v) dXdG v2 dv under study at time T dT. On the other handf~ (T, X, G, v) dXdG v2 dvdT/t of the formerly  divergent pairs are now in the group at time T. This results in the equation  ( a a faPP(T X G v)_fd~(T X 6 v)   p        (4)             In order to solve eqs. (3) and (4), we transform to a coordinate system which moves evenly and rectilinearly  227  Volume 165, number 2,3  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  12 January 1990  with the inertial centre velocity G of the two groups of pairs under study, which are described by functions  f ~  (T, X, G, v) and f ~ ( T, X, 6, v). Under such conditions T  = T, X  = X  GT. Then the solution of the  equations will take the form  f~~=C1T +C2, fdivC(T~  r)+C2. (5)     In eq. (5) C1 = C~ (X ), C2 = C2 (X ) are the values which are conserved along the inertial centre trajectory;  moreover C~ is bound to be equal to zero, Otherwise, the result becomes physically absurd: either the number  of pairs of the groups under study will grow without limit, or it will take a negative value.   Thus the distribution functionsf~ ( T, X, G, v) andfr </xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="fla" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>9085433D</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(90)85433-D</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)85433-D</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="unknown" year="1990"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Equations of pair distribution functions</ce:title>
            <ce:author-group>
               <ce:author>
                  <ce:given-name>I.V.</ce:given-name>
                  <ce:surname>Lebed</ce:surname>
               </ce:author>
               <ce:affiliation>
                  <ce:textfn>Central Aero-Hydrodynamical Institute, Zjukovsky-3, Moscow District 140160, USSR</ce:textfn>
               </ce:affiliation>
            </ce:author-group>
            <ce:date-received day="6" month="7" year="1989"/>
            <ce:abstract class="author">
               <ce:section-title>Abstract</ce:section-title>
               <ce:abstract-sec>
                  <ce:simple-para view="all" id="simple-para.0010">A description of a rarefied gas is presented using the method of pair functions. The conception of pair distribution functions is introduced and a heuristical derivation of the equations for pair functions is presented. Unlike the situation with the traditional Boltzmann equation, the hypothesis of molecular chaos was not used during the derivation of the equations for pair functions.</ce:simple-para>
               </ce:abstract-sec>
            </ce:abstract>
         </head>
         <tail>
            <ce:bibliography view="all" id="bibliography.0010">
               <ce:section-title>References</ce:section-title>
               <ce:bibliography-sec id="bibliography-sec.0010">
                  <ce:bib-reference id="BIB1">
                     <ce:label>[1]</ce:label>
                     <sb:reference>
                        <sb:contribution langtype="en">
                           <sb:authors>
                              <sb:author>
                                 <ce:given-name>R.L.</ce:given-name>
                                 <ce:surname>Liboff</ce:surname>
                              </sb:author>
                           </sb:authors>
                        </sb:contribution>
                        <sb:host>
                           <sb:book>
                              <sb:book-series>
                                 <sb:series>
                                    <sb:title>
                                       <sb:maintitle>Introduction to the theory of kinetic equations</sb:maintitle>
                                    </sb:title>
                                 </sb:series>
                              </sb:book-series>
                              <sb:date>1969</sb:date>
                              <sb:publisher>
                                 <sb:name>Wiley</sb:name>
                                 <sb:location>New York</sb:location>
                              </sb:publisher>
                           </sb:book>
                        </sb:host>
                     </sb:reference>
                  </ce:bib-reference>
               </ce:bibliography-sec>
            </ce:bibliography>
         </tail>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>