<full-text-retrieval-response xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/svapi/article/dtd" xmlns:bk="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/bk/dtd" xmlns:cals="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/cals/dtd" xmlns:ce="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/dtd" xmlns:ja="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:sa="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-aff/dtd" xmlns:sb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/struct-bib/dtd" xmlns:tb="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/common/table/dtd" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xocs="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:prism="http://prismstandard.org/namespaces/basic/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><coredata><prism:url>https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/0009261490855068</prism:url><dc:identifier>doi:10.1016/0009-2614(90)85506-8</dc:identifier><eid>1-s2.0-0009261490855068</eid><prism:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)85506-8</prism:doi><pii>0009-2614(90)85506-8</pii><dc:title>Author index to volume 174 </dc:title><prism:publicationName>Chemical Physics Letters</prism:publicationName><prism:aggregationType>Journal</prism:aggregationType><prism:issn>00092614</prism:issn><prism:volume>174</prism:volume><prism:issueIdentifier>6</prism:issueIdentifier><prism:startingPage>669</prism:startingPage><prism:endingPage>678</prism:endingPage><prism:pageRange>669-678</prism:pageRange><prism:number>6</prism:number><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><prism:coverDate>1990-11-23</prism:coverDate><prism:coverDisplayDate>23 November 1990</prism:coverDisplayDate><prism:copyright>Copyright © 1990  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</prism:copyright><prism:publisher>Published by Elsevier B.V.</prism:publisher><dc:description/><openaccess>0</openaccess><openaccessArticle>false</openaccessArticle><openaccessType/><openArchiveArticle>false</openArchiveArticle><openaccessSponsorName/><openaccessSponsorType/><openaccessUserLicense/><link href="https://api.elsevier.com/content/article/pii/0009261490855068" rel="self"/><link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/0009261490855068" rel="scidir"/></coredata><originalText><xocs:doc xmlns:xoe="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xoe/dtd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/xocs/dtd http://null/schema/dtds/document/fulltext/xcr/xocs-article.xsd">
   <xocs:meta>
      <xocs:content-family>serial</xocs:content-family>
      <xocs:content-type>JL</xocs:content-type>
      <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
      <xocs:ssids>
         <xocs:ssid type="alllist">291210</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291687</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291720</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291790</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291821</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="subj">291940</xocs:ssid>
         <xocs:ssid type="content">31</xocs:ssid>
      </xocs:ssids>
      <xocs:srctitle>Chemical Physics Letters</xocs:srctitle>
      <xocs:normalized-srctitle>CHEMICALPHYSICSLETTERS</xocs:normalized-srctitle>
      <xocs:orig-load-date yyyymmdd="20020115">2002-01-15</xocs:orig-load-date>
      <xocs:available-online-date yyyymmdd="20020115">2002-01-15</xocs:available-online-date>
      <xocs:ew-transaction-id>2015-10-04T23:22:40</xocs:ew-transaction-id>
      <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-0009261490855068</xocs:eid>
      <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(90)85506-8</xocs:pii-formatted>
      <xocs:pii-unformatted>0009261490855068</xocs:pii-unformatted>
      <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)85506-8</xocs:doi>
      <xocs:item-stage>S350</xocs:item-stage>
      <xocs:item-version-number>S350.2</xocs:item-version-number>
      <xocs:item-weight>HEAD-ONLY</xocs:item-weight>
      <xocs:hub-eid>1-s2.0-S0009261400X09530</xocs:hub-eid>
      <xocs:timestamp yyyymmdd="20151006">2015-10-06T13:23:50.72332-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
      <xocs:dco>0</xocs:dco>
      <xocs:tomb>0</xocs:tomb>
      <xocs:date-search-begin>19901123</xocs:date-search-begin>
      <xocs:year-nav>1990</xocs:year-nav>
      <xocs:indexeddate epoch="1011052800">2002-01-15T00:00:00Z</xocs:indexeddate>
      <xocs:articleinfo>rawtext articleinfo articletitlenorm cid cids contenttype copyright crossmark dateloaded dateloadedtxt datesearch datesort dateupdated dco docsubtype doctype doi eid ewtransactionid hubeid indexeddate issfirst issn issnnorm issuelist itemstage itemtransactionid itemweight openaccess openarchive pg pgfirst pglast pii piinorm pubdatestart pubdatetxt pubyr sortorder srctitle srctitlenorm srctype ssids alllist content subj tomb volfirst volissue volumelist webpdf webpdfpagecount yearnav articletitle</xocs:articleinfo>
      <xocs:issns>
         <xocs:issn-primary-formatted>0009-2614</xocs:issn-primary-formatted>
         <xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>00092614</xocs:issn-primary-unformatted>
      </xocs:issns>
      <xocs:crossmark is-crossmark="0">false</xocs:crossmark>
      <xocs:vol-first>174</xocs:vol-first>
      <xocs:volume-list>
         <xocs:volume>174</xocs:volume>
      </xocs:volume-list>
      <xocs:iss-first>6</xocs:iss-first>
      <xocs:issue-list>
         <xocs:issue>6</xocs:issue>
      </xocs:issue-list>
      <xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>Volume 174, Issue 6</xocs:vol-iss-suppl-text>
      <xocs:sort-order>26</xocs:sort-order>
      <xocs:first-fp>669</xocs:first-fp>
      <xocs:last-lp>678</xocs:last-lp>
      <xocs:pages>
         <xocs:first-page>669</xocs:first-page>
         <xocs:last-page>678</xocs:last-page>
      </xocs:pages>
      <xocs:cover-date-orig>
         <xocs:start-date>19901123</xocs:start-date>
      </xocs:cover-date-orig>
      <xocs:cover-date-text>23 November 1990</xocs:cover-date-text>
      <xocs:cover-date-start>1990-11-23</xocs:cover-date-start>
      <xocs:cover-date-year>1990</xocs:cover-date-year>
      <xocs:document-type>converted-article</xocs:document-type>
      <xocs:document-subtype>mis</xocs:document-subtype>
      <xocs:copyright-line>Copyright © 1990  Published by Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</xocs:copyright-line>
      <xocs:normalized-article-title>AUTHORINDEXVOLUME174</xocs:normalized-article-title>
      <xocs:refkeys/>
      <xocs:open-access>
         <xocs:oa-article-status is-open-access="0" is-open-archive="0"/>
      </xocs:open-access>
      <xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
         <xocs:attachment-set-type>item</xocs:attachment-set-type>
         <xocs:pii-formatted>0009-2614(90)85506-8</xocs:pii-formatted>
         <xocs:pii-unformatted>0009261490855068</xocs:pii-unformatted>
         <xocs:eid>1-s2.0-0009261490855068</xocs:eid>
         <xocs:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)85506-8</xocs:doi>
         <xocs:cid>271350</xocs:cid>
         <xocs:timestamp>2015-10-06T13:23:50.72332-04:00</xocs:timestamp>
         <xocs:cover-date-start>1990-11-23</xocs:cover-date-start>
         <xocs:attachments>
            <xocs:web-pdf>
               <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-0009261490855068-main.pdf</xocs:attachment-eid>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:0009261490855068/MAIN/application/pdf/beda12c6061fbbda7d154f7b3191681a/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:0009261490855068/MAIN/application/pdf/beda12c6061fbbda7d154f7b3191681a/main.pdf</xocs:ucs-locator>
               <xocs:filename>main.pdf</xocs:filename>
               <xocs:extension>pdf</xocs:extension>
               <xocs:pdf-optimized>true</xocs:pdf-optimized>
               <xocs:filesize>718961</xocs:filesize>
               <xocs:web-pdf-purpose>MAIN</xocs:web-pdf-purpose>
               <xocs:web-pdf-page-count>10</xocs:web-pdf-page-count>
               <xocs:web-pdf-images>
                  <xocs:web-pdf-image>
                     <xocs:attachment-eid>1-s2.0-0009261490855068-main_1.png</xocs:attachment-eid>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-us-east/content/pii:0009261490855068/PREVIEW/image/png/4a8e718788334c576015941e871519b7/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:ucs-locator>https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/prod-ucs-content-store-eu-west/content/pii:0009261490855068/PREVIEW/image/png/4a8e718788334c576015941e871519b7/main_1.png</xocs:ucs-locator>
                     <xocs:filename>main_1.png</xocs:filename>
                     <xocs:extension>png</xocs:extension>
                     <xocs:filesize>58882</xocs:filesize>
                     <xocs:pixel-height>849</xocs:pixel-height>
                     <xocs:pixel-width>656</xocs:pixel-width>
                     <xocs:attachment-type>IMAGE-WEB-PDF</xocs:attachment-type>
                     <xocs:pdf-page-num>1</xocs:pdf-page-num>
                  </xocs:web-pdf-image>
               </xocs:web-pdf-images>
            </xocs:web-pdf>
         </xocs:attachments>
      </xocs:attachment-metadata-doc>
   </xocs:meta>
   <xocs:rawtext>Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEITERS  23November 1990  Author Index to Volume 174    Absbagen, M., J. Kowaiski, M. Meyberg, G. zu Putlitz, J. Slaby and F. Trager, Neutrali-  zation of mass-separated lead-cluster ions in sodium vapor  Akaba, R., H. Sakuragi and K. Tokumaru, Detection of dimeric radical cations of trans-  stilbene in 2,4,6-triphenylpyrylium tetrafluoroborate-sensitized electron transfer reac-  tions in dichloromethane  Al-Soufi, W., K.H. Grellmann and B. Nickel, Triplet state formation and cis itrans iso-  merization in the excited singlet state of the keto tautomer of 2- (2 -  hydroxyphenyl )benzothiazole  Alvarez, R.A., see E.R. Lovejoy  Andre, J., see G. Brincourt  Anisimov, O.A., see V.1. Melekhov  Arickx, F., see J. Broeckhove  Armstrong, R.L., see A. Tzalmona  Astashkin, AV. and A. Schweiger, Electron-spin transient nutation: a new approach to sim-  plify the interpretation of ESR spectra  Avnir, D., see R. Gutfraind  Azumi, T., see S. Yamamoto    Baltzer, P., see M. Carlsson Gothe  Bard, A.J., see C. Liu  Barker, J.R., see B.M. Toselli  Barnes, C.J., see M. Lindroos  Bazzo, R., C.J. Edge, M.R. Wormald, T.W. Rademacher and R.A. Dwek, Full simulation  of ROESY, including the Hartmann Hahn effects  Beidoun, A., see A. Penzkofer  Berg, M., see T.J. Kang  Bernath, P.F., see M. Douay  Bernholc, J., see J.-Y. Yi  Bernstein, J., J.A.R.P. Sarma and A. Gavezzotti, Generation of unknown crystal phases for  aromatic hydrocarbons by packing energy calculations  Bethune, D.S., G. Meijer, W.C. Tang and H.J. Rosen, The vibrational Raman spectra of  purified solid films of C60 and C70  Bitting Jr., H.C., see C.T. Lin  Bolkunov, l.A., N.M. Sergeyev and N.N. Shapet ko,  TO,  H coupling constants in intra-  molecular hydrogen bonds  Bowers, MT., see P.P. Radi  Bowman, R.M., M. Dantus and A.H. Zewail, Femtosecond multiphoton dynamics of higher-  energy potentials  Brincourt, G., R. Catella, Y. Zerega and J. Andre, Time-of-flight detection of ions ejected  from a radiofrequency quadrupole trap: experimental determination of their J secular  frequency  174 (1990) 455      174 (1990) 80  (1990) 609  (1990) [51  (1990) 626  (1990) 95  (1990) 504  (1990) 199  174  174  174  174  174  174  174 (1990) 595  174 (1990) 8  174 (1990) 176  174  174  174  174  (1990) 109  (1990) 162  (1990) 304  (1990) 108  174 (1990) 313  174 (1990) 621  174 (1990) 476  174 (1990) 230  174 (1990) 461    174 (1990) 361    174 (1990) 219  174 (1990) 269    174 (1990) 587  174 (1990) 223    174 (1990) 546      174 (1990) 626  669  Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  23November 1990  Brochon, J.-C., AK. Livesey, J. Pouget and B. Valeur, Data analysis in frequency-domain  fluorometry by the maximum entropy method   recovery of fluorescence lifetime  distributions  Broeckhove, J., B. Feyen, L. Lathouwers, F. Arickx and P. Van Leuven, Quantum time  evolution of vibrational states in curve-crossing problems  Buck, U., X.J. Gu, R. Krohne and Ch. Lauenstein, Infrared photodissociation of size-se-  lected acetonitrile clusters    Cacelli, I., Basis set and gauge dependence of ab initio radiative lifetimes for the A21t state  of the HF~ molecule  Car, R., see J.-Y. Yi  Carlsson Gothe, M., F.T. Chau, P. Baitzer, S. Svensson, B. Wannberg and L. K.arlsson, Vi-  brationally resolved study of the fourth photoelectron band of acetylene at 23.5 eV  Catella, R., see G. Brincourt  Chaboy, J., J. Garcia, A. Marcelli and M.F. Ruiz-Lapez, An experimental and theoretical  study of multielectron excitations at the L3 absorption edge in some rare earth alloys  and their hydrides  Chan, F., see C.A. Jolly  Chaquin, P., see A. Sevin  Chau, F.T., see M. Carlsson Gothe  Chen, J., see E. Quiflones  Chen, J.M., see J.S. Tse  Chittock, R.S., see F. Wilkinson  Chou, P.4., M,L. Martinez and S.L. Studer, Direct spectroscopie measurements of ~Ag 02  production by thermodecomposition and UV (266 nm) photolysis of benzaldehyde  hydrotrioxide  Church, D.A., see S. Tu  Comsa, G., see L.K. Verheij  Couto dos Santos, M.A., see O.L. Malta  Crosby, G.A., see S. Yamamoto  Cross, A., see A. Tzalmona  Cummins, P.L. and J .E. Gready, Atomic charges derived from semiempirical electrostatic  potentials: an interaction energy method  Curini, M., see H.A. Kolodziej  Curtiss, L.A., see P.W. Deutsch  Cyr, M., see H. Levanon    Dagdigian, P.J., see E. Quiflones  Dagdigian, P.J., see D. Patel-Misra  Dantus, M., see R.M. Bowman  Davis, L.M., see E.B. Shera  Dedonder-Lardeux, C., see W. Siebrand  Demtroder, W., see W. Theiss  De Santis, A. and A. Gregori, On the allowed and induced cross contributions in light scat-  tering from fluids of small molecules  Deutsch, P.W., L.A. Curtiss and J.A. Pople, Boron dimer: dissociation energy and ioni-  zation potentials  174 (1990) 517    174 (1990) 504    174 (1990) 247      174 (1990) 37  174 (1990) 461    174 (1990) 109  174 (1990) 626      174 (1990) 389  174 (1990) 320  174 (1990) 185  174 (1990) 109  174 (1990) 65  174 (1990) 603  174 (1990) 416      174 (1990) 46  174 (1990) 301  174 (1990) 449  174 (1990) 13  174 (1990) 176  174 (1990) 199    174 (1990) 355  174 (1990) 254  174 (1990) 33  174 (1990) 235    174 (1990) 65  174 (1990) 113  174 (1990) 546  174 (1990) 553  174 (1990) 558  174 (1990) 126    174 (1990) 631    174 (1990) 33  670  Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  23 November 1990  Dilung, 1.1., see E.I. Kapinus  Dmitrieva, I.K., see T.N. Zolotuidjina  Dolg, M., H. Stoll and H. Preuss, Ab initio pseudopotential study of the ~I and 7E states  of GdO  Domke, M., C. Xue, A. Puschmann, T. Mandel, E. Hudson, D.A. Shirley and G. Kaindl,  Carbon and oxygen K-edge photoionization of the CO molecule, Chem. Phys. Letters  173 (1990) 122. Erratum  Douay, M. and P.F. Bernath, Laser spectroscopy of CaNC and SrNC  Dwek, R.A., see R. Bazzo  Dyall, KG. and K. Foegri Jr., Kinetic balance and variational bounds failure in the solution  of the Dirac equation in a finite Gaussian basis set    Eckhardt, B., J.M. Gomez Llorente and E. Pollak, Phase space analysis of chaotic spectra  in a conservative Hamiltonian system  Edge, C.J., see R. Bazzo  Endo, Y., M. tida and Y. Ohshima, Predissociation of ammonia A state studied by mi-  crowave optical double-resonance spectroscopy    Ftegri Jr., K., see K.G. Dyall  Fawcett, W.R., Dipole dipole interactions and their role in relaxation processes in polar  solvents  Ferris, K.F. and S.M. Risser, Bond alternation in phosphonitrilic compounds  Feyen, B., see J. Broeckhove  Freed, J.H., see A. Polimeno  Freed, J.H., see A. Polimeno  Fujii, N., see T. Tokuda  Fukunaga, K., see K. Yoshikawa    Galaup, J.P., see P.J. van der Zaag  Galili, T., see H. Levanon  GarcIa, J., see J. Chaboy  Garza-Lopez, R.A., J.K. Rudra and J.J. Kozak, Diffusion of a dimer through a structured  medium  Gavezzotti, A., see J. Bernstein  Gladkov, S.O., On the theory of control of chemical reactions by osoillating high frequency  electric field  Gomez Llorcnte, J.M., see B. Eekhardt  Graff, M.M. and A.F. Wagner, Theoretical studies of fine-structure effects and long-range  forces: approximating the reactive surface of O ( 3P) + OH ( n)  Grant, A.J. and B.T. Pickup, An analysis of molecular response properties  Gready, J.E., see P.L. Cummins  Gregori, A., see A. De Santis  Grellmann, K.H., see W. Al-Soufi  Grimm, J. and C. von Borczyskowski, Characterization of triplet aggregates in doped 1,4-  dibromobenzene crystals  Ou, X.J., see U. Buck  Gurtler, P., see P. Laporte  174 (1990) 75  174 (1990) 655    174 (1990) 208      174 (1990) 668  174 (1990) 230  174 (1990) 313    174 (1990) 25      174 (1990) 325  174 (1990) 313    174 (1990) 401      174 (1990) 25  174  174  174  174  174  174  174  (1990) 167  (1990) 333  (1990) 504  (1990) 338  (1990) 481  (1990) 385  (1990) 203  174 (1990) 467  174 (1990) 235  174 (1990) 389    174 (1990) 278  174 (1990) 361    174 (1990) 636  174 (1990) 325      174 (1990) 287  174 (1990) 523  174 (1990) 355  174 (1990) 631  174 (1990) 609    174 (1990) 294  174 (1990) 247  174 (1990) 61    671  Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYS1CS LETTERS  23 November 1990  Gurtler, P., see M. Kraas  Gutfraind, R., M. Sheintuch and D. Avnir, Multifraetal scaling analysis of diffusion-lim-  ited reactions with devil s staircase and Cantor set catalytic structures    Haase, F., J. Sauer and V. Kello, The beryllium atom water molecule interaction. A many-  body perturbation theory study  Hashimoto, K., S. Iwata andY. Osamura, An MCSCF study of the low-lying states of C2H~  Hecht, L. and L.A. Nafie, Linear polarization Raman optical activity: a new form of natural  optical activity  Higashide, H., see K. Kasatani  Histed, M., J.A. Howard, H.A. Joly and B. Mile, EPR spectra of the complexes of P(OMe)3  and PMe, with Cu atoms in hydrocarbon matrices at 77 K  Howard, JA., see M. Histed  Hsu, M.-T., see P.P. Radi  Hu, P., see M. Lindroos  Huang, R., see J. Zhan  Hudson, E., see M. Domke  Hugenschmidt, M.B., see L.K. Verheij    lida, M., see Y. Endo  Ikeda, S., see S. Yamamoto  Ikeuti, M., see K. Kobayashi  Ikeyama, T., see S. Yamamoto  Imazeki, S., see Y. Tomioka  ltaya, A., T. Yarnada and H. Masuhara, Laser photolysis study on photoinduced charge  separation in poly(N-vinylcarbazole) thin films  Iwata, S., see K. Hashimoto  174 (1990) 396    174 (1990) 8      174 (1990) 19  174 (1990) 649    174 (1990) 575  174 (1990) 71  174  174  174  174  174  174  174    174  174  174  174  174  (1990) 411  (1990) 411  (1990) 223  (1990) 108  (1990) 568  (1990) 668  (1990) 449    (1990) 401  (1990) 176  (1990) 157  (1990) 176  (1990) 433  174 (1990) 145  174 (1990) 649  Jackson, R.L., Spectroscopy of the CH,Zn radical. Vibrational frequencies and electronic  configurations of the ~  A, and ~ states  Janssen, R., see E.R.H. van Eck  Jolly, C.A., F. Chan and D.S. Marynick, Calculated inversion bathers and proton affinities  for P(CH3)3 and P(C6H,),  Joly, H.A., see M. Histed  Jouvet, C., see W. Siebrand    Kaindl, G., see M. Domke  Kamiya, M., A nuclear magnetic dipolar relaxation study of the internal rotation associated  with intramolecular hydrogen bonding  Kang, T.J., J. Yu and M. Berg, Rapid solvation of a nonpolar solute measured by ultrafast  transient holeburning  Kapinus, E.!. and 1.!. Dilung, Remote electron transfer in the quenching of porphyrin flu-  orescence by oxidants  Karisson, L., see M. Carlsson Gothe  Kasatani, K., H. Higashide, H. Shinohara and H. Sato, Chemiluminescent reactions stud-  ied by laser ablation. Detection of AlO (B ~ ~) in the Al + 02 system  Katoh, R., M. Ogiu and M. Kotani, Photoemission by singlet-exciton fusion in an anthra-  cene crystal  174 (1990) 53  174 (1990) 428    174 (1990) 320  174 (1990) 411  174 (1990) 558    174 (1990) 668    174 (1990) 661    174 (1990) 476    174 (1990) 75  174 (1990) 109    174 (1990) 71    174 (1990) 531  672  Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEiTERS  23 November 1990  Katoh, R. and M. Kotani, External photoemission by singlet-exciton photoionization in an  anthracene single crystal  Katoh, R. and M. Kotani, Photoionization and optical absorption of singlet excitons in a  t-stilbene crystal: excitation energy dependence of the ionization efficiency  Kawai, A., T. Okutsu and K. Obi, CIDEP in photodissociation of  cbloromethylnaphthalene  Kawakami, H., see K. Yoshikawa  Keller, RA., see E.B. Shera  Kello, V., see F. Haase  Kello, V. and A.J. Sadlej, Relativistic contributions to molecular electric-field gradients in  hydrogen halides  Kemper, P.R., see P.P. Radi  Kim, Y.H., T. Ree and H.K. Shin, Dependence of bond dissociation on initial vibrational  phase in the He + 12 system  King, D.A., see M. Lindroos  Kobayashi, K., M. Ikeuti and G. Okada, Appearance of surface states at the TiO2JH2O in-  terface after deposition of Fe atoms on the TiO2 surface  Kolodziej, H.A., K. Orzechowski, S. Sorriso and M. Curini, Dielectric relaxation and non-  linear dielectric effect in diazo compounds  Kotani, M., see R. Katoh  Kotani, M., see R. Katoh  Kotani, M., see R. Katoh  Kowalski, J., see M. Abshagen  Kozak, J.J., see R.A. Garza-Lopez  Kraas, M. and P. Gurtler, Emission and excitation spectra of rare gas hydride trimers in  rare gas matrices  Krohne, R., see U. Buck  174 (1990) 537    174 (1990) 541    174 (1990) 213  174 (1990) 203  174 (1990)553  174 (1990) 19    174 (1990) 641  174 (1990) 223    174 (1990) 494  174 (1990) 108    174 (1990) 157  174 (1990)  174 (1990)  174 (1990)  174 (1990)  174 (1990)  174 (1990)  254  531  537  541  455  278  174 (1990) 396  174 (1990)247  Lakhtakia, A., Polarizability dyadics of small chiral ellipsoids  Lapone, P., J.-L. Subtil, R. Reininger and P. Gurtler, Time- and energy-resolved lumines-  cence of the KrAr exciplex: from the dilute to the condensed phase  Latajka, Z. and S. Schemer, Correlation between interaction energy and shift of the car-  bonyl stretching frequency  Lathouwers, L., see J. Broeekhove  Lauenstein, Ch., see U. Buck  Lee, H.Y., see C.T. Lin  Lemaire, C., see A. Tzalmona  Leszczyftski, J., Electron correlation effects in the ab initio study on tautomerism of guanine  Leung, M.S., see C.T. Lin  Levanon, H., A. Regev, S. Michaeli, T. Galili, M. Cyr and J.L. Sessler, The photoexcited  triplet state of sapphyrin dication. Unusual spin alignment in monomers and spin de-  localization in dimers  Levine, R.D., The steric effect in surface scattering of oriented molecules: an optical model  interpretation  Li, 0,-Y. and X.-W. Wu, Rotary echo NMR spectroscopy in three-level systems  Lin, C.T., H.Y. Lee, H.C. Bitting Jr., R.A. Lipeles, M.B. Tueling and MS. Leung, Emission  and excitation spectra of thermally diffused ions in PLZT ceramics  Lindroos, M., C.J. Barnes, P. Hu and D.A. King, The termination and multilayer relaxa-  tion at the Co{lO1O) surface, Chem. Phys. Letters 173 (1990) 92. Erratum  174 (1990) 583      174 (1990) 61      174 (1990) 179  174 (1990) 504   174 (1990) 247  174 (1990) 269  174 (1990) 199  174 (1990) 347  174 (1990) 269   174 (1990) 235   174 (1990) 1  174 (1990) 309    174 (1990) 269   174 (1990) 108  673  Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEiTERS  23November 1990  Lipeles, R.A., see C.T. Lin  Liii, C. and Ai. Bard, Irradiation-induced nanometer-scale surface etching of a CdSe film  with a scanning tunneling microscope  Livesey, A.K., see J-C. Brochon  Loesch, H.J., see M. Velegrakis  Lotshaw, W.T., see D. McMorrow  Lovejoy, E.R., R.A. Alvarez and C.B. Moore, The yield of CO in the reaction:  CH2(a A1)+CH2CO  Lucia, J., see X. Song  Lund, A., see VI. Melekhov    Maas, W.E.J.R., see E.R.H. van Eck  Malta, 0.L. and M.A. Couto dos Santos, Theoretical analysis of the fluorescence yield of  rare earth ions in glasses containing small metallic particles  Mandel, T., see M. Domke  Marcelli, A., see J. Chaboy  Martinez, M.L., see P.-T. Chou  Marynick, D.S., see C.A. Jolly  Masuda, T., see T. Takigawa  Masuhara, H., see A. Itaya  Mazer, M., see M. Valko  McCammon, J.A., see R.A. Wheeler  MeMorrow, D. and W.T. Lotshaw, The frequency response of condensed-phase media to  femtosecond optical pulses: spectral-filter effects  Meech, S.R. and K. Yoshihara, Picosecond dynamics at the solid liquid interface: a total  internal reflection time-resolved surface second-harmonie generation study  Meijer, G., see D.S. Bethune  Melekhov, V.1., O.A. Anisimov, L. Sjoqvist and A. Lund, The electronic structure of eis-  and trans-decalin radical cations in halocarbon matrices: an ESR and MNDO study  Melnik, M., see M. Valko  Menzinger, M., see A. Tzalmona  Meyberg, M., see M. Abshagen  Michaeli, S., see H. Levanon  Mile, B., see M. Histed  Misra, G.P., see R.P. Rastogi  Moore, C.B., see E.R. Lovejoy  Mori, A., see H. Sekiya  Moylan, C.R., see A. Skumanich  Muschenborn, H.J., see W. Theiss    Nafie, LA., see L. Hecht  Nakai, H., see H. Nakatsuji  Nakatsuji, H. and H. Nakai, Theoretical study on molecular and dissociative ehemisorp-  tions of an 02 molecule on an Ag surface: dipped adeluster model combined with sym-  metry-adapted cluster-configuration interaction method  Nickel, B., see W. Al-Soufi  174 (1990) 269    174 (1990) 162  174 (1990) 517  174 (1990) 438  174 (1990) 85    174 (1990) 151  174 (1990) 377  174 (1990) 95    174 (1990) 428    174 (1990) 13  174 (1990) 668  174 (1990) 389  174 (1990) 46  174 (1990) 320  174 (1990) 259  174 (1990) 145  174 (1990) 591  174 (1990) 369    174 (1990) 85    174 (1990) 423  174 (1990) 219    174 (1990) 95  174 (1990) 591  174 (1990) 199  174 (1990) 455  174 (1990) 235  174 (1990) 411  174 (1990) 617  174 (1990) 151  174 (1990) 133  174 (1990) 139  174 (1990) 126    174 (1990) 575  174 (1990) 283      174 (1990) 283  174 (1990) 609  674  Volume 114, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LEiTERS  23 November 1990  Nieolaides, C.A. and P. Valtazanos, Hydrogen complexes of Be3 + 174 (1990) 489  Nishimura, Y., see H. Sekiya 174 (1990) 133  Obi, K., see A. Kawai 174 (1990) 213  Oguu, M., seeR. Katoh 174 (1990) 531  Oh, D.J., see/.-Y.Yi 174 (1990) 461  Ohshima, Y., see Y. Endo 174 (1990) 401  Okada, G., see K. Kobayashi 174 (1990) 157  Okutsu, T., see A. Kawai 174 (1990) 213  Orzeehowski, K., see H.A. Kolodziej 174 (1990) 254  Osamura, Y., see K. Hashimoto 174 (1990) 649    Papakondylis, A., see A. Sevin  Patel-Misra, D., D.G. Sauder and P.J. Dagdigian, Observation of the ND A3fl X ~i  isv  + 1 sequence  Pauls, S., see X. Song  Pelikan, P., see M. Valko  Penzkofer, A., A. Beidoun and G. Wagenblast, Saturable absorption dynamics of a cy-  anoviayl diethylaniline dye  Persson, B.N.J. and R. Ryberg, Dipole-coupling-induced line narrowing in adsorbate vi-  brational spectroscopy  Pickup, B.T., see A.J. Grant  Podgornik, R., Forces and conformation of a polyeleetrolyte chain between two charged  walls  Poelsema, B., see L.K. Verheij  Pohl, K., see R. Vogel  Polavarapu, P.L., Sum rules for Cartesian polarizability derivative tensors  Polimeno, A. and J.H. Freed, A many-body stochastic approach to rotational motions in  liquids: a reassessment of the Hubbard Einstein relation  Polimeno, A. and J.H. Freed, A many-body stochastic approach to rotational motions in  liquids: complex decay times in highly viscous fluids  Pollak, E., see B. Eekhardt  Pople, J.A., see P.W. Deutsch  Pouget, J., see J.-C. Brochon  Preuss, H., see M. Dolg  Puschmann, A., see M. Domke    Quiflones, E., J. Chen and P.J. Dagdigian, Observation of NH (X 3E , a  A) from the   H+NCO reaction 174 (1990) 65    Rademacher, T.W., see R. Bazzo  Radi, P.P., M.-T. Hsu, M.E. Rineon, P.R. Kemper and M.T. Bowers, On the structure,  reactivity and relative stability of the large carbon cluster ions C~, C~a and C~i  Rastogi, R.P. and G.P. Misra, Critical limits in Belousov Zhabotinskii reaction system  Ree, T., see Y.H. Kim  Regev, A., see H. Levanon  Reilly, J.P., see X. Song  174 (1990) 185    174 (1990) 113  174 (1990) 377  174 (1990) 591    174 (1990) 621    174 (1990) 443  174 (1990) 523  174  174  174  174  (1990) 191  (1990) 449  (1990) 241  (1990) 511  174 (1990) 338  174  174  174  174  174  174  (1990) 481  (1990) 325  (1990) 33  (1990) 517  (1990) 208  (1990) 668  174 (1990) 313  174  174  174  174  174  (1990) 223  (1990) 617  (1990) 494  (1990) 235  (1990) 377  675  Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  23 November 1990  Reininger, R., see P. Laporte  Rincon, M.E., see P.P. Radi  Risser, S.M., see K.F. Ferris  Rosen, Hi., see D.S. Bethune  Rudra, J.K., see R.A. Garza-Lopez  Ruiz-Lopez, M.F., see J. Chaboy  Ryberg, R., see B.N.J. Persson    Sadlej, A.J., see V. KellO  Sakuragi, H., see R. Akaba  Sarma, J.A.R.P., see J. Bernstein  Sasaki, K., see H. Sekiya  Sato, H., see K. Kasatani  Sauder, D.G., see D. Patel-Misra  Sauer, J., see F. Haase  Schaefer III, H.F., see G.E. Seuseria  Schemer, S., see Z. Latajka  Schweiger, A., see A.V. Astashkin  Scuseria, G.E. and H.F. Schaefer III, Diatomic chromium (Cr2): application of the cou-  pled cluster method including all single and double excitations (CCSD)  Seitzinger, N.K., see E.B. Shera  Sekiya, H., K. Sasaki, Y. Nishimura, A. Mon and H. Takeshita, Electronic spectra of jet-  cooled 3-bromotropolone in the 5, 5o region. Study of intramolecular hydrogen bond  Sergeyev, N.M., see l.A. Bolkunov  Sessler, J.L., see H. Levanon  Sevin, A., P. Chaquin and A. Papakondylis, A mechanistic study of the physical quenching  of Mg by C2H2. Comparison of adiabatic and diabatic potential energy surfaces  Shapet ko, N.N., see l.A. Bolkunov  Sheintuch, M., see R. Gutfraind  Shera, E.B., N.K. Seitzinger, L.M. Davis, R.A. Keller and S.A. Soper, Detection of single  fluorescent molecules  Shimizu, K., see T. Tokuda  Shin, H.K., see Y.H. Kim  Shinohara, H., see K. Kasatani  Shirley, D.A., see M. Domke  Siebrand, W., F. Zerbetto and M.Z. Zgierski, New assignment of the vibrational structure  of the V4 N transition in ethylene-d4  Siebrand, W., C. Dedonder-Lardeux and C. Jouvet, Observation and analysis of the cold  fluorescence-excitation spectrum of 2,3-dimethyl-2-butene  Sjoqvist, L., see V.1. Melekhov  Skumanich, A. and C.R. Moylan, The vibrational overtone spectrum of a thin polymer film  Slaby, J., see M. Abshagen  Song, X., C.W. Wilkerson Jr., J. Lucia, S. Pauls and J.P. Reilly, Direct observation of time-  dependent intramolecular vibrational relaxation in jet-cooled p-n-alkylanilines by laser  photoelectron spectroseopy  Soper, S.A., see E.B. Shera  Sorriso, S., see H.A. Kolodziej  174 (1990) 61  174 (1990) 223  174 (1990) 333  174 (1990) 219  174 (1990) 278  174 (1990) 389  174 (1990) 443    174 (1990) 641  174 (1990) 80  174 (1990) 361  174 (1990) 133  174 (1990) 71  174 (1990) 113  174 (1990) 19  174 (1990) 501  174 (1990) 179  174 (1990) 595    174 (1990) 501  174 (1990) 553    174 (1990) 133  174 (1990) 587  174 (1990) 235    174 (1990) 185  174 (1990) 587  174 (1990) 8    174 (1990) 553  174 (1990) 385  174 (1990) 494  174 (1990) 71  174 (1990) 668    174 (1990) 119    174 (1990) 558  174 (1990) 95  174 (1990) 139  174 (1990) 455      174 (1990) 377  174 (1990) 553  174 (1990) 254  676  Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  23 November 1990  Srivatsavoy, V.J.P. and B. Venkataraman, Laser flash photolysis of 1-  acetylaminoanthraquinone  Stace, A.J., Possible ion pairs in multiply charged water clusters  Stoll, H., see M. Doig  Studer, S.L., see P.-T. Chou  Subtil, J.-L., see P. Laporte  Svensson, S., see M. Carlsson Gothe    Takeshita, H., see H. Sekiya  Takigawa, T., K. Urayama and T. Masuda, Critical behavior of the specific viscosity of  poly (vinyl alcohol) solutions near the gelation threshold  Tan, K.H., see J.S. Tse  Tanaka, I,, see T. Tokuda  Tanaka, N., see Y. Tomioka  Tang, W.C., see D.S. Bethune  Theiss, W., H.J. Muschenbom and W. Demtroder, Laser speetroscopy of the Li2 D  nu state  Tokuda, T., N. Fujii, S. Yoshida, K. Shimizu and I. Tanaka, New emission of CuCl2 in  chemically produced 02 ( A) flow  Tokumaru, K., see R. Akaba  Tomioka, Y., S. Imazeki and N. Tanaka, Highly oriented polydiacetylene monolayer formed  at the air-water interface  Toselli, J3.M. and J.R. Barker, Quantum effects in large molecule collisional energy transfer?  Trager, F., see M. Abshagen  Tse, J.S., K.H. Tan and J.M. Chen, Oxygen K-edge XANES of crystalline and amorphous  ice  Tu, S. and D.A. Church, Electron transfer collisions of Be2~ with H2 and Be  Tueling, M.B., see C.T. Lin  Tzalmona, A., R.L. Armstrong, M. Menzinger, A. Cross and C. Lemaire, Detection of  chemical waves by magnetic resonance imaging    Urayama, K., see T. Takigawa   174 (1990) 406  174 (1990) 103  174 (1990) 208   174 (1990) 46   174 (1990) 61  174 (1990) 109    174 (1990) 133    174 (1990) 259  174 (1990) 603  174 (1990) 385  174 (1990) 433   174 (1990) 219  174 (1990) 126    174 (1990) 385  174 (1990) 80    174 (1990) 433  174 (1990) 304  174 (1990) 455    174 (1990) 603  174 (1990) 301  174 (1990) 269    174 (1990) 199    174 (1990) 259  174 (1990) 591  174 (1990) 517    174 (1990) 591  174 (1990) 489  174 (1990) 263    174 (1990) 467    174 (1990) 428  174 (1990) 504  174 (1990) 263  174 (1990) 428  174 (1990) 438  174 (1990) 406  Valach, F., see M. Valko  Valeur, B., see J.-C. Broehon  Valko, M., M. MelnIk, P. Pelikan, F. Valach and M. Maziir, ESR spectra of Cu (II) com-  plexes with biologically important ligands at 77 K  Valtazanos, P., see C.A. Nicolaides  Van Baar, J.F., see A. Wakker  Van der Zaag, P.J., J.P. Galaup and S. Volker, Influence of the experimental parameters on  time-resolved transient hole-burning  Van Eck, E.R.H., R. Janssen, W.E..J.R. Maas and W.S. Veeman, A novel application of nu-  clear spin-echo double-resonance to aluminophosphates and aluminosilicates  Van Leuven, P., see J. Broeekhove  Van Lith, W.J., see A. Wakker  Veeman, W.S., see E.R.H. van Eck  Velegrakis, M. and H.J. Loeseh, Rainbow scattering and time of flight spectra for Ar HCI  Venkntaraman, B., see V.J.P. Srivatsavoy  677  Volume 174, number 6  CHEMICAL PHYSICS LETTERS  23November 1990  Verheij, L.K., M.B. Hugenschmidt, B. Poelsema and G. Comsa, Influence of a very low  density of defects on the deuterium oxygen reaction on Pt (111)  Vogel, R., K. Pohl and H. Weller, Sensitization of highly porous, polycrystalline TiO2 elec-  trodes by quantum sized CdS  Volker, S., see P.J. van der Zaag  Von Borezyskowski, C., see J. Grimm    Wagenblast, G., see A. Penzkofer  Wagner, A.F., see M.M. Graff  Wakker, A., J.F. van Baar and Wi. van Lith, Scaling behaviour of concentration fluctua-  tions in a ternary liquid mixture: a dynamic light-seattering study  Wannberg, B., see M. Carisson Gothe  Weller, H., see R. Vogel  Wheeler, R.A. and J.A. McCammon, a orbitals in quantum path integral simulations of elec-  tron transfer paths  Wilkerson Jr., C.W., see X. Song  Wilkinson, F., D.R. Worrall and R.S. Chittock, Absorption and decay of excited states of  azomethine dyes on picosecond timescales  Wolff, D. and H. Zacharias, Lifetimes and collisional self-quenching rates for C2H2  A A~(v=o to 4)  Wormald, M.R., see R. Bazzo  Worrall, D.R., see F. Wilkinson  Wu, X-W., see G.-Y. Li    Xue, C., see M. Domke    Yamada, T., see A. Itaya  Yamamoto, S., S. Ikeda, T. Ikeyama, T. Azumi and G.A. Crosby, Zero-field splittings of  phenanthroline-localized  a emitting levels in mixed-ligand zinc (II) complexes  Yi, J.-Y., D.J. Oh, J. Bemhole and R. Car, Structural transitions in aluminum clusters  Yoshida, S., see T. Tokuda  Yoshihara, K., see S.R. Meech  Yoshikawa, K., K. Fukunaga and H. Kawakami, A tri-phasic mode is stable when three  non-linear oscillators interact with each other  Yu, J., see T.J. Kang    Zacharias, H., see D. Wolff  Zerbetto, F., see W. Siebrand  Zerega, Y., see G. Brineourt  Zewail, A.H., see R.M. Bowman  Zgierski, M.Z., see W. Siebrand  Zhan, J., R. Huang, Q. Zhuang and C. Zhang, A further study on the production of NF(b)  and IF(B) in the NH3 F F2 CF3I reaction system  Zhang, C., see J. Zhan  Zhuang, Q., see J. Zhan  Zolotukhina, T.N. and I.K. Dmitrieva, Correlation energies of diatomics obtained with a  nonlocal density functional  Zu Putlitz, G., see M. Abshagen  174 (1990) 449    174 (1990) 241  174 (1990) 467  174 (1990) 294    174 (1990) 621  174 (1990) 287    174 (1990) 263  174 (1990) 109  174 (1990) 241    174 (1990) 369  174 (1990) 377    174 (1990) 416    174 (1990) 563  174 (1990) 313  174 (1990) 416  174 (1990) 309    174 (1990) 668    174 (1990) 145    174 (1990) 176  174 (1990) 461  174 (1990) 385  174 (1990) 423    174 (1990) 203  174 (1990) 476    174 (1990) 563  174 (1990) 119  174 (1990) 626  174 (1990) 546  174 (1990) 119    174 (1990) 568  174 (1990) 568  174 (1990) 568    174 (1990) 655  174 (1990) 455  678   (1990) 208   174 (1990) 46   174 (1990) 61  174 (1990) 109    174 (1990) 133    174 (1990) 259  174 (1990) 603  174 (1990) 385  174 (1990) 433   174 (1990) 219  174 (1990) 126    174 (1990) 385  174 (1990) 80    174 (1990) 433  174 (1990) 304  174 (1990) 455    174 (1990) 603  174 (1990) 301  174 (1990) 269    174 (1990) 199    174 (1990) 259  174 (1990) 591  174 (1990) 517    174 (1990) 591  174 (1990) 489  174 (1990) 263    174 (1990) 467    174 (1990) 428  174 (1990) 504  174 (1990) 263  174 (1990) 428  174 (1990) 438  174 (1990) 406  Valach, F., see M. Valko  Valeur, B., see J.-C. Broehon  Valko, M., M. MelnIk, P. Pelikan, F. Valach and M. Maziir, ESR spectra of Cu (II) com-  plexes with biologically important ligands at 77 K  Valtazanos, P., see C.A. Nicolaides  Van Baar, J.F., see A. Wakker  Van der Zaag, P.J., J.P. Galaup and S. Volker, Influence of the experimental parameters on  time-resolved transient hole-burning  Van Eck, E.R.H., R. Janssen, W.E..J.R. Maas and W.S. Veeman, A nov</xocs:rawtext>
   <xocs:serial-item>
      <converted-article xmlns="http://www.elsevier.com/xml/ja/dtd" version="4.5.2" docsubtype="mis" xml:lang="en">
         <item-info>
            <jid>CPLETT</jid>
            <aid>90855068</aid>
            <ce:pii>0009-2614(90)85506-8</ce:pii>
            <ce:doi>10.1016/0009-2614(90)85506-8</ce:doi>
            <ce:copyright type="other" year="1990"/>
         </item-info>
         <head>
            <ce:title>Author index to volume 174</ce:title>
         </head>
      </converted-article>
   </xocs:serial-item>
</xocs:doc></originalText></full-text-retrieval-response>